<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-01-27T18:18:23-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">CarissaEats</title><subtitle>A food and travel blog by @CarissaEats, where I share my favorite small businesses, easy recipes, and travel adventures.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Summer in Asia</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/beyond/asia" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Summer in Asia" /><published>2021-01-20T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2021-01-20T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/beyond/asia</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/beyond/asia">&lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/china/heycha1.JPG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;
          Fruity Cheese Tea Trio
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/taiwan/taipeifood.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;
          Oyster Omelette + Noodle Soup
        &lt;/div&gt;        
    &lt;/div&gt;    
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reason I look back on Asia especially fondly is because the foods I’ve grown up eating and learned to love here in the states truly felt at home in Asia – which seems obvious, but only becomes more apparent when you finally go. Yes, the Asian food in America is undisputedly excellent, but the Asian food IN Asia is on another level. The meals can be so simple and “bare bones”, but are elevated when compared to how they taste in America. Chefs in the states who immigrated from Asia often need to adjust their flavorings to pander to a wide variety of taste buds, whereas chefs in China are catering to mostly Chinese consumers, allowing them to stick to their more traditional methods. These photos are from my summer in Asia in 2018, where I was introduced to so many new dishes and elevations of ones I already knew. My dad grew up in China, so he knows his way around and has some fun tidbits to add about some of the foods we tried, which only added to this incredible experience of staying in China. I will also preface this post by saying that a lot of the foods I’m sharing below are non-traditional, but I ate plenty of traditionally Cantonese dishes during my time - I was just enjoying the moment and couldn’t snap a photo!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This post will include mostly photos, but I’ll write about any foods that may need more of a description, connections to other cultures, or have a story I want to share. While I don’t have the exact restaurant names, keep these dishes on your list for the future!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Dishes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&quot;dishes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;h5 id=&quot;guangzhou&quot;&gt;Guangzhou&lt;/h5&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Some people say Cantonese food is the most boring of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://hakkasan.com/stories/eight-culinary-traditions-china/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;Eight Chinese Cuisines&lt;/a&gt;, as it doesn’t pack the kick of Sichuan or Hunan cuisine, but the simplicity of the dishes is the most impressive part. You might be used to seeing Cantonese cuisine through &lt;em&gt;dim sum&lt;/em&gt; (to touch the heart) or &lt;em&gt;yum cha&lt;/em&gt; (to drink tea), which is typically drinking tea with smaller plates. Some popular dishes you might know of are rice rolls drowning in sweet soy sauce (a personal favorite of mine) and char siu (叉烧) bao (baked or steamed roast pork buns). &lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/china/gzchashu.jpg&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;~Fancy~ Char Siu&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/china/gzcafe.JPG&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Char Siu + Beef Chow Fun&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/china/garlicribs.jpg&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Crispy Garlic Ribs&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/china/riceroll.jpg&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;HK-style Cheung Fun&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Above are just a small sampling of Cantonese dishes I got a photo of: char siu, &lt;em&gt;gon chow ngau huo&lt;/em&gt; (beef chow fun), crispy garlic pork ribs, and HK-style cheung fun. Note the distinction between the cheung fun pictured above, and the Cantonese one; HK-style ones are literally tiny rolls, and Cantonese ones are unrolled (but still “rolls), longer, and thinner. It’s pretty much just the shape, but both are shockingly addictive. Enjoy HK-style cheung fun doused in hoisin + peanut sauces (as seen above), and Cantonese ones doused in sweet soy sauce. This is &lt;em&gt;important&lt;/em&gt;. This is NOT the soy sauce you eat with sushi, but a perfect umami and sweet combination that pares very well with the plainness of cheung fun. &lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/china/gzroastpork.jpg&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Siu Yuk Roast Pork&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;  
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/china/roastplatter2.jpg&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Assorted Roast Platter&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/china/gzdumplings.JPG&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Fried Dumplings&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/china/gzpuff.jpg&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;See below!&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Just a miscellaneous collection of food pictured above. Siu yuk, or roast pork, is CRISPY, and there’s no deep frying involved. This roast pork is stuffed with a variety of seasonings and hoisin sauce, which you’ll get a taste of once the pork is cut up. The picture next to the roast pork is a platter of the most popular Cantonese meats, which are char siu, siu yuk, roast duck (different from Peking duck!), as well as the not originally Cantonese drunken chicken. You also see the jellyfish salad, which doesn’t taste like seafood whatsoever.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Now, we all know what dumplings are, but what’s pictured on the right is still an enigma to me two years later. It’s this gorgeous fluffy pudding, soufflé/sponge cake thing covered in sliced nuts. I have virtually no idea what it’s actually intended to be, but it’s definitely something to try out if you ever come across it! &lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h5 id=&quot;taipei&quot;&gt;Taipei&lt;/h5&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/taiwan/beefnoodle1.JPG&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Beef Noodle Soup&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/taiwan/scallionpancake.jpg&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Scallion Pancake&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/taiwan/taipeicorndog.jpg&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Special Corn Dogs&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/taiwan/taiwanxlb.JPG&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Xiao Long Bao&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;The best food in Asia really comes from the no-frills restaurants and the famous Taiwanese night markets. We went to &lt;strong&gt;Raohe&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Shi Lin Night Markets&lt;/strong&gt;, IIRC, but there are plenty of lesser known ones that likely serve as equally good products. &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Those hand-pulled noodles and freshly-wrapped boiled dumplings were from this tiny, open-air shop a few blocks from the hotel we stayed at. And my GOSH, don't even get me started on those scallion pancakes. The scallion pancakes in America don't do these justice! You can get ham, cheese, egg, and a sweet-spicy sauce/glaze as toppings or just get it plain. Fantastic either way.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Those corn dogs are just like Korean corn dogs, which are dipped in rice batter, as opposed to traditional cornmeal batter, coated in panko, and stuffed with mozzarella cheese and/or a hot dog. They’re also dusted with granulated sugar and topped with ketchup, honey mustard, and/or or Japanese mayo. The last photo is &lt;em&gt;xiao long bao&lt;/em&gt;, which I don’t believe are originally Taiwanese, but you may recognize them from the &lt;a href=&quot;https://dintaifungusa.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;Din Tai Fung&lt;/a&gt; empire that is 100% from Taiwan.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h5 id=&quot;singapore&quot;&gt;Singapore&lt;/h5&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/singapore/chashu.jpg&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Chashu (top) and Steak (Bottom) Rice Bowls&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/singapore/frybasket.JPG&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Fry Basket&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/singapore/satay.JPG&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Mixed Satay&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/singapore/spicypork.jpg&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Suan Ni Bai Rou&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;The top two photos are from &lt;a href=&quot;https://pasarbella.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;PasarBella at Suntec City&lt;/a&gt;, an NYC-inspired food hall. I know some people are shaking their heads in disappointment for not eating traditionally Singaporean food, but I remember eating here more out of convenience than anything. Nonetheless, the food was delicious, and there's not really much else to say.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;This satay is from &lt;strong&gt;Newton Food Centre&lt;/strong&gt; -- fun fact, it's where Crazy Rich Asians filmed that intro scene of Nick, Rachel, Colin, and Araminta eat at a hawker centre! We also ate chili crab (one of the national Singaporean dishes), accompanied by mantou (steamed or fried buns - no stuffing), as well as roti prata and quite a few more dishes from various stalls. Next to it is the Sichuan &lt;em&gt;Suan Ni Bai Rou&lt;/em&gt; pork belly. I know this isn't quite Singaporean, but we did eat it in Singapore, so that's why it's under the Singapore &quot;category&quot;. It's a very famous Sichuan dish, and it consists of &lt;em&gt;ultra-thin&lt;/em&gt; pork belly doused in chili-garlic sauce. This is one of Antonia's favorite dishes, but be warned - describing the sauce as &lt;em&gt;just&lt;/em&gt; garlic is being modest. This dish is g a r l i c k y.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;h4 id=&quot;boba-sweets&quot;&gt;Boba + Sweets&lt;/h4&gt;
  &lt;h5 id=&quot;guangzhou&quot;&gt;Guangzhou&lt;/h5&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/china/heycha2.JPG&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Cheese Mango&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/china/heycha3.jpg&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Black Sugar Boba&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/china/gztart1.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Macanese Egg Tarts&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/china/milkfry.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Fried Milk&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;IT’S DESSERT TIMEEEE! I don’t have a preference for sweet or savory, but my sweet tooth was satisfied in Asia! The boba tea, the cheese tea, the tarts, EVERY dessert is incredible there. Above, you see some mango cheese tea, which is mango blended with ice topped with a lightly salted cheese foam, which I drank nearly every day on my journey. At the very top, you also see a strawberry cheese and grape cheese, which are solid competitors for best drink at HeyCha. You also see a black sugar boba, which is similar to brown sugar boba, a thicker and stickier drink topping, but with a more licorice-like taste. I prefer brown sugar, but black sugar boba tastes great, too. &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Below those drinks are Macanese egg tarts, which are inspired by Portuguese tarts, which are one of my favorite warm desserts. The Macanese egg tart shells are flakier and much more layered, compared to their Hong Kong-style counterparts with a crumblier, but still puff pastry-esque crust. Next, I’m ecstatic to present the incredible FRIED MILK!!! Don’t expect a drink to flow out once you bite in, but it’s a milk custard rolled in a thin wrapper (or sometimes a batter). It has only a subtle sweetness, which is ideal for me. I’ve never had the Spanish leche frita, but if it’s anything like this Cantonese variation, I am &lt;em&gt;in&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;h5 id=&quot;taipei&quot;&gt;Taipei&lt;/h5&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/taiwan/brownsugarbub.jpg&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Black Sugar Boba&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/taiwan/bubbletea.JPG&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Fiftea&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/taiwan/7_11_bub.jpg&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Original Boba&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/taiwan/chocolatebao.JPG&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Chocolate Red Bean Bao&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;While brown sugar boba is starting to gain traction in the states, the black sugar boba is not quite on the same level of popularity just yet. I personally don't love the licorice taste of the black sugar, but I for sure see the appeal of this drink. Just as brown sugar, or really any sugar, can be caramelized, black sugar can be as well, and that’s what you see above. The “Fiftea” bubble tea photo next to it was unfortunately more disappointing -- Antonia knew it was a well-known chain, so she suggested we try it. The bubbles were fine, but we didn't love the tea flavor as much. My dad said his milk tea tasted good, so maybe it’s just the fruit teas we had.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;We also went to a 7-Eleven in Taiwan, and much to my pleasant surprise, they had 7-11 Bubble Tea! It was actually quite good, but I do suggest supporting the local milk tea shops. Next to that, there’s the final dessert I share, which is the chocolate red bean bao. If you live in a U.S. state with a Din Tai Fung, you certainly don’t need to go to Taiwan for these, BUT...wow, I love red bean desserts, and this one repurposed those paper-thin dumpling skins I love to hold in some chocolate-y red bean goodness.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;h5 id=&quot;hong-kong&quot;&gt;Hong Kong&lt;/h5&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/hongkong/hkwaffle.jpg&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;That famous &lt;em&gt;gai dan jai&lt;/em&gt; from &lt;strong&gt;Lee Keung Kee North Point Egg Waffles&lt;/strong&gt;. My maternal extended family resides in Hong Kong, so they were excited for me to have my first Hong Kong egg waffle IN Hong Kong! I'm a huuuuuge egg waffle fan, and when I talk to my grandma about how much I love these waffles, we just laugh about the name every time. The name literally means little chicken egg, and we just think the name is so fitting for this dessert. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;button id=&quot;showfoods&quot; class=&quot;showmorephotosbutton&quot; onclick=&quot;toggleFoods()&quot;&gt;( + ) show me the food!&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Activities&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&quot;activities&quot;&gt;
  &lt;h5 id=&quot;guangzhou&quot;&gt;Guangzhou&lt;/h5&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/china/wallofshells.JPG&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Lingnan Impression Park&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/china/lilythepom.jpg&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Lily the Pomeranian&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lingnan Impression Park&lt;/strong&gt;: Stalls of street art and food, along with stunning attractions, like this Wall of Oyster Shells.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Lily is my Guangzhou family's dog. How do you not fall in love with those eyes?!&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Not quite an activity, but I wanted to share her beauty.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
  &lt;h5 id=&quot;taipei&quot;&gt;Taipei&lt;/h5&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/taiwan/chiang-kai-shek.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Chiang Kai-shek Memorial&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/taiwan/taiwanlandscape.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Yangmingshan National Park&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/taiwan/jadebokchoy.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Jade Bok Choy&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/taiwan/meatstone.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Dongpo Pork Stone&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;We didn't have a ton of stops on our trip, but that just meant we got to spend some more time at each! First is the &lt;strong&gt;Chiang Kai Shek Memorial&lt;/strong&gt;, as Chiang Kai-shek, the former leader of the Chinese Nationalist Party, died in Taipei. The memorial had multiple exhibits, so be sure to check those out when you're there.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Next, we checked out &lt;strong&gt;Yangmingshan National Park&lt;/strong&gt;, where there was a volcano, along with a ton of grass-lined valleys and COWS! Definitely smelled like cow dung, but an enjoyable experience nonetheless.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Now...onto the &lt;strong&gt;National Palace Museum&lt;/strong&gt;, home to the Jade Bok Choy and Dongpo Pork Stone! You can see how intricate the details are - they perfectly walk the fine line between ultra-elegant and realistic. &lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h5 id=&quot;hong-kong&quot;&gt;Hong Kong&lt;/h5&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/hongkong/bigbuddha.JPG&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Tian Tan Buddha&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/hongkong/hkclocktower.jpg&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;HK Railway Clock Tower&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tian Tan Buddha&lt;/strong&gt;, or as it's informally known, the Big Buddha! Wow, it was a &lt;em&gt;journey&lt;/em&gt; to get here. You first hop on a gondola, the ride of which took about 30-45 minutes one way, and then, take a decent walk to the steps of the Buddha. The Buddha sits above a hilltop, and the steps are no joke. However, I was truly in awe of this bronze masterpiece, beyond its sheer magnitude. I am nonreligious (I don't even know what I really identify as), but according to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.plm.org.hk/eng/buddha.php&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;Po Lin Monastery&lt;/a&gt;, the statue, which &quot;symbolizes the stability of Hong Kong, prosperity of China and peace on earth&quot;, took 12 years to plan and build. It wasn't ridiculously loud at the top, and I appreciated the peacefulness of the attraction. The Buddha would be very close to the top of my list for places I would like to return to. &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Former &lt;strong&gt;Kowloon-Canton Railway Clock Tower&lt;/strong&gt; is a symbol of &quot;moving on&quot; for the Chinese immigrants who passed through this terminus of Kowloon–Canton Railway to start new lives in Hong Kong. My dad told us we had to visit this clock tower, since my mom and him used to stop by.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;

  &lt;h5 id=&quot;singapore&quot;&gt;Singapore&lt;/h5&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/singapore/gardensbythebay.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Gardens by the Bay&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/singapore/faberpeakbells.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Faber Peak Bells&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/singapore/marinabaysands.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Marina Bay Sands&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/singapore/minimerlion.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Mini Merlion...&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gardens by the Bay&lt;/strong&gt;: One of the most famous Singaporean attractions, you can find beautiful flora and incredible architecture in any of the sub-exhibitions. I visited the Cloud Forest (where this photo was taken) and the Flower Dome. They also have a musical light show at night to check out - it's &lt;em&gt;free&lt;/em&gt;, and you just lie down on a  blanket and look up!&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mount Faber Peak&lt;/strong&gt;: take the Singapore Cable Car up to Faber Peak. There's a giant Bell of Happiness, but also a fence to tie your personalized mini bell.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Antonia in front of the &lt;strong&gt;Marina Bay Sands&lt;/strong&gt;, arguably one of the most famous hotels in the world. &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;This &lt;strong&gt;Merlion&lt;/strong&gt; is the national symbol of Singapore, but also a bit of an inside joke in my family. When my dad decided put Singapore as one of our destinations, he also was adamant about us seeing the giant Merlion. But this one...is ~only~ 8.6 meters tall. Not that it's not huge, but my dad kept saying that the Merlion he visited thirty years ago was far, far taller AND that the giant one was the original Merlion. So we kept looking up &quot;giant Merlion&quot; on Google, but we couldn't find it! Eventually, we discovered it was on Sentosa Island, which is certainly still in Singapore, just not as centrally located. Luckily, Singapore is quite small, so we made the trip to see the lovely Sentosa Merlion, which BTW, is a replica. This one is THIRTY SEVEN meters tall! You can ride an elevator up this giant replica, but we decided it wasn't worth the price. As I was writing this, I unfortunately found out it was permanently closed and demolished just over a year ago 😞 But I'm fortunate to have seen it before Singapore had to say goodbye.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
  
  &lt;p&gt;Without further ado, this is the giant Merlion...&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/singapore/sentosamerlion.jpg&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;Sentosa Merlion&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;button id=&quot;showplaces&quot; class=&quot;showmorephotosbutton&quot; onclick=&quot;togglePlaces()&quot;&gt;( + ) show me where to go!&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope this guide helped you live vicariously through my 2018 self. I thought a lot about how disconnected I felt with my Chinese heritage, but I’ve been on a journey to understand my roots ever since then. Thank you China, Singapore, Taiwan, Hong Kong, and Macau for an amazing, introspective summer. I am so grateful for food on the table and each of these experiences❤️&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/hongkong/hkviews.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;HK Harbor&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="beyond" /><summary type="html">Fruity Cheese Tea Trio Oyster Omelette + Noodle Soup The reason I look back on Asia especially fondly is because the foods I’ve grown up eating and learned to love here in the states truly felt at home in Asia – which seems obvious, but only becomes more apparent when you finally go. Yes, the Asian food in America is undisputedly excellent, but the Asian food IN Asia is on another level. The meals can be so simple and “bare bones”, but are elevated when compared to how they taste in America. Chefs in the states who immigrated from Asia often need to adjust their flavorings to pander to a wide variety of taste buds, whereas chefs in China are catering to mostly Chinese consumers, allowing them to stick to their more traditional methods. These photos are from my summer in Asia in 2018, where I was introduced to so many new dishes and elevations of ones I already knew. My dad grew up in China, so he knows his way around and has some fun tidbits to add about some of the foods we tried, which only added to this incredible experience of staying in China. I will also preface this post by saying that a lot of the foods I’m sharing below are non-traditional, but I ate plenty of traditionally Cantonese dishes during my time - I was just enjoying the moment and couldn’t snap a photo! This post will include mostly photos, but I’ll write about any foods that may need more of a description, connections to other cultures, or have a story I want to share. While I don’t have the exact restaurant names, keep these dishes on your list for the future! Dishes Guangzhou Some people say Cantonese food is the most boring of the Eight Chinese Cuisines, as it doesn’t pack the kick of Sichuan or Hunan cuisine, but the simplicity of the dishes is the most impressive part. You might be used to seeing Cantonese cuisine through dim sum (to touch the heart) or yum cha (to drink tea), which is typically drinking tea with smaller plates. Some popular dishes you might know of are rice rolls drowning in sweet soy sauce (a personal favorite of mine) and char siu (叉烧) bao (baked or steamed roast pork buns). ~Fancy~ Char Siu Char Siu + Beef Chow Fun Crispy Garlic Ribs HK-style Cheung Fun Above are just a small sampling of Cantonese dishes I got a photo of: char siu, gon chow ngau huo (beef chow fun), crispy garlic pork ribs, and HK-style cheung fun. Note the distinction between the cheung fun pictured above, and the Cantonese one; HK-style ones are literally tiny rolls, and Cantonese ones are unrolled (but still “rolls), longer, and thinner. It’s pretty much just the shape, but both are shockingly addictive. Enjoy HK-style cheung fun doused in hoisin + peanut sauces (as seen above), and Cantonese ones doused in sweet soy sauce. This is important. This is NOT the soy sauce you eat with sushi, but a perfect umami and sweet combination that pares very well with the plainness of cheung fun. Siu Yuk Roast Pork Assorted Roast Platter Fried Dumplings See below! Just a miscellaneous collection of food pictured above. Siu yuk, or roast pork, is CRISPY, and there’s no deep frying involved. This roast pork is stuffed with a variety of seasonings and hoisin sauce, which you’ll get a taste of once the pork is cut up. The picture next to the roast pork is a platter of the most popular Cantonese meats, which are char siu, siu yuk, roast duck (different from Peking duck!), as well as the not originally Cantonese drunken chicken. You also see the jellyfish salad, which doesn’t taste like seafood whatsoever. Now, we all know what dumplings are, but what’s pictured on the right is still an enigma to me two years later. It’s this gorgeous fluffy pudding, soufflé/sponge cake thing covered in sliced nuts. I have virtually no idea what it’s actually intended to be, but it’s definitely something to try out if you ever come across it! Taipei Beef Noodle Soup Scallion Pancake Special Corn Dogs Xiao Long Bao The best food in Asia really comes from the no-frills restaurants and the famous Taiwanese night markets. We went to Raohe and Shi Lin Night Markets, IIRC, but there are plenty of lesser known ones that likely serve as equally good products. Those hand-pulled noodles and freshly-wrapped boiled dumplings were from this tiny, open-air shop a few blocks from the hotel we stayed at. And my GOSH, don't even get me started on those scallion pancakes. The scallion pancakes in America don't do these justice! You can get ham, cheese, egg, and a sweet-spicy sauce/glaze as toppings or just get it plain. Fantastic either way. Those corn dogs are just like Korean corn dogs, which are dipped in rice batter, as opposed to traditional cornmeal batter, coated in panko, and stuffed with mozzarella cheese and/or a hot dog. They’re also dusted with granulated sugar and topped with ketchup, honey mustard, and/or or Japanese mayo. The last photo is xiao long bao, which I don’t believe are originally Taiwanese, but you may recognize them from the Din Tai Fung empire that is 100% from Taiwan. Singapore Chashu (top) and Steak (Bottom) Rice Bowls Fry Basket Mixed Satay Suan Ni Bai Rou The top two photos are from PasarBella at Suntec City, an NYC-inspired food hall. I know some people are shaking their heads in disappointment for not eating traditionally Singaporean food, but I remember eating here more out of convenience than anything. Nonetheless, the food was delicious, and there's not really much else to say. This satay is from Newton Food Centre -- fun fact, it's where Crazy Rich Asians filmed that intro scene of Nick, Rachel, Colin, and Araminta eat at a hawker centre! We also ate chili crab (one of the national Singaporean dishes), accompanied by mantou (steamed or fried buns - no stuffing), as well as roti prata and quite a few more dishes from various stalls. Next to it is the Sichuan Suan Ni Bai Rou pork belly. I know this isn't quite Singaporean, but we did eat it in Singapore, so that's why it's under the Singapore &quot;category&quot;. It's a very famous Sichuan dish, and it consists of ultra-thin pork belly doused in chili-garlic sauce. This is one of Antonia's favorite dishes, but be warned - describing the sauce as just garlic is being modest. This dish is g a r l i c k y. Boba + Sweets Guangzhou Cheese Mango Black Sugar Boba Macanese Egg Tarts Fried Milk IT’S DESSERT TIMEEEE! I don’t have a preference for sweet or savory, but my sweet tooth was satisfied in Asia! The boba tea, the cheese tea, the tarts, EVERY dessert is incredible there. Above, you see some mango cheese tea, which is mango blended with ice topped with a lightly salted cheese foam, which I drank nearly every day on my journey. At the very top, you also see a strawberry cheese and grape cheese, which are solid competitors for best drink at HeyCha. You also see a black sugar boba, which is similar to brown sugar boba, a thicker and stickier drink topping, but with a more licorice-like taste. I prefer brown sugar, but black sugar boba tastes great, too. Below those drinks are Macanese egg tarts, which are inspired by Portuguese tarts, which are one of my favorite warm desserts. The Macanese egg tart shells are flakier and much more layered, compared to their Hong Kong-style counterparts with a crumblier, but still puff pastry-esque crust. Next, I’m ecstatic to present the incredible FRIED MILK!!! Don’t expect a drink to flow out once you bite in, but it’s a milk custard rolled in a thin wrapper (or sometimes a batter). It has only a subtle sweetness, which is ideal for me. I’ve never had the Spanish leche frita, but if it’s anything like this Cantonese variation, I am in. Taipei Black Sugar Boba Fiftea Original Boba Chocolate Red Bean Bao While brown sugar boba is starting to gain traction in the states, the black sugar boba is not quite on the same level of popularity just yet. I personally don't love the licorice taste of the black sugar, but I for sure see the appeal of this drink. Just as brown sugar, or really any sugar, can be caramelized, black sugar can be as well, and that’s what you see above. The “Fiftea” bubble tea photo next to it was unfortunately more disappointing -- Antonia knew it was a well-known chain, so she suggested we try it. The bubbles were fine, but we didn't love the tea flavor as much. My dad said his milk tea tasted good, so maybe it’s just the fruit teas we had. We also went to a 7-Eleven in Taiwan, and much to my pleasant surprise, they had 7-11 Bubble Tea! It was actually quite good, but I do suggest supporting the local milk tea shops. Next to that, there’s the final dessert I share, which is the chocolate red bean bao. If you live in a U.S. state with a Din Tai Fung, you certainly don’t need to go to Taiwan for these, BUT...wow, I love red bean desserts, and this one repurposed those paper-thin dumpling skins I love to hold in some chocolate-y red bean goodness. Hong Kong That famous gai dan jai from Lee Keung Kee North Point Egg Waffles. My maternal extended family resides in Hong Kong, so they were excited for me to have my first Hong Kong egg waffle IN Hong Kong! I'm a huuuuuge egg waffle fan, and when I talk to my grandma about how much I love these waffles, we just laugh about the name every time. The name literally means little chicken egg, and we just think the name is so fitting for this dessert. ( + ) show me the food! Activities Guangzhou Lingnan Impression Park Lily the Pomeranian Lingnan Impression Park: Stalls of street art and food, along with stunning attractions, like this Wall of Oyster Shells. Lily is my Guangzhou family's dog. How do you not fall in love with those eyes?! Not quite an activity, but I wanted to share her beauty. Taipei Chiang Kai-shek Memorial Yangmingshan National Park Jade Bok Choy Dongpo Pork Stone We didn't have a ton of stops on our trip, but that just meant we got to spend some more time at each! First is the Chiang Kai Shek Memorial, as Chiang Kai-shek, the former leader of the Chinese Nationalist Party, died in Taipei. The memorial had multiple exhibits, so be sure to check those out when you're there. Next, we checked out Yangmingshan National Park, where there was a volcano, along with a ton of grass-lined valleys and COWS! Definitely smelled like cow dung, but an enjoyable experience nonetheless. Now...onto the National Palace Museum, home to the Jade Bok Choy and Dongpo Pork Stone! You can see how intricate the details are - they perfectly walk the fine line between ultra-elegant and realistic. Hong Kong Tian Tan Buddha HK Railway Clock Tower Tian Tan Buddha, or as it's informally known, the Big Buddha! Wow, it was a journey to get here. You first hop on a gondola, the ride of which took about 30-45 minutes one way, and then, take a decent walk to the steps of the Buddha. The Buddha sits above a hilltop, and the steps are no joke. However, I was truly in awe of this bronze masterpiece, beyond its sheer magnitude. I am nonreligious (I don't even know what I really identify as), but according to the Po Lin Monastery, the statue, which &quot;symbolizes the stability of Hong Kong, prosperity of China and peace on earth&quot;, took 12 years to plan and build. It wasn't ridiculously loud at the top, and I appreciated the peacefulness of the attraction. The Buddha would be very close to the top of my list for places I would like to return to. The Former Kowloon-Canton Railway Clock Tower is a symbol of &quot;moving on&quot; for the Chinese immigrants who passed through this terminus of Kowloon–Canton Railway to start new lives in Hong Kong. My dad told us we had to visit this clock tower, since my mom and him used to stop by. Singapore Gardens by the Bay Faber Peak Bells Marina Bay Sands Mini Merlion... Gardens by the Bay: One of the most famous Singaporean attractions, you can find beautiful flora and incredible architecture in any of the sub-exhibitions. I visited the Cloud Forest (where this photo was taken) and the Flower Dome. They also have a musical light show at night to check out - it's free, and you just lie down on a blanket and look up! Mount Faber Peak: take the Singapore Cable Car up to Faber Peak. There's a giant Bell of Happiness, but also a fence to tie your personalized mini bell. Antonia in front of the Marina Bay Sands, arguably one of the most famous hotels in the world. This Merlion is the national symbol of Singapore, but also a bit of an inside joke in my family. When my dad decided put Singapore as one of our destinations, he also was adamant about us seeing the giant Merlion. But this one...is ~only~ 8.6 meters tall. Not that it's not huge, but my dad kept saying that the Merlion he visited thirty years ago was far, far taller AND that the giant one was the original Merlion. So we kept looking up &quot;giant Merlion&quot; on Google, but we couldn't find it! Eventually, we discovered it was on Sentosa Island, which is certainly still in Singapore, just not as centrally located. Luckily, Singapore is quite small, so we made the trip to see the lovely Sentosa Merlion, which BTW, is a replica. This one is THIRTY SEVEN meters tall! You can ride an elevator up this giant replica, but we decided it wasn't worth the price. As I was writing this, I unfortunately found out it was permanently closed and demolished just over a year ago 😞 But I'm fortunate to have seen it before Singapore had to say goodbye. Without further ado, this is the giant Merlion... Sentosa Merlion ( + ) show me where to go! I hope this guide helped you live vicariously through my 2018 self. I thought a lot about how disconnected I felt with my Chinese heritage, but I’ve been on a journey to understand my roots ever since then. Thank you China, Singapore, Taiwan, Hong Kong, and Macau for an amazing, introspective summer. I am so grateful for food on the table and each of these experiences❤️ HK Harbor</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/beyond/china/heycha1.JPG" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/beyond/china/heycha1.JPG" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Making Mi-so Happy!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jerseyeats/misoteriyaki" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Making Mi-so Happy!" /><published>2021-01-20T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2021-01-20T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jerseyeats/misoteriyaki</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jerseyeats/misoteriyaki">&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/jerseyeats/miso/misoteriyaki1.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;Beef Teriyaki&lt;/div&gt;    
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Serving up everything from teri buns to Korean-style ramen to mixed tempura, &lt;a href=&quot;http://misoteriyaki.com/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Miso Teriyaki&lt;/a&gt; entered the Bergen County dining scene in March 2020. When I saw a teriyaki restaurant coming to Tenafly, it dawned on me that I haven’t had teriyaki in years. Apparently, it’s the unofficial signature dish of Seattle, which now makes me regret not eating it when I had the opportunity to go there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But alas, Miso arrived and according to their logo, they’re based in Seattle! I don’t know their full story, but I would love to interview them to get the full scoop on their roots and why they decided to bring their West Coast food over to &lt;em&gt;freezing Jersey&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Above, you can see their hand trimmed, char-broiled &lt;strong&gt;beef teriyaki&lt;/strong&gt;, which from some angles, kind of just looks like cooked beef. But wow, it packs a punch! If you love beef bulgogi, you may equally enjoy this. The classic “burnt” flavor is present, but not in an overwhelming way that turns you off – if you’ve ever had East Asian barbecue, you know the sensation! You can tell the marinade is deeply embedded throughout the beef and isn’t just added in the last few minutes of cooking. What an incredible dish!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I believe all the teriyaki dishes come with a small container of their teriyaki sauce, but I personally prefer the meat or “substance” (tofu, shrimp, salmon, etc.) of the dish by itself. Save that little sauce vessel for those huge portions of rice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/jerseyeats/miso/yakisoba.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;Chicken Yakisoba&lt;/div&gt;    
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay, vegetable galore in this noodle dish. The amount of veggies in their &lt;strong&gt;chicken yakisoba&lt;/strong&gt; would be my only criticism, but not for a dislike of veggies!! I enjoy vegetables, but felt there was an imbalance of noodle to vegetable. I found this a bit odd, since restaurants typically try to overload with carbs rather than the more expensive vegetables. I enjoyed the chicken and the noodles, as I’m a huuuuuuge “thick egg-type” noodle fan, as opposed to thinner spaghetti-like types. Note that they cook their noodles a little under al-dente, so if you prefer less chewy noodles, just request them to be “fully cooked”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/jerseyeats/miso/chickenkatsu.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Chicken Katsu&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/jerseyeats/miso/ribteriyaki.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt; 
        &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Rib Teriyaki&lt;/div&gt;  
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t know why, but &lt;strong&gt;chicken katsu&lt;/strong&gt; always hits the spot for me. It’s some part of a chicken covered in panko breadcrumbs, BUT OH MY I just love it. Miso serves a katsu sauce that’s not the traditional &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Bull-Dog-Vegetable-Fruit-Tonkatsu-Bottles/dp/B01N5DB4EW&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bull-Dog Tonkatsu Sauce&lt;/a&gt;. I wasn’t able to catch a photo of the sauce, but dare I say, it was better than the Bull-Dog? I may just be making that up – they could very well be the same. Anyway, Miso’s katsu was thinner than I liked, but that’s simply a preference. The katsu is a great pairing to an assortment of otherwise grilled meats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, to the right of the chicken katsu is the &lt;strong&gt;rib teriyaki&lt;/strong&gt;. It’s the winner of these four dishes for me! The ribs are laterally cut – the same way Korean galbi ribs* are. While I think the marinade is likely the same for both, I think the char has the ability to shine more on ribs. With thinner beef, too much char can overpower the taste of the meat itself, while these flanken (lateral) cut ribs need that mild burnt taste to bring out the flavor of the beef.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;fun-fact-if-youve-ever-heard-the-term-la-galbi-the-name-stems-from-either-1-the-korean-communitys-popularization-of-the-dish-in-los-angeles-or-2-the-lateral-cut-style-of-the-ribs&quot;&gt;*Fun fact: If you’ve ever heard the term LA Galbi, the name stems from either 1. the Korean community’s popularization of the dish in Los Angeles or 2. the lateral cut style of the ribs.&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Operating during the pandemic is already a huge challenge, but opening at the beginning of one adds its own obstacles to an already difficult time. I know Miso isn’t alone in this struggle, but if you have the means to support another business right now, keep Miso on your list! They deliver on their commitment to serve exceptional teriyaki, and I hope to try their fried rice and teri bun dishes soon as well.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="jerseyeats" /><summary type="html">Beef Teriyaki Serving up everything from teri buns to Korean-style ramen to mixed tempura, Miso Teriyaki entered the Bergen County dining scene in March 2020. When I saw a teriyaki restaurant coming to Tenafly, it dawned on me that I haven’t had teriyaki in years. Apparently, it’s the unofficial signature dish of Seattle, which now makes me regret not eating it when I had the opportunity to go there. But alas, Miso arrived and according to their logo, they’re based in Seattle! I don’t know their full story, but I would love to interview them to get the full scoop on their roots and why they decided to bring their West Coast food over to freezing Jersey. Above, you can see their hand trimmed, char-broiled beef teriyaki, which from some angles, kind of just looks like cooked beef. But wow, it packs a punch! If you love beef bulgogi, you may equally enjoy this. The classic “burnt” flavor is present, but not in an overwhelming way that turns you off – if you’ve ever had East Asian barbecue, you know the sensation! You can tell the marinade is deeply embedded throughout the beef and isn’t just added in the last few minutes of cooking. What an incredible dish! I believe all the teriyaki dishes come with a small container of their teriyaki sauce, but I personally prefer the meat or “substance” (tofu, shrimp, salmon, etc.) of the dish by itself. Save that little sauce vessel for those huge portions of rice. Chicken Yakisoba Okay, vegetable galore in this noodle dish. The amount of veggies in their chicken yakisoba would be my only criticism, but not for a dislike of veggies!! I enjoy vegetables, but felt there was an imbalance of noodle to vegetable. I found this a bit odd, since restaurants typically try to overload with carbs rather than the more expensive vegetables. I enjoyed the chicken and the noodles, as I’m a huuuuuuge “thick egg-type” noodle fan, as opposed to thinner spaghetti-like types. Note that they cook their noodles a little under al-dente, so if you prefer less chewy noodles, just request them to be “fully cooked”. Chicken Katsu Rib Teriyaki I don’t know why, but chicken katsu always hits the spot for me. It’s some part of a chicken covered in panko breadcrumbs, BUT OH MY I just love it. Miso serves a katsu sauce that’s not the traditional Bull-Dog Tonkatsu Sauce. I wasn’t able to catch a photo of the sauce, but dare I say, it was better than the Bull-Dog? I may just be making that up – they could very well be the same. Anyway, Miso’s katsu was thinner than I liked, but that’s simply a preference. The katsu is a great pairing to an assortment of otherwise grilled meats. Finally, to the right of the chicken katsu is the rib teriyaki. It’s the winner of these four dishes for me! The ribs are laterally cut – the same way Korean galbi ribs* are. While I think the marinade is likely the same for both, I think the char has the ability to shine more on ribs. With thinner beef, too much char can overpower the taste of the meat itself, while these flanken (lateral) cut ribs need that mild burnt taste to bring out the flavor of the beef. *Fun fact: If you’ve ever heard the term LA Galbi, the name stems from either 1. the Korean community’s popularization of the dish in Los Angeles or 2. the lateral cut style of the ribs. Operating during the pandemic is already a huge challenge, but opening at the beginning of one adds its own obstacles to an already difficult time. I know Miso isn’t alone in this struggle, but if you have the means to support another business right now, keep Miso on your list! They deliver on their commitment to serve exceptional teriyaki, and I hope to try their fried rice and teri bun dishes soon as well.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/jerseyeats/miso/misoteriyaki1.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/jerseyeats/miso/misoteriyaki1.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Grandma’s Baozi</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/recipes/grandmabao" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Grandma’s Baozi" /><published>2021-01-06T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2021-01-06T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/recipes/grandmabao</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/recipes/grandmabao">&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/recipes/bao/grandmabao.png&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5GajgDBZeoQ&amp;amp;t=3s&amp;amp;ab_channel=bub&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Watch Antonia’s ~cinematography~ of our grandma making baozi&lt;/a&gt;! Please like, comment, and subscribe to the &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCqH5MDmErneKqkCnYxBGnEA&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;bub YouTube channel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, where she posts vlogs from her apartment provided by her internship, and I even make a cameo once in a while for our “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLXr-C5XyXq8c2sFUzGIP5w5HxpAtvWgYF&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;bake w/ bubs&lt;/a&gt;” series! The recipe is transcribed by Antonia, as my grandma speaks in Cantonese throughout.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I promised Antonia I would promo her videos, because she really works beyond hard on each and every one of them! Between the cover art and animations she creates, she really deserves all the love.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="recipes" /><summary type="html">Watch Antonia’s ~cinematography~ of our grandma making baozi! Please like, comment, and subscribe to the bub YouTube channel, where she posts vlogs from her apartment provided by her internship, and I even make a cameo once in a while for our “bake w/ bubs” series! The recipe is transcribed by Antonia, as my grandma speaks in Cantonese throughout. I promised Antonia I would promo her videos, because she really works beyond hard on each and every one of them! Between the cover art and animations she creates, she really deserves all the love.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/recipes/bao/grandmabao.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/recipes/bao/grandmabao.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">The Croissant Chronicles</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/recipes/croissantchronicles" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Croissant Chronicles" /><published>2020-12-23T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2020-12-23T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/recipes/croissantchronicles</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/recipes/croissantchronicles">&lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/recipes/croissant/croissantportrait1.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/recipes/croissant/croissantportrait3.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I made croissants from scratch for the first time! Ever since my sister, Antonia, a croissant connoisseur (just kidding, she’s only made croissants twice before), told me she made croissants from scratch, I’ve been itching to try making them too. It’s month eight of being totally at home, so we finally decided to tackle this challenge! Many hours later, they were far from perfect, but still the perfect homemade baked good to keep us company. This collaboration is with my big sister, Antonia, an aspiring vlogger.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;watch-our-bake-with-bubs-video-here--like-comment-and-subscribe&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2d7ew5ALNX0&amp;amp;ab_channel=bub&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;WATCH OUR BAKE WITH BUBS VIDEO HERE ~ Like, Comment, AND Subscribe!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/recipes/croissant/croissantfood/croissantsolo1.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/recipes/croissant/croissantfood/blueberrycroissant.JPEG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Recipe adapted from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jocooks.com/recipes/homemade-croissants/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Jo Cooks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; - great recipe!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;croissants-from-scratch&quot;&gt;Croissants From Scratch&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&quot;yields-8-medium-croissants-but-you-can-make-16-smaller-ones-instead&quot;&gt;Yields 8 medium croissants, but you can make ~16 smaller ones instead&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ingredients&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;¾ cup lukewarm milk&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;⅛ cup packed brown sugar&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1½ tsp active dry yeast&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;3½ cups all-purpose flour &lt;em&gt;(may need as little as 3¼ or as much as 4 cups)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;¾ cup salted butter, &lt;em&gt;if using unsalted butter, add ½ tbsp salt&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;½ egg for egg wash&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Lightly stir lukewarm milk, brown sugar, and yeast with a fork in your mixing bowl. Let sit for 5 minutes, until foamy.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Add flour (and salt, &lt;strong&gt;if using unsalted butter&lt;/strong&gt;) to the bowl 1 cup at a time, and mix until soft, elastic, but still a little bit sticky.
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Start off with a sturdy spatula, then move on to kneading with your hands.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Loosely wrap the dough in plastic wrap and place the dough in a bowl. Refrigerate for one hour.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Make. The. Butter. Layer.&lt;/strong&gt; Y’all, this is the moment I was looking forward to the most, because of how fun recipe videos made it look. &lt;em&gt;It was fun.&lt;/em&gt; Cut the butter into evenly sized (especially the &lt;strong&gt;thickness&lt;/strong&gt;; the other dimensions are less important). Arrange the layers into a rectangular formation onto a sheet of plastic wrap (what we did) or parchment paper (what we would recommend). Place another equally-sized sheet on top of the butter rectangle.
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Parchment paper is a lot less clingy than plastic wrap, which is why we recommend it.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;The sheet of plastic/parchment should be considerably larger than the rectangle of butter. I recommend skipping to &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/2d7ew5ALNX0?t=102&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;1:42&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; to see how large our rectangle of wrap was.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Use a rolling pin to roll out on all sides of the butter rectangle. Be very careful when rolling this butter rectangle out. The rectangle shouldn’t be over rolled on any one side, as this would distort the rectangular formation. I recommend alternating the orientation of the rolling pin from vertical to horizontal several times through this process. See &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/2d7ew5ALNX0?t=102&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;2:04&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; to get an idea of what we did for ours.
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;We had a pretty imperfect rectangle, so I wouldn’t be discouraged if yours comes out a bit wonky looking. However, don’t veer too far off the intended rectangle, and definitely try your best to attain that shape!&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Refrigerate the dough&lt;/strong&gt; until use. This is important. You do not want this butter to be melty in the slightest, as the kitchen itself already has heat. This heat will soften your butter with time, but this butter sheet needs to be very firm!&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Flour your work surface, whether that be directly on your countertop or on a large tray (like ours), and roll out the dough into a rectangle that’s about 5 millimeters thick. The other dimensions are a little bit more up to you, because a bunch of different recipes give different sizes. Just make sure that the height of the dough rectangle is about equal to the width of the butter sheet.
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;To clarify, the width is the longest side (in reference to either the individual butter or dough sheet). The height is the shorter dimension.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Place your butter sheet in the center of the dough rectangle. This butter sheet should be ⅓ of the dough - you can think of the dough not &lt;em&gt;currently&lt;/em&gt; in contact with the butter as flaps! These flaps should be just slightly larger than the butter sheet rectangle.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fold these two flaps over the butter sheet one after another, similar to how a letter is folded. Now, move your rolling pin vertically (the “height” or shorter side of the dough should be closest to you) to form another rectangle that is similar sized to the dimensions of the original dough rectangle.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fold the dough rectangle like a letter again (thirds!) Place it on a tray, and wrap the tray in plastic wrap. Refrigerate for one hour.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This step needs to be repeated 3 times, meaning four times in addition to the previous step&lt;/strong&gt;! Move your rolling pin vertically (the “height” or shorter side of the dough should be closest to you) to form another rectangle that is similar sized to the dimensions of the original dough rectangle. Fold the dough rectangle like a letter (in thirds). Place it on a tray, and wrap the tray in plastic wrap. Refrigerate for one hour, &lt;strong&gt;with the exception of the fourth time&lt;/strong&gt;. &lt;em&gt;Refrigerate (at least) overnight only for the fourth (final) time&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Split the dough in half - freeze one half if you plan on using it another time. Roll the dough halves into long, ¼ inch thick rectangles. Cut each rectangle into triangles (more like an isosceles). They really can be any length you want, but you can probably cut 4-12 from each half.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Use a rolling pin to “flatten” each triangle from the wide side up. Stretch out the skinny side and begin rolling your triangle as tightly as possible!&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Place each triangle 1 to 2 inches apart on a baking sheet lined with parchment paper.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Let the croissants rise a bit for one more hour - you’re almost there! Brush them with egg wash.
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;You can also roll them ahead of time, then refrigerate for up to 18 hours prior to baking. Wrap the baking with plastic wrap, not tightly or loosely, but just tight enough so as little moisture as possible escapes.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Preheat the oven to 400°F. Get those croissants in the oven and bake for 8 to 12 minutes at 400°F, then turn down the heat to 375°F and bake them for another 8 to 12 minutes. They should be golden brown!&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Enjoy with whatever spreads, jams, sauces, and anything you like! We tried them with several fruit jams (blueberry, fig, strawberry, and more).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/recipes/croissant/croissantfood/buttersheet.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/recipes/croissant/croissantfood/readytobakecroissant.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes, this is a loooonnnnngggggg process, but I can confidently say the end result is worth it. My sister made them without me one additional time after the filming of this video, and I enjoyed them so much. They are FAR from perfect, but are still an unbelievably good treat. &lt;em&gt;Warning&lt;/em&gt;: they ARE buttery, but equally flaky. Now, start the recipe and devour these little pockets of goodness!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;final-results&quot;&gt;FINAL RESULTS!🤩&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/recipes/croissant/croissantfood/croissant2.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;they-look-like-they-have-such-a-solid-bottom-because-we-over-egg-washed---no-worries-if-this-happens-to-you-as-theyre-still-awesome&quot;&gt;They look like they have such a solid bottom, because we over egg-washed - no worries if this happens to you, as they’re still awesome.&lt;/h6&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="recipes" /><summary type="html">I made croissants from scratch for the first time! Ever since my sister, Antonia, a croissant connoisseur (just kidding, she’s only made croissants twice before), told me she made croissants from scratch, I’ve been itching to try making them too. It’s month eight of being totally at home, so we finally decided to tackle this challenge! Many hours later, they were far from perfect, but still the perfect homemade baked good to keep us company. This collaboration is with my big sister, Antonia, an aspiring vlogger. WATCH OUR BAKE WITH BUBS VIDEO HERE ~ Like, Comment, AND Subscribe! Recipe adapted from Jo Cooks - great recipe! Croissants From Scratch Yields 8 medium croissants, but you can make ~16 smaller ones instead Ingredients ¾ cup lukewarm milk ⅛ cup packed brown sugar 1½ tsp active dry yeast 3½ cups all-purpose flour (may need as little as 3¼ or as much as 4 cups) ¾ cup salted butter, if using unsalted butter, add ½ tbsp salt ½ egg for egg wash Directions Lightly stir lukewarm milk, brown sugar, and yeast with a fork in your mixing bowl. Let sit for 5 minutes, until foamy. Add flour (and salt, if using unsalted butter) to the bowl 1 cup at a time, and mix until soft, elastic, but still a little bit sticky. Start off with a sturdy spatula, then move on to kneading with your hands. Loosely wrap the dough in plastic wrap and place the dough in a bowl. Refrigerate for one hour. Make. The. Butter. Layer. Y’all, this is the moment I was looking forward to the most, because of how fun recipe videos made it look. It was fun. Cut the butter into evenly sized (especially the thickness; the other dimensions are less important). Arrange the layers into a rectangular formation onto a sheet of plastic wrap (what we did) or parchment paper (what we would recommend). Place another equally-sized sheet on top of the butter rectangle. Parchment paper is a lot less clingy than plastic wrap, which is why we recommend it. The sheet of plastic/parchment should be considerably larger than the rectangle of butter. I recommend skipping to 1:42 to see how large our rectangle of wrap was. Use a rolling pin to roll out on all sides of the butter rectangle. Be very careful when rolling this butter rectangle out. The rectangle shouldn’t be over rolled on any one side, as this would distort the rectangular formation. I recommend alternating the orientation of the rolling pin from vertical to horizontal several times through this process. See 2:04 to get an idea of what we did for ours. We had a pretty imperfect rectangle, so I wouldn’t be discouraged if yours comes out a bit wonky looking. However, don’t veer too far off the intended rectangle, and definitely try your best to attain that shape! Refrigerate the dough until use. This is important. You do not want this butter to be melty in the slightest, as the kitchen itself already has heat. This heat will soften your butter with time, but this butter sheet needs to be very firm! Flour your work surface, whether that be directly on your countertop or on a large tray (like ours), and roll out the dough into a rectangle that’s about 5 millimeters thick. The other dimensions are a little bit more up to you, because a bunch of different recipes give different sizes. Just make sure that the height of the dough rectangle is about equal to the width of the butter sheet. To clarify, the width is the longest side (in reference to either the individual butter or dough sheet). The height is the shorter dimension. Place your butter sheet in the center of the dough rectangle. This butter sheet should be ⅓ of the dough - you can think of the dough not currently in contact with the butter as flaps! These flaps should be just slightly larger than the butter sheet rectangle. Fold these two flaps over the butter sheet one after another, similar to how a letter is folded. Now, move your rolling pin vertically (the “height” or shorter side of the dough should be closest to you) to form another rectangle that is similar sized to the dimensions of the original dough rectangle. Fold the dough rectangle like a letter again (thirds!) Place it on a tray, and wrap the tray in plastic wrap. Refrigerate for one hour. This step needs to be repeated 3 times, meaning four times in addition to the previous step! Move your rolling pin vertically (the “height” or shorter side of the dough should be closest to you) to form another rectangle that is similar sized to the dimensions of the original dough rectangle. Fold the dough rectangle like a letter (in thirds). Place it on a tray, and wrap the tray in plastic wrap. Refrigerate for one hour, with the exception of the fourth time. Refrigerate (at least) overnight only for the fourth (final) time. Split the dough in half - freeze one half if you plan on using it another time. Roll the dough halves into long, ¼ inch thick rectangles. Cut each rectangle into triangles (more like an isosceles). They really can be any length you want, but you can probably cut 4-12 from each half. Use a rolling pin to “flatten” each triangle from the wide side up. Stretch out the skinny side and begin rolling your triangle as tightly as possible! Place each triangle 1 to 2 inches apart on a baking sheet lined with parchment paper. Let the croissants rise a bit for one more hour - you’re almost there! Brush them with egg wash. You can also roll them ahead of time, then refrigerate for up to 18 hours prior to baking. Wrap the baking with plastic wrap, not tightly or loosely, but just tight enough so as little moisture as possible escapes. Preheat the oven to 400°F. Get those croissants in the oven and bake for 8 to 12 minutes at 400°F, then turn down the heat to 375°F and bake them for another 8 to 12 minutes. They should be golden brown! Enjoy with whatever spreads, jams, sauces, and anything you like! We tried them with several fruit jams (blueberry, fig, strawberry, and more). Yes, this is a loooonnnnngggggg process, but I can confidently say the end result is worth it. My sister made them without me one additional time after the filming of this video, and I enjoyed them so much. They are FAR from perfect, but are still an unbelievably good treat. Warning: they ARE buttery, but equally flaky. Now, start the recipe and devour these little pockets of goodness! FINAL RESULTS!🤩 They look like they have such a solid bottom, because we over egg-washed - no worries if this happens to you, as they’re still awesome.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/recipes/croissant/croissantportrait1.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/recipes/croissant/croissantportrait1.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">IRVINS x BOPOMOFO</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/stories/irvins-bopomofo" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="IRVINS x BOPOMOFO" /><published>2020-12-09T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2020-12-09T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/stories/irvins-bopomofo</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/stories/irvins-bopomofo">&lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/stories/irvins/irvins5.JPEG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/stories/irvins/irvins2.JPEG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m honored and ecstatic to finally announce that I’m a partner for the exclusive launch of IRVINS Salted Egg Salmon Fish Skin chips!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://eatirvins.com/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;IRVINS Salted Egg&lt;/a&gt; chips turned a signature &lt;em&gt;Salted Egg Crab&lt;/em&gt; dish, which became a local River Valley phenomenon, into some #DangerouslyAddictive snacks. As they say on their website,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;tldr-started-from-a-restaurant-now-theyre-here&quot;&gt;TLDR: Started from a restaurant. Now [&lt;em&gt;they’re&lt;/em&gt;] here.&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had the privilege of travelling to Singapore for a few days in 2018, as its proximity to Guangzhou (where my dad grew up) made it an ideal getaway during my summer in China. Singapore was certainly on my bucket list, primarily for the hawker stands. But WOW, I was completely blown away by the country (island city-state?) - I would take the opportunity to live there in a heartbeat. Okay, probably with further research, too, but you get the point - Singapore felt like home! The humidity would likely be the greatest turn off for most, but I’m pretty indifferent to it. It didn’t feel humid when I was there, so I may just not have that weather association to Singapore, though.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;quick-singapore-facts-singapore-is-majority-ethnic-chinese-with-malay-and-indian-populations-making-up-the-subsequent-major-demographics-singapore-is-also-known-for-being-religiously-diverse&quot;&gt;Quick Singapore Facts: Singapore is majority ethnic Chinese, with Malay and Indian populations making up the subsequent major demographics. Singapore is also known for being religiously diverse.&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being Chinese-American, I feel seen in Singapore, and since I speak English, it’s pretty easy to get around. I hope I can return one day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, back to the stuff about deez chips! You know the basic origin story of IRVINS, and the company now has brick and mortar stores in Southeast Asia. IRVINS is finally ~making their way to the US~, and small businesses, like &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bopomofocafe.com/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;BOPOMOFO Café&lt;/a&gt; are partnering with the company to distribute their wonderful products!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;BOPOMOFO&lt;/em&gt; represents the “Chinese ABCs”. The café seeks to unite and uplift the Asian-American community through food, drink, design, and hospitality - not too far from what I hope food can do for the people I’m with!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/stories/irvins/antoniaphil.JPG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Antonia and Phil @ BPMF&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/stories/irvins/antoniaphildan.JPG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Antonia, Dan, and Phil&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Their food and drink celebrate the identity many Asian-Americans struggle with their whole lives: being too Asian to do or be x, y, or z, but not Asian enough to feel fully accepted by family members “in the motherland”. Dishes, like mapo tofu tater tots, combine the foods you ate at home with the ones from your school cafeteria. Homemade lunches were “too exotic” or “smelly”, yet you craved those flavors when you no longer brought them to school in fear of being made fun of. You start to get used to the chicken fingers and fries at school, and heck, you even start to like them. And that’s okay! BOPOMOFO embraces that and lets you know you’re not alone when you’re in their company. I’ve never eaten there, but Antonia goes to college very close by, and she got the opportunity to meet Phil, BOPOMOFO’s co-owner that you may recognize from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/user/WongFuProductions&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Wong Fu Productions&lt;/a&gt;, a true pioneer in Asian-American media. Antonia raves about their food, and I trust her taste. BOPOMOFO has become integral to the San Gabriel Valley (the 626 and beyond) community, and they’re aware of the platform they have and are using it for good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, they’ve partnered with IRVINS as one of the limited distributors of the Salted Egg Salmon Fish Skins! The fish skins are extremely popular in Southeast Asia, but the salmon fish skin was created specifically for American and Canadian taste buds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They are, indeed, #DANGEROUSLYADDICTIVE. I am not a huge fish skin person, but these chips could change that for me. The buzz word, &lt;em&gt;umami&lt;/em&gt;, is the best way to describe these.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/stories/irvins/irvins1.JPEG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/stories/irvins/irvins4.JPEG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They’re made with the follow ultra-fresh ingredients, straight from their website:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Salted duck egg yolk, a familiar ingredient commonly used in Asian dishes.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Curry leaves, bringing out the fragrance in our snacks.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Red chili pepper, giving our snacks a slight kick while enhancing the salted egg taste.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some might be frightened by the idea of a fried fish skin, but PLEASE don’t knock it until you try it. I know some of my followers may be vegetarian or vegan, so I understand that this product may not fit all dietary restrictions. But if you don’t have any, give them a shot - they’re a true delicacy worth every bite. Enter my giveaway or &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bopomofocafe.com/market&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;order them from BOPOMOFO&lt;/a&gt; today. My giveaway closes December 16th at 5:00PM EST, and you can enter as many times as you’d like by tagging a different friend in separate comments. Sharing my giveaway post on your story will also grant an extra entry! Full details &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/carissaeats/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;on the post&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/stories/irvins/enjoyirvins.JPEG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/stories/irvins/irvins3.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;📣GO SUPPORT IRVINS AND BOPOMOFO📣&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/stories/irvins/btsirvins.JPEG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;BTS of Photoshoot (ft. Cheese Puff Tiger)&lt;/div&gt;    
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="stories" /><summary type="html">I’m honored and ecstatic to finally announce that I’m a partner for the exclusive launch of IRVINS Salted Egg Salmon Fish Skin chips! IRVINS Salted Egg chips turned a signature Salted Egg Crab dish, which became a local River Valley phenomenon, into some #DangerouslyAddictive snacks. As they say on their website, TLDR: Started from a restaurant. Now [they’re] here. I had the privilege of travelling to Singapore for a few days in 2018, as its proximity to Guangzhou (where my dad grew up) made it an ideal getaway during my summer in China. Singapore was certainly on my bucket list, primarily for the hawker stands. But WOW, I was completely blown away by the country (island city-state?) - I would take the opportunity to live there in a heartbeat. Okay, probably with further research, too, but you get the point - Singapore felt like home! The humidity would likely be the greatest turn off for most, but I’m pretty indifferent to it. It didn’t feel humid when I was there, so I may just not have that weather association to Singapore, though. Quick Singapore Facts: Singapore is majority ethnic Chinese, with Malay and Indian populations making up the subsequent major demographics. Singapore is also known for being religiously diverse. Being Chinese-American, I feel seen in Singapore, and since I speak English, it’s pretty easy to get around. I hope I can return one day. Now, back to the stuff about deez chips! You know the basic origin story of IRVINS, and the company now has brick and mortar stores in Southeast Asia. IRVINS is finally ~making their way to the US~, and small businesses, like BOPOMOFO Café are partnering with the company to distribute their wonderful products! BOPOMOFO represents the “Chinese ABCs”. The café seeks to unite and uplift the Asian-American community through food, drink, design, and hospitality - not too far from what I hope food can do for the people I’m with! Antonia and Phil @ BPMF Antonia, Dan, and Phil Their food and drink celebrate the identity many Asian-Americans struggle with their whole lives: being too Asian to do or be x, y, or z, but not Asian enough to feel fully accepted by family members “in the motherland”. Dishes, like mapo tofu tater tots, combine the foods you ate at home with the ones from your school cafeteria. Homemade lunches were “too exotic” or “smelly”, yet you craved those flavors when you no longer brought them to school in fear of being made fun of. You start to get used to the chicken fingers and fries at school, and heck, you even start to like them. And that’s okay! BOPOMOFO embraces that and lets you know you’re not alone when you’re in their company. I’ve never eaten there, but Antonia goes to college very close by, and she got the opportunity to meet Phil, BOPOMOFO’s co-owner that you may recognize from Wong Fu Productions, a true pioneer in Asian-American media. Antonia raves about their food, and I trust her taste. BOPOMOFO has become integral to the San Gabriel Valley (the 626 and beyond) community, and they’re aware of the platform they have and are using it for good. So, they’ve partnered with IRVINS as one of the limited distributors of the Salted Egg Salmon Fish Skins! The fish skins are extremely popular in Southeast Asia, but the salmon fish skin was created specifically for American and Canadian taste buds. They are, indeed, #DANGEROUSLYADDICTIVE. I am not a huge fish skin person, but these chips could change that for me. The buzz word, umami, is the best way to describe these. They’re made with the follow ultra-fresh ingredients, straight from their website: Salted duck egg yolk, a familiar ingredient commonly used in Asian dishes. Curry leaves, bringing out the fragrance in our snacks. Red chili pepper, giving our snacks a slight kick while enhancing the salted egg taste. Some might be frightened by the idea of a fried fish skin, but PLEASE don’t knock it until you try it. I know some of my followers may be vegetarian or vegan, so I understand that this product may not fit all dietary restrictions. But if you don’t have any, give them a shot - they’re a true delicacy worth every bite. Enter my giveaway or order them from BOPOMOFO today. My giveaway closes December 16th at 5:00PM EST, and you can enter as many times as you’d like by tagging a different friend in separate comments. Sharing my giveaway post on your story will also grant an extra entry! Full details on the post. 📣GO SUPPORT IRVINS AND BOPOMOFO📣 BTS of Photoshoot (ft. Cheese Puff Tiger)</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/stories/irvins/irvins2.JPEG" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/stories/irvins/irvins2.JPEG" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Turkey Day 🥧</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/stories/thanksgiving" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Turkey Day 🥧" /><published>2020-11-26T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2020-11-26T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/stories/thanksgiving</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/stories/thanksgiving">&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/stories/thanksgiving/pumpkinpie.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Happy Turkey Day y’all! I wanted to say what I’m thankful for, recap how I celebrated for the past few years (and what I’m doing today), and share some Thanksgiving recipes from my favorite food bloggers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So what does Thanksgiving mean to me?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;i-want-to-preface-this-by-saying-this-post-is-about-what-im-grateful-for-and-what-ive-done-on-thanksgiving-day-for-the-past-few-years-you-can-practice-gratitude-while-still-acknowledging-thanksgivings-problematic-history--in-what-the-day-represents-to-indigenous-people--and-there-are-so-many-resources-out-there-to-educate-yourself-and-stop-perpetuating-the-myths-we-grew-up-learning&quot;&gt;I want to preface this by saying this post is about what I’m grateful for, and what I’ve done on Thanksgiving Day for the past few years. You can practice gratitude, while still acknowledging Thanksgiving’s problematic history – in what the day represents to Indigenous people – and there are so many resources out there to educate yourself and stop perpetuating the myths we grew up learning.&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In elementary and part of middle school, the Chinese community in my town would frequently have get-togethers (we used to hang out a lot!), and I would always look forward to the main event of the year: Thanksgiving dinner. Most, if not all of us (my town’s Chinese community), don’t have any extended family in the states, so our communal heritage brought us even closer as friends. As the years passed, though, we’ve lowered it on our priorities list. Quarantine makes me feel even more nostalgic about those times, but I remain hopeful about seeing them in the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But anyway…in the past few years, I’ve felt the magic of this four-day weekend fizzle out, but I still feel an immense appreciation for this quick getaway from the hecticness of school. I also spend this time to share my gratitude for people who’ve made a remarkable impact in my life in the past 11 months.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For 2020, I have a lot to be grateful for. Yes, it’s been a rough year; I’ve had to be on lockdown completely for the past eight months and be &lt;em&gt;almost excessively&lt;/em&gt; cautious, because I live with my grandma. It has definitely taken a toll on me, but I’ve had time to reflect on myself about many aspects of my life. This isn’t my journal, so I don’t want to delve in too deep, but I still want to share a a short list of the many things I’ve been especially thankful for this year…here it is:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I’ve gotten to cultivate a relationship with my dad that wouldn’t have had the time to be nurtured in other circumstances (and that is &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; to take away from how this pandemic has impacted millions; COVID-19 to have never happened would be ideal). Have we had our &lt;em&gt;very fair&lt;/em&gt; share of quarrels and times we’ve needed to spend apart? Absolutely. But I learned to empathize with him like I had never before, and that’s just one thing to be thankful for.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Simply having the privilege to stay at home. My dad’s been working from home for at least 15 years now, so our family situation was minimally affected. Please wear a mask &lt;em&gt;if&lt;/em&gt; you choose to see anyone outside the people you live with – do it for the people who do not have the privilege to stay at home (essential and frontline workers).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;This. blog. I have no idea what 2020 would be without this. Even if no one is reading this, I am incredibly lucky to use this platform as a way to share my stories behind food and the businesses I want to share. I’m not too caught up with the size of my audience, because I do this for myself and my passion for culinary adventures. Building this blog from scratch is my ultimate passion project: there’s always something to be done, whether it’s the inner framework, the CSS design, the stories. And I cherish every moment with it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/stories/thanksgiving/shackfuyupork.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;
        Iberico Pork Pluma
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 2016, my dad, Antonia, and I took our first trip in quite some time after we had a big event in our life happen earlier in the year. On Thanksgiving Day 2016, we headed to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bonedaddies.com/restaurant/shackfuyu/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Shack-Fuyu: The Japanese Restaurant by Bone Daddies&lt;/a&gt;. I kid you not, returning to this place is on my bucket list. Shack-Fuyu is the type of sit-down restaurant I’m most into - a spin on East Asian food with signature dishes and desserts. This spin doesn’t need to be a “modern” take, but needs to have a connection to the chef, in whichever way that may be. This dish is the Iberico Pork Pluma with Spring Onion and Black Pepper Miso. Get the Kinako French Toast with Matcha Soft Serve too. &lt;em&gt;Absolute chef’s kiss&lt;/em&gt;…okay, back to the Thanksgiving stuff. I went off on a tangent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/stories/thanksgiving/chickiesandpetes.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Crab Fries from Chickie’s &amp;amp; Pete’s, Philly Airport (2018)&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/stories/thanksgiving/becbagel2.JPG&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Bacon, Egg, Cheese Bagel from Celebrity Bagels (2019)&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 2017, I remember it being a Chinese get together. It’s only a vague memory, but my dad made a point about this gathering being one of my sister’s last before heading off to college. In 2018, my dad and I were on a flight to visit Antonia! We flew from the Philly airport (far cheaper than from JFK), so that day was just getting to the airport, waiting (we ate crab fries 😋), flying, and eating at pretty much the only restaurant still open on Thanksgiving day (a Hong Kong café, IIRC). That weekend remains one of the favorite times in my life thus far. I was “homesick” for my sister, and it couldn’t have been a better getaway. Last year, I spent it by eating a BEC from Celebrity Bagels and just watching Netflix. This year will probably be similar: I’ll be eating some good food, taking a break, and hanging with Antonia. And I cannot wait.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To finish off, I want to share some Thanksgiving recipes from my favorite food bloggers. Some are more traditional, but some may be unexpected combinations or fusion flavors. Enjoy (even if it may be too late to try these out for this year)!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://seonkyounglongest.com/fried-rice-stuffing/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Fried Rice Stuffing&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;I’ve been a &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://seonkyounglongest.com/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Seonkyoung Longest&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; fan since the beginning! Her backstory is not without its challenges, but is inspiring when you see where she is today. She creates Korean, Chinese, and Japanese favorites, but also makes more experimental recipes like this one. She has a &lt;a href=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Korean-glazed&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://seonkyounglongest.com/how-to-cook-lemongrass-turkey/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;lemongrass&lt;/a&gt; turkey and &lt;a href=&quot;https://seonkyounglongest.com/cranberry-sauce/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;~spicy~ cranberry sauce&lt;/a&gt; recipe to check out as well. Fried rice stuffing blends two of my identities together (I am Chinese-American after all!), so I’m definitely optimistic about the results!&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://iamafoodblog.com/green-bean-casserole/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Green Bean Casserole&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;The classic green bean casserole! I loveeeee the French-fried onions on the top of these. &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://iamafoodblog.com/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;i am a food blog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; makes a ton of Asian/Asian-inspired recipes, along with a variety of other cuisines. This husband-wife duo has a stunning blog that I’ve followed for years, and you’ll be endlessly scrolling through their recipe index (not complaining though). They also have a &lt;a href=&quot;https://iamafoodblog.com/thanksgiving/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;guide to downsize your Thanksgiving&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.halfbakedharvest.com/maple-pecan-sticky-buns/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Extra Sticky Maple Pecan Sticky Buns&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Like cinnamon rolls, but without the cream cheese frosting. It’s perfect for those with a lot of baking ingredients (flour, eggs, yeast, sugar, cinnamon, etc.), but don’t have cream cheese. I am those.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.halfbakedharvest.com/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Half Baked Harvest&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;feels&lt;/em&gt; exactly the way it should sound. It’s warm, comforting, and feels like home.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.halfbakedharvest.com/sweet-potato-pie-dutch-baby/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Sweet Potato Pie Dutch Baby&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Another &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.halfbakedharvest.com/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Half Baked Harvest&lt;/a&gt; one. A homey pie favorite turned into a pancake - can’t get better than that.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://mynameisyeh.com/mynameisyeh/2018/8/overnight-cinnamon-rolls-with-tahini-cream-frosting&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Cinnamon Rolls with Tahini Cream Frosting and Pistachio Rose Dukkah&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;These rolls &lt;em&gt;do&lt;/em&gt; have cream cheese frosting, but heck, this was too cool of a recipe not to share! &lt;a href=&quot;https://mynameisyeh.com&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Molly Yeh&lt;/a&gt; is a Jewish-Chinese musician turned cookbook author and farm girl. I’m sure she’s still a musician at her core, but I admire her most as an awesome food blogger with tons of narratives to share! She certainly draws inspiration from her experiences in all different walks of life, whether it be the city AND farm girl in her or her multiracial background.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/stories/thanksgiving/bmbcheesecake3.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m also enjoying this Cranberry and Goat Cheese Cheesecake from &lt;a href=&quot;https://mynameisyeh.com/mynameisyeh/2018/8/overnight-cinnamon-rolls-with-tahini-cream-frosting&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Black Magic Bakehouse&lt;/a&gt;. I may do a future post for it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ENJOY YOUR TURKEY DAY Y’ALL! 🦃 (turkey isn’t on everyone’s table, but the point isn’t any different 🥔) Stay safe, and I’m sending all my positivity your way!!!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="stories" /><summary type="html">Happy Turkey Day y’all! I wanted to say what I’m thankful for, recap how I celebrated for the past few years (and what I’m doing today), and share some Thanksgiving recipes from my favorite food bloggers. So what does Thanksgiving mean to me? I want to preface this by saying this post is about what I’m grateful for, and what I’ve done on Thanksgiving Day for the past few years. You can practice gratitude, while still acknowledging Thanksgiving’s problematic history – in what the day represents to Indigenous people – and there are so many resources out there to educate yourself and stop perpetuating the myths we grew up learning. In elementary and part of middle school, the Chinese community in my town would frequently have get-togethers (we used to hang out a lot!), and I would always look forward to the main event of the year: Thanksgiving dinner. Most, if not all of us (my town’s Chinese community), don’t have any extended family in the states, so our communal heritage brought us even closer as friends. As the years passed, though, we’ve lowered it on our priorities list. Quarantine makes me feel even more nostalgic about those times, but I remain hopeful about seeing them in the future. But anyway…in the past few years, I’ve felt the magic of this four-day weekend fizzle out, but I still feel an immense appreciation for this quick getaway from the hecticness of school. I also spend this time to share my gratitude for people who’ve made a remarkable impact in my life in the past 11 months. For 2020, I have a lot to be grateful for. Yes, it’s been a rough year; I’ve had to be on lockdown completely for the past eight months and be almost excessively cautious, because I live with my grandma. It has definitely taken a toll on me, but I’ve had time to reflect on myself about many aspects of my life. This isn’t my journal, so I don’t want to delve in too deep, but I still want to share a a short list of the many things I’ve been especially thankful for this year…here it is: I’ve gotten to cultivate a relationship with my dad that wouldn’t have had the time to be nurtured in other circumstances (and that is not to take away from how this pandemic has impacted millions; COVID-19 to have never happened would be ideal). Have we had our very fair share of quarrels and times we’ve needed to spend apart? Absolutely. But I learned to empathize with him like I had never before, and that’s just one thing to be thankful for. Simply having the privilege to stay at home. My dad’s been working from home for at least 15 years now, so our family situation was minimally affected. Please wear a mask if you choose to see anyone outside the people you live with – do it for the people who do not have the privilege to stay at home (essential and frontline workers). This. blog. I have no idea what 2020 would be without this. Even if no one is reading this, I am incredibly lucky to use this platform as a way to share my stories behind food and the businesses I want to share. I’m not too caught up with the size of my audience, because I do this for myself and my passion for culinary adventures. Building this blog from scratch is my ultimate passion project: there’s always something to be done, whether it’s the inner framework, the CSS design, the stories. And I cherish every moment with it. Iberico Pork Pluma In 2016, my dad, Antonia, and I took our first trip in quite some time after we had a big event in our life happen earlier in the year. On Thanksgiving Day 2016, we headed to Shack-Fuyu: The Japanese Restaurant by Bone Daddies. I kid you not, returning to this place is on my bucket list. Shack-Fuyu is the type of sit-down restaurant I’m most into - a spin on East Asian food with signature dishes and desserts. This spin doesn’t need to be a “modern” take, but needs to have a connection to the chef, in whichever way that may be. This dish is the Iberico Pork Pluma with Spring Onion and Black Pepper Miso. Get the Kinako French Toast with Matcha Soft Serve too. Absolute chef’s kiss…okay, back to the Thanksgiving stuff. I went off on a tangent. Crab Fries from Chickie’s &amp;amp; Pete’s, Philly Airport (2018) Bacon, Egg, Cheese Bagel from Celebrity Bagels (2019) In 2017, I remember it being a Chinese get together. It’s only a vague memory, but my dad made a point about this gathering being one of my sister’s last before heading off to college. In 2018, my dad and I were on a flight to visit Antonia! We flew from the Philly airport (far cheaper than from JFK), so that day was just getting to the airport, waiting (we ate crab fries 😋), flying, and eating at pretty much the only restaurant still open on Thanksgiving day (a Hong Kong café, IIRC). That weekend remains one of the favorite times in my life thus far. I was “homesick” for my sister, and it couldn’t have been a better getaway. Last year, I spent it by eating a BEC from Celebrity Bagels and just watching Netflix. This year will probably be similar: I’ll be eating some good food, taking a break, and hanging with Antonia. And I cannot wait. To finish off, I want to share some Thanksgiving recipes from my favorite food bloggers. Some are more traditional, but some may be unexpected combinations or fusion flavors. Enjoy (even if it may be too late to try these out for this year)! Fried Rice Stuffing I’ve been a Seonkyoung Longest fan since the beginning! Her backstory is not without its challenges, but is inspiring when you see where she is today. She creates Korean, Chinese, and Japanese favorites, but also makes more experimental recipes like this one. She has a Korean-glazed and lemongrass turkey and ~spicy~ cranberry sauce recipe to check out as well. Fried rice stuffing blends two of my identities together (I am Chinese-American after all!), so I’m definitely optimistic about the results! Green Bean Casserole The classic green bean casserole! I loveeeee the French-fried onions on the top of these. i am a food blog makes a ton of Asian/Asian-inspired recipes, along with a variety of other cuisines. This husband-wife duo has a stunning blog that I’ve followed for years, and you’ll be endlessly scrolling through their recipe index (not complaining though). They also have a guide to downsize your Thanksgiving! Extra Sticky Maple Pecan Sticky Buns Like cinnamon rolls, but without the cream cheese frosting. It’s perfect for those with a lot of baking ingredients (flour, eggs, yeast, sugar, cinnamon, etc.), but don’t have cream cheese. I am those. Half Baked Harvest feels exactly the way it should sound. It’s warm, comforting, and feels like home. Sweet Potato Pie Dutch Baby Another Half Baked Harvest one. A homey pie favorite turned into a pancake - can’t get better than that. Cinnamon Rolls with Tahini Cream Frosting and Pistachio Rose Dukkah These rolls do have cream cheese frosting, but heck, this was too cool of a recipe not to share! Molly Yeh is a Jewish-Chinese musician turned cookbook author and farm girl. I’m sure she’s still a musician at her core, but I admire her most as an awesome food blogger with tons of narratives to share! She certainly draws inspiration from her experiences in all different walks of life, whether it be the city AND farm girl in her or her multiracial background. I’m also enjoying this Cranberry and Goat Cheese Cheesecake from Black Magic Bakehouse. I may do a future post for it! ENJOY YOUR TURKEY DAY Y’ALL! 🦃 (turkey isn’t on everyone’s table, but the point isn’t any different 🥔) Stay safe, and I’m sending all my positivity your way!!!</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/stories/thanksgiving/pumpkinpie.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/stories/thanksgiving/pumpkinpie.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Stories of My Favorite Foods</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/stories/favoritefoods" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Stories of My Favorite Foods" /><published>2020-11-04T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2020-11-04T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/stories/favoritefoods</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/stories/favoritefoods">&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/stories/favoritefoods/katsu.JPG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;Chicken Katsu from Mitsuwa&lt;/div&gt;    
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Food represents celebration, warmth, and unity to me. At its core, food brings people together, whether it’s an excuse to catch up with old friends or just enjoying a meal with the people you love. Food helps us get through tough times, but makes the happy times even sweeter. There’s more about how I got into cooking and food on my &lt;a href=&quot;/aboutme.html&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;About Me&lt;/a&gt; page, but today, I’m here to share the memories attached to my favorite foods!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/china/gzcafe.JPG&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Beef Chow Fun + Char Siu Fan&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/stories/favoritefoods/triodumpling.jpg&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Shanghainese Trio&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Gon chow ngau huo&lt;/em&gt;, or beef chow fun, is a popular Cantonese dish that’s pretty much just fresh rice noodles, which are sticky if not constantly tossed in the wok, soy sauce, thin steak, mung bean sprouts, scallions, but packs a punch of flavor in every bite. I’ve been eating this dish for as long as I can remember, yet I was not always a fan of it. My dad absolutely loves this dish, though, so it’s grown on me a ton. It tastes great with other roast meats, as seen in the char siu above too. Char siu is Cantonese honey-barbecued pork, which tastes great with plain rice or chopped in a fried rice. There are plenty of roast shops in Chinatown to buy both char siu + gon chow ngau huo, so I’ll try to compile a list of shops for the future. It’s such a cheap meal, and there’s no better food deals than Chinatowns!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The “Shanghainese Trio”, the nickname I gave these three dishes, consists of &lt;em&gt;chong you bing&lt;/em&gt;, or scallion pancakes, fried dumplings, and &lt;em&gt;sheng jian bao&lt;/em&gt;, or pan-fried baos. I love these three dishes from Shanghai 21 (formerly Shanghai Asian Manor). I haven’t been there since it was known as the former, but their scallion pancakes are extremely crunchy and fluffy, and these baos and dumplings are stuffed with so much flavor. I can’t vouch for how these taste now, but regardless of if these dishes are made by my Grandma or at Shanghai 21, I will always keep these dishes on my favorites list.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/losangeles/okonomiyaki.JPG&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;
        GOAM - Green Onions and Mayo
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I praised the glorious okonomiyaki on my &lt;a href=&quot;/beyond/losangeles#okonomiyaki&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;Los Angeles&lt;/a&gt; post, so explore it over there!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/china/cheesetea.jpg&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Mango Cheese Tea&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/hongkong/hkwaffle.jpg&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Gai Dan Jai&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cheese tea, the drink phenomenon from China, is as interesting as it sounds. I hadn’t been to China since I was around 8 years old, but on my first trip to China in 2017, Antonia and I became obsessed after our first introduction to it. The “cheese” is a sweet cream cheese foam sprinkled with salt, which adds a perfect savory note to the drink. I urge you to try this should the opportunity arise, and not to let the daunting title scare you away! &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.heytea.com/aboutUsEn.html&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HeyCha&lt;/a&gt;, originally from Guangdong and pictured above, is the pioneer of cheese tea in Asia, and people wait hours upon hours to grab a cup of it. It is very, very worth it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Gai dan jai&lt;/em&gt;, or egg waffles, are an absolute contender for favorite dessert (excluding boba or cheese tea). The egg whites folded into the batter differentiate gai dan jai from standard Belgian waffles, along with a little custard powder and tapioca starch that create a slight chewiness. I had my first traditional HK egg waffle from Lee Keung Kee North Point Egg Waffles in Tsim Sha Tsui, Hong Kong, and it definitely met my expectations. &lt;a href=&quot;http://wowfulls.com/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Wowfulls&lt;/a&gt; has changed the egg waffle game in NYC, as they make egg waffle sundaes and have created pizza egg waffles in the past, so I encourage you to catch them at any upcoming popups!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/stories/favoritefoods/tteokbokki.JPG&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;
        Cheese Tteokbokki
    &lt;/div&gt;    
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t have a specific memory attached to these rice cakes, other than that the first time I had them, I devoured them. Korean rice cakes smothered in gochujang (chili paste) sauce and covered in gooey mozzarella cheese. Enough said ~&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/stories/favoritefoods/mightyquinns.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Barbecue Burnt Ends + More&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/stories/favoritefoods/arthurssteak.JPG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Ribeye Steak + Caesar Salad&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These ribs, burnt ends, and brisket are from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mightyquinnsbbq.com/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Mighty Quinn’s&lt;/a&gt;. I just love burnt ends, there’s not really another explanation 😂 The steak and salad are from &lt;a href=&quot;https://arthurshoboken.com/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Arthur’s Steakhouse&lt;/a&gt; in Hoboken. Before my dad made the full time switch to working from home (like over 14 years ago), he used to eat here for coworker meals and bring leftovers home for me and my sister. We became obsessed with their garlic bread, and eventually, got to eat in the restaurant. Arthur’s makes an incredible chicken caesar salad and “Our Steak”, a 24oz marbled Rib Eye, served with Arthur’s Potatoes. This is another restaurant I remember eating at for years, so I can’t wait to return one day and bite into their sometimes burnt, nonetheless tasty, potatoes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/stories/favoritefoods/becbagel.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;
        B.E.C. Bagel
    &lt;/div&gt;    
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This beautiful bacon, egg, and cheese bagel from Celebrity Bagels, a Tenafly staple, is one heck of special Sunday morning treat. I get mine with salt, pepper, and ketchup on an everything bagel, since I enjoy the variety of seasonings on top.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/stories/favoritefoods/tofupudding.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;
        Tofu Pudding
    &lt;/div&gt;    
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I really got into &lt;em&gt;dou fu hua&lt;/em&gt;, or tofu pudding, this year, when my dad and I went to Chinatown in February. This was not my first time trying it, but I was not as &lt;em&gt;obsessed&lt;/em&gt; with it until then. Its primary ingredient is tofu, and although it may just seem like a bowl of soft tofu, it is really an extraordinary canvas for any condiments you like. The flavor itself is very neutral, meaning you can go either sweet or savory with it. Sweet dou fu hua is topped with a brown sugar syrup, which is how I typically eat it and is as seen above. Savory dou fu hua is topped with soy sauce, vinegar, chili oil, and scallions. I don’t think I’ve ever had the savory one, but it’s certainly one I’d love to try. My family likes it too, but I could eat the whole quart this pudding comes in!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/stories/favoritefoods/claypotrice.JPG&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Claypot Rice&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/stories/favoritefoods/cheesebakedrice.JPG&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Cheese-Baked Rice&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I figured I could finish this list off by tying it back to my roots. &lt;em&gt;Bao zai fan&lt;/em&gt;, or claypot rice, and &lt;em&gt;cheese-baked rice&lt;/em&gt; are two popular Hong Kong café items. Claypot rice is typically topped with &lt;em&gt;lap cheong&lt;/em&gt;, or Chinese sausage, and &lt;em&gt;choi sum&lt;/em&gt;, or Chinese broccoli, but this one is topped with lamb chops and fried egg. We have a claypot at home, and it really makes meals special, since it sustains high temperatures. The pot browns the cooked rice, creating a nutty, toasty flavor unable to be replicated by just putting it in the oven.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The cheese-baked rice sounds a little odd, but everything about it works. It’s almost like a cheese pizza with a rice base. I’ve noticed a lot of Asian tomato sauces are a lot sweeter than their Italian counterparts, and the sauce on this one has a light bell pepper note as well. I’m not a fan of peppers at all, but I &lt;em&gt;will&lt;/em&gt; eat them if they’re in this rice. The cheese is almost a nod to Hong Kong’s “East Meets West” background, when HK was a Crown Colony of the British empire. My parents lived in Guangzhou, and much of my maternal extended family lives in Hong Kong today, so eating these dishes is a taste of my Hong Kong memories.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;both-pictures-were-taken-at-xo-kitchen-restaurant食坊-my-familys-go-to-in-manhattan-chinatown-pre-pandemic-they-make-dumplings-wrapped-in-an-ultra-thin-eggy-wrapper-that-are-a-must-try-here-too&quot;&gt;Both pictures were taken at XO Kitchen Restaurant食坊, my family’s go-to in Manhattan Chinatown pre-pandemic. They make dumplings wrapped in an ultra-thin, eggy wrapper that are a must-try here, too.&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is by no means an exclusive list - I have far too many foods I would consider a 20 on a 1 to 10 scale of strongly dislike to absolutely devour, so I’ll likely be updating the list in the future. I hope you enjoyed reading some of the reasons why I appreciate (and dream of) these foods a little extra.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="stories" /><summary type="html">Chicken Katsu from Mitsuwa Food represents celebration, warmth, and unity to me. At its core, food brings people together, whether it’s an excuse to catch up with old friends or just enjoying a meal with the people you love. Food helps us get through tough times, but makes the happy times even sweeter. There’s more about how I got into cooking and food on my About Me page, but today, I’m here to share the memories attached to my favorite foods! Beef Chow Fun + Char Siu Fan Shanghainese Trio Gon chow ngau huo, or beef chow fun, is a popular Cantonese dish that’s pretty much just fresh rice noodles, which are sticky if not constantly tossed in the wok, soy sauce, thin steak, mung bean sprouts, scallions, but packs a punch of flavor in every bite. I’ve been eating this dish for as long as I can remember, yet I was not always a fan of it. My dad absolutely loves this dish, though, so it’s grown on me a ton. It tastes great with other roast meats, as seen in the char siu above too. Char siu is Cantonese honey-barbecued pork, which tastes great with plain rice or chopped in a fried rice. There are plenty of roast shops in Chinatown to buy both char siu + gon chow ngau huo, so I’ll try to compile a list of shops for the future. It’s such a cheap meal, and there’s no better food deals than Chinatowns! The “Shanghainese Trio”, the nickname I gave these three dishes, consists of chong you bing, or scallion pancakes, fried dumplings, and sheng jian bao, or pan-fried baos. I love these three dishes from Shanghai 21 (formerly Shanghai Asian Manor). I haven’t been there since it was known as the former, but their scallion pancakes are extremely crunchy and fluffy, and these baos and dumplings are stuffed with so much flavor. I can’t vouch for how these taste now, but regardless of if these dishes are made by my Grandma or at Shanghai 21, I will always keep these dishes on my favorites list. GOAM - Green Onions and Mayo I praised the glorious okonomiyaki on my Los Angeles post, so explore it over there! Mango Cheese Tea Gai Dan Jai Cheese tea, the drink phenomenon from China, is as interesting as it sounds. I hadn’t been to China since I was around 8 years old, but on my first trip to China in 2017, Antonia and I became obsessed after our first introduction to it. The “cheese” is a sweet cream cheese foam sprinkled with salt, which adds a perfect savory note to the drink. I urge you to try this should the opportunity arise, and not to let the daunting title scare you away! HeyCha, originally from Guangdong and pictured above, is the pioneer of cheese tea in Asia, and people wait hours upon hours to grab a cup of it. It is very, very worth it. Gai dan jai, or egg waffles, are an absolute contender for favorite dessert (excluding boba or cheese tea). The egg whites folded into the batter differentiate gai dan jai from standard Belgian waffles, along with a little custard powder and tapioca starch that create a slight chewiness. I had my first traditional HK egg waffle from Lee Keung Kee North Point Egg Waffles in Tsim Sha Tsui, Hong Kong, and it definitely met my expectations. Wowfulls has changed the egg waffle game in NYC, as they make egg waffle sundaes and have created pizza egg waffles in the past, so I encourage you to catch them at any upcoming popups! Cheese Tteokbokki I don’t have a specific memory attached to these rice cakes, other than that the first time I had them, I devoured them. Korean rice cakes smothered in gochujang (chili paste) sauce and covered in gooey mozzarella cheese. Enough said ~ Barbecue Burnt Ends + More Ribeye Steak + Caesar Salad These ribs, burnt ends, and brisket are from Mighty Quinn’s. I just love burnt ends, there’s not really another explanation 😂 The steak and salad are from Arthur’s Steakhouse in Hoboken. Before my dad made the full time switch to working from home (like over 14 years ago), he used to eat here for coworker meals and bring leftovers home for me and my sister. We became obsessed with their garlic bread, and eventually, got to eat in the restaurant. Arthur’s makes an incredible chicken caesar salad and “Our Steak”, a 24oz marbled Rib Eye, served with Arthur’s Potatoes. This is another restaurant I remember eating at for years, so I can’t wait to return one day and bite into their sometimes burnt, nonetheless tasty, potatoes. B.E.C. Bagel This beautiful bacon, egg, and cheese bagel from Celebrity Bagels, a Tenafly staple, is one heck of special Sunday morning treat. I get mine with salt, pepper, and ketchup on an everything bagel, since I enjoy the variety of seasonings on top. Tofu Pudding I really got into dou fu hua, or tofu pudding, this year, when my dad and I went to Chinatown in February. This was not my first time trying it, but I was not as obsessed with it until then. Its primary ingredient is tofu, and although it may just seem like a bowl of soft tofu, it is really an extraordinary canvas for any condiments you like. The flavor itself is very neutral, meaning you can go either sweet or savory with it. Sweet dou fu hua is topped with a brown sugar syrup, which is how I typically eat it and is as seen above. Savory dou fu hua is topped with soy sauce, vinegar, chili oil, and scallions. I don’t think I’ve ever had the savory one, but it’s certainly one I’d love to try. My family likes it too, but I could eat the whole quart this pudding comes in! Claypot Rice Cheese-Baked Rice I figured I could finish this list off by tying it back to my roots. Bao zai fan, or claypot rice, and cheese-baked rice are two popular Hong Kong café items. Claypot rice is typically topped with lap cheong, or Chinese sausage, and choi sum, or Chinese broccoli, but this one is topped with lamb chops and fried egg. We have a claypot at home, and it really makes meals special, since it sustains high temperatures. The pot browns the cooked rice, creating a nutty, toasty flavor unable to be replicated by just putting it in the oven. The cheese-baked rice sounds a little odd, but everything about it works. It’s almost like a cheese pizza with a rice base. I’ve noticed a lot of Asian tomato sauces are a lot sweeter than their Italian counterparts, and the sauce on this one has a light bell pepper note as well. I’m not a fan of peppers at all, but I will eat them if they’re in this rice. The cheese is almost a nod to Hong Kong’s “East Meets West” background, when HK was a Crown Colony of the British empire. My parents lived in Guangzhou, and much of my maternal extended family lives in Hong Kong today, so eating these dishes is a taste of my Hong Kong memories. Both pictures were taken at XO Kitchen Restaurant食坊, my family’s go-to in Manhattan Chinatown pre-pandemic. They make dumplings wrapped in an ultra-thin, eggy wrapper that are a must-try here, too. This is by no means an exclusive list - I have far too many foods I would consider a 20 on a 1 to 10 scale of strongly dislike to absolutely devour, so I’ll likely be updating the list in the future. I hope you enjoyed reading some of the reasons why I appreciate (and dream of) these foods a little extra.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/stories/favoritefoods/katsu.JPG" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/stories/favoritefoods/katsu.JPG" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Menya Sandaime</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jerseyeats/menya" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Menya Sandaime" /><published>2020-10-07T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2020-10-07T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jerseyeats/menya</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jerseyeats/menya">&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/jerseyeats/menyasandaime/menya.JPG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before I start, I have to say that I would eat the noodles at Menya Sandaime every day, if I could.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to their website, they continue to use a traditional Japanese recipe that has been passed through three generations. Their Tokyo-style broth takes over 12 hours to prepare, and they make their noodles in-house. Seriously, you can even see the room where they make their noodles in their 1st Fort Lee location! With their quality and time-intensive ingredients, this restaurant is dangerously tempting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/jerseyeats/menyasandaime/menyaramen.jpg&quot; height=&quot;200px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;2 Tonkotsu Ramens&lt;/div&gt;  
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The pork broth here is so fatty and indulgent, and pairs so well with their housemade noodles. I’ve tried their &lt;strong&gt;tonkotsu&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;black ramen&lt;/strong&gt; dishes, which both have a tonkotsu broth base. The difference between these two dishes is that the black ramen has the addition of a smoky seafood flavor. For those who might be scared off by this, it’s really not that fishy, and I actually like this addition a lot. My favorite between these two is the &lt;strong&gt;original tonkotsu&lt;/strong&gt;, but you can’t go wrong with either. If you like some spice, their karakuchi ramen has the spicy version of the tonkotsu ramen. These are the three ramen options that are topped with bean sprouts, scallions, spinach, marinated egg, &amp;amp; grilled pork belly. The tonkotsu ramen is $9.50 at the Fort Lee locations, while the black and karakuchi ramen are $10.50.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now I’d like to talk about my favorite dish here - the &lt;strong&gt;tsukemen&lt;/strong&gt; ($11). Tsukemen is a ramen variation* where the noodles are plated separately from the broth. These dipping noodles are slowly gaining popularity in the U.S., but you might be wondering - it sounds just like deconstructed ramen, so why am I paying $1.50 more to get ramen plated separately?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;-tsukemen-is-very-different-from-ramen-and-should-be-eaten-by-dipping-a-small-portion-of-noodles-into-the-broth-the-noodles-should-not-be-poured-directly-into-the-broth&quot;&gt;* &lt;em&gt;Tsukemen is very different from ramen and should be eaten by dipping a small portion of noodles into the broth. The noodles should not be poured directly into the broth!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/jerseyeats/menyasandaime/menya2.JPG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What separates tsukemen from traditional ramen are 1. their noodles and 2. the broth. I prefer the tsukemen noodles that are comparably thicker and chewier than the tonkotsu ramen noodles. The tsukemen broth is slightly thicker than the tonkotsu broth, which makes sense for the noodles to absorb more broth. The tsukemen broth is a very similar broth base to the black ramen, which comes with a smoky seafood flavor as well. However, the tsukemen broth comes with small chunks of onions and pork, which pairs really well with the noodles. The tsukemen noodles are topped with bean sprouts, scallions, spinach, marinated egg, &amp;amp; grilled pork belly (it comes with one extra piece than the ramen😊).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;tsukemen-is-perfect-for-the-summer-too-as-the-noodles-arent-soaking-in-a-hot-broth&quot;&gt;Tsukemen is perfect for the summer too, as the noodles aren’t soaking in a hot broth.&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Their pork is unbelievably tasty - it’s perfectly fatty and slightly charred. Pork belly is one of the integral components of a ramen dish, and I’d say that you can usually judge how good a ramen place is by their pork. If you don’t like red meat, they also offer a shrimp option to substitute the pork, which my dad once ordered in addition to to the pork belly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/jerseyeats/menyasandaime/tonkotsumenyashirmp.jpg&quot; height=&quot;200px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;Tonkotsu Ramens - (Top) Shrimp + Pork Belly&lt;/div&gt;  
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Menya also offers amazing &lt;strong&gt;gyoza&lt;/strong&gt; ($5.60), or Japanese pan-fried dumplings, which a framed newspaper on their wall claims is the best. Dumplings are different EVERYWHERE you get them, and Menya’s gyoza certainly do not disappoint! As you can see, they have a thin crispy sheet that connects all these dumplings together, which is probably created by pouring a small amount of water + starch into the pan; this allows for an added crisp that elevates the already existing flavor of the meat filling. I’d say these are a must-have side to your noodles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/jerseyeats/menyasandaime/menyagyoza.jpg&quot; height=&quot;200px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Menya opened a second Fort Lee location off Bergen Boulevard that offers specialty items not sold at their original location, such as chicken kara-age, pork buns, chicken teriyaki &amp;amp; grilled pork belly dons (rice bowls), as well as an extended list of noodle add-ons. I’ve only tried the &lt;strong&gt;pork buns&lt;/strong&gt; (1/$3, 2/$5), which I honestly didn’t have high expectations for. Not because I doubted how good the pork would be, but because I didn’t know how worth it the buns would be, since they use the same pork belly in the ramen. However, I was very pleasantly surprised by these buns - they blew my expectations out of the water! Somehow, the pork reimagined in the bao bun was a totally different, yet still as indulgent, experience than the ramen dishes. The buns are slathered in spicy mayo and topped with scallions, which were a refreshing complement to the charred pork belly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/jerseyeats/menyasandaime/menyabuns.jpg&quot; height=&quot;200px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m not too adventurous when I come here, as I usually get the same dishes every time, but I have complete confidence that all their dishes are just as amazing as the ones I routinely eat. Ramen can cost $20+ in Manhattan, and Menya’s pricing is unbeatable. If I go to the city with my dad, we typically stop by Menya on our way home, instead of eating overpriced and under-delivering noodles. These warming and filling noodles are the greatest meal on a snowy winter night, but somehow also on a warm summer day. I cannot stress how extraordinary these noodles are!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/jerseyeats/menyasandaime/menya3.jpg&quot; height=&quot;200px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt; 
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/jerseyeats/menyasandaime/takeoutmenya.JPG&quot; height=&quot;200px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="jerseyeats" /><summary type="html">Before I start, I have to say that I would eat the noodles at Menya Sandaime every day, if I could. According to their website, they continue to use a traditional Japanese recipe that has been passed through three generations. Their Tokyo-style broth takes over 12 hours to prepare, and they make their noodles in-house. Seriously, you can even see the room where they make their noodles in their 1st Fort Lee location! With their quality and time-intensive ingredients, this restaurant is dangerously tempting. 2 Tonkotsu Ramens The pork broth here is so fatty and indulgent, and pairs so well with their housemade noodles. I’ve tried their tonkotsu and black ramen dishes, which both have a tonkotsu broth base. The difference between these two dishes is that the black ramen has the addition of a smoky seafood flavor. For those who might be scared off by this, it’s really not that fishy, and I actually like this addition a lot. My favorite between these two is the original tonkotsu, but you can’t go wrong with either. If you like some spice, their karakuchi ramen has the spicy version of the tonkotsu ramen. These are the three ramen options that are topped with bean sprouts, scallions, spinach, marinated egg, &amp;amp; grilled pork belly. The tonkotsu ramen is $9.50 at the Fort Lee locations, while the black and karakuchi ramen are $10.50. Now I’d like to talk about my favorite dish here - the tsukemen ($11). Tsukemen is a ramen variation* where the noodles are plated separately from the broth. These dipping noodles are slowly gaining popularity in the U.S., but you might be wondering - it sounds just like deconstructed ramen, so why am I paying $1.50 more to get ramen plated separately? * Tsukemen is very different from ramen and should be eaten by dipping a small portion of noodles into the broth. The noodles should not be poured directly into the broth! What separates tsukemen from traditional ramen are 1. their noodles and 2. the broth. I prefer the tsukemen noodles that are comparably thicker and chewier than the tonkotsu ramen noodles. The tsukemen broth is slightly thicker than the tonkotsu broth, which makes sense for the noodles to absorb more broth. The tsukemen broth is a very similar broth base to the black ramen, which comes with a smoky seafood flavor as well. However, the tsukemen broth comes with small chunks of onions and pork, which pairs really well with the noodles. The tsukemen noodles are topped with bean sprouts, scallions, spinach, marinated egg, &amp;amp; grilled pork belly (it comes with one extra piece than the ramen😊). Tsukemen is perfect for the summer too, as the noodles aren’t soaking in a hot broth. Their pork is unbelievably tasty - it’s perfectly fatty and slightly charred. Pork belly is one of the integral components of a ramen dish, and I’d say that you can usually judge how good a ramen place is by their pork. If you don’t like red meat, they also offer a shrimp option to substitute the pork, which my dad once ordered in addition to to the pork belly. Tonkotsu Ramens - (Top) Shrimp + Pork Belly Menya also offers amazing gyoza ($5.60), or Japanese pan-fried dumplings, which a framed newspaper on their wall claims is the best. Dumplings are different EVERYWHERE you get them, and Menya’s gyoza certainly do not disappoint! As you can see, they have a thin crispy sheet that connects all these dumplings together, which is probably created by pouring a small amount of water + starch into the pan; this allows for an added crisp that elevates the already existing flavor of the meat filling. I’d say these are a must-have side to your noodles. Menya opened a second Fort Lee location off Bergen Boulevard that offers specialty items not sold at their original location, such as chicken kara-age, pork buns, chicken teriyaki &amp;amp; grilled pork belly dons (rice bowls), as well as an extended list of noodle add-ons. I’ve only tried the pork buns (1/$3, 2/$5), which I honestly didn’t have high expectations for. Not because I doubted how good the pork would be, but because I didn’t know how worth it the buns would be, since they use the same pork belly in the ramen. However, I was very pleasantly surprised by these buns - they blew my expectations out of the water! Somehow, the pork reimagined in the bao bun was a totally different, yet still as indulgent, experience than the ramen dishes. The buns are slathered in spicy mayo and topped with scallions, which were a refreshing complement to the charred pork belly. I’m not too adventurous when I come here, as I usually get the same dishes every time, but I have complete confidence that all their dishes are just as amazing as the ones I routinely eat. Ramen can cost $20+ in Manhattan, and Menya’s pricing is unbeatable. If I go to the city with my dad, we typically stop by Menya on our way home, instead of eating overpriced and under-delivering noodles. These warming and filling noodles are the greatest meal on a snowy winter night, but somehow also on a warm summer day. I cannot stress how extraordinary these noodles are!!</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/jerseyeats/menyasandaime/menya.JPG" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/jerseyeats/menyasandaime/menya.JPG" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Cheese (Bread) Please!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/recipes/cheesebread" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Cheese (Bread) Please!" /><published>2020-09-23T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2020-09-23T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/recipes/cheesebread</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/recipes/cheesebread">&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/recipes/cheesebread/cheesebread3.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;apologies-for-all-the-cringey-cheese-puns-on-the-way&quot;&gt;Apologies for all the cringey cheese puns on the way…&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Inspired by the Brazilian cheese bread, &lt;strong&gt;pão de queijo&lt;/strong&gt;, this naturally gluten-free tapioca cheese bread is not what you might first think of when you hear “bread”, but its airiness, chewiness, and exterior crunchiness will be sure to win over even the most passionate bread purists. I want to preface this by saying this cheese bread is by no means authentic or traditional, but it still contains the two basic ingredients of cheese and tapioca flour.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;brazilian-cheese-bread-history-according-to-eater-the-first-instance-of-pão-de-queijo-was-likely-produced-with-the-tapioca-starch-17th-century-slave-communities-collected-during-the-processing-of-cassava-plants-to-supplement-their-meager-daily-rations-but-cheese-wasnt-incorporated-until-the-beginning-of-the-20th-century&quot;&gt;Brazilian Cheese Bread History: According to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eater.com/2016/8/8/12402578/pao-de-queijo-brazilian-cheese-bread-gluten-free&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Eater&lt;/a&gt;, the first instance of pão de queijo was likely produced with the tapioca starch 17th-century slave communities collected “during the processing of cassava plants to supplement their meager daily rations”, but cheese wasn’t incorporated until the beginning of the 20th century.&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This recipe is as simple as it gets for bread. As long as you have tapioca flour, the other ingredients are very likely already in your pantry/fridge. I adapted this recipe from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.allrecipes.com/recipe/98554/brazilian-cheese-bread-pao-de-queijo/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Allrecipes.com&lt;/a&gt;, whose second step requires a saucepan to boil the liquid ingredients together, but a microwave to melt the butter did the trick for me. After that, it’s just a progression of dumping ingredients into a bowl and pouring the batter into a muffin tin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I recommend using a Pyrex liquid measuring cup to do all your mixing in, as it makes pouring into a muffin tin even easier, but a regular mixing bowl and spoon will do the job as well. The recipe I adapted mine from implies that the mixture should be solid enough to drop small balls of it onto a sheet pan, but mine comes out as a thicker-than-cake batter. Regardless, I’ve never had a time where I didn’t absolutely devour these bread bites, so I’m doing something right!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just a quick 18 minutes in the oven later, and you’ll find a toasted cheese aroma circulating through your kitchen. The golden-brown tops will let you know that they’re ready to go - the inside may be &lt;em&gt;slightly&lt;/em&gt; underbaked, but there should be no liquid left whatsoever. This cheese bread is incredibly addictive - I make them to “share” with my dad, but once I start, I can’t hold myself back from eating more, which my grandma gets very upset about when I need to eat dinner in the next 20 minutes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They’ve been perfectly shaped by the muffin mold the past two times I’ve made these, but even if they come out with a hole on the bottom, I promise they’re still DELICIOUS! I used too much butter the first couple times, which is partly why the ones below are more golden (no complaints there). You can see the difference in the photos below. Plus, you can use the hole as a vehicle for any condiments you might want to add.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/recipes/cheesebread/cheesebread4.JPG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;1st Time Cheese Breads (still really &lt;em&gt;goud-a&lt;/em&gt;)&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/recipes/cheesebread/cheesebread1.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;After some ~character development~&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now let’s get on with the recipe and &lt;em&gt;cheese&lt;/em&gt; the day!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;tapioca-cheese-bread&quot;&gt;Tapioca Cheese Bread&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&quot;yields-12-breads-in-a-mini-muffin-tin&quot;&gt;Yields 12 breads in a mini muffin tin&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ingredients&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1 cup tapioca flour&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;2 tablespoons warm melted butter&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;⅓ cup milk or soy milk&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;⅓ cup grated Parmesan or gouda cheese (more or less, based on your preferred cheesiness)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1 beaten egg&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;½ teaspoon salt&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;⅛ teaspoon of granulated garlic (optional)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Preheat your oven to 375°F, or 190°C.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Combine milk, warm melted butter, beaten egg, and salt.
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Be sure to thoroughly mix, as you do not want the egg to cook at all.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Stir in the tapioca flour in two parts and mix until smooth.
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Luckily, you don’t have to worry about overmixing as you would with regular bread, since there’s no gluten in this recipe!&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Combining tapioca flour and liquids can create a slimy texture, so you may struggle to mix at first.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Add the cheese of your choice and stir well.
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;I’ve only tried Parmesan and gouda, but any lower-moisture cheeses would definitely work.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fill each mold basically full, but not to the point where any batter spreads out of the individual cup.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bake until the tops are lightly golden brown for 15-20 minutes. Aren’t they &lt;em&gt;cheesy&lt;/em&gt; on the eyes?
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Because of the butter and oils from the cheese, the breads should come right out of a non-stick muffin tray.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Serve with honey, jam, or marinara sauce.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/recipes/cheesebread/cheesebread2.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="recipes" /><summary type="html">Apologies for all the cringey cheese puns on the way… Inspired by the Brazilian cheese bread, pão de queijo, this naturally gluten-free tapioca cheese bread is not what you might first think of when you hear “bread”, but its airiness, chewiness, and exterior crunchiness will be sure to win over even the most passionate bread purists. I want to preface this by saying this cheese bread is by no means authentic or traditional, but it still contains the two basic ingredients of cheese and tapioca flour. Brazilian Cheese Bread History: According to Eater, the first instance of pão de queijo was likely produced with the tapioca starch 17th-century slave communities collected “during the processing of cassava plants to supplement their meager daily rations”, but cheese wasn’t incorporated until the beginning of the 20th century. This recipe is as simple as it gets for bread. As long as you have tapioca flour, the other ingredients are very likely already in your pantry/fridge. I adapted this recipe from Allrecipes.com, whose second step requires a saucepan to boil the liquid ingredients together, but a microwave to melt the butter did the trick for me. After that, it’s just a progression of dumping ingredients into a bowl and pouring the batter into a muffin tin. I recommend using a Pyrex liquid measuring cup to do all your mixing in, as it makes pouring into a muffin tin even easier, but a regular mixing bowl and spoon will do the job as well. The recipe I adapted mine from implies that the mixture should be solid enough to drop small balls of it onto a sheet pan, but mine comes out as a thicker-than-cake batter. Regardless, I’ve never had a time where I didn’t absolutely devour these bread bites, so I’m doing something right! Just a quick 18 minutes in the oven later, and you’ll find a toasted cheese aroma circulating through your kitchen. The golden-brown tops will let you know that they’re ready to go - the inside may be slightly underbaked, but there should be no liquid left whatsoever. This cheese bread is incredibly addictive - I make them to “share” with my dad, but once I start, I can’t hold myself back from eating more, which my grandma gets very upset about when I need to eat dinner in the next 20 minutes. They’ve been perfectly shaped by the muffin mold the past two times I’ve made these, but even if they come out with a hole on the bottom, I promise they’re still DELICIOUS! I used too much butter the first couple times, which is partly why the ones below are more golden (no complaints there). You can see the difference in the photos below. Plus, you can use the hole as a vehicle for any condiments you might want to add. 1st Time Cheese Breads (still really goud-a) After some ~character development~ Now let’s get on with the recipe and cheese the day! Tapioca Cheese Bread Yields 12 breads in a mini muffin tin Ingredients 1 cup tapioca flour 2 tablespoons warm melted butter ⅓ cup milk or soy milk ⅓ cup grated Parmesan or gouda cheese (more or less, based on your preferred cheesiness) 1 beaten egg ½ teaspoon salt ⅛ teaspoon of granulated garlic (optional) Directions Preheat your oven to 375°F, or 190°C. Combine milk, warm melted butter, beaten egg, and salt. Be sure to thoroughly mix, as you do not want the egg to cook at all. Stir in the tapioca flour in two parts and mix until smooth. Luckily, you don’t have to worry about overmixing as you would with regular bread, since there’s no gluten in this recipe! Combining tapioca flour and liquids can create a slimy texture, so you may struggle to mix at first. Add the cheese of your choice and stir well. I’ve only tried Parmesan and gouda, but any lower-moisture cheeses would definitely work. Fill each mold basically full, but not to the point where any batter spreads out of the individual cup. Bake until the tops are lightly golden brown for 15-20 minutes. Aren’t they cheesy on the eyes? Because of the butter and oils from the cheese, the breads should come right out of a non-stick muffin tray. Serve with honey, jam, or marinara sauce.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/recipes/cheesebread/cheesebread3.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/recipes/cheesebread/cheesebread3.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">With All My Tart 💖</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/nyceats/pinklady" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="With All My Tart 💖" /><published>2020-09-16T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2020-09-16T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/nyceats/pinklady</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/nyceats/pinklady">&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/nyceats/pinklady/pinklady1.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Inspired by the Hokkaido Cheese in Japan, &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/pinkladycheesetart/?hl=en&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Pinklady Cheese Tart&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; is a new Chinatown small business selling creamy cheese tarts located at 11 Mott Street.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You might be unfamiliar with the Hokkaido cheese tarts that Pinklady is inspired by. Hokkaido, the northernmost Japanese island, has a massive countryside that can support a successful dairy industry. According to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.japan-guide.com/e/e5312.html&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;japan-guide.com&lt;/a&gt;, the island produce’s half of Japan’s milk, and their dairy products are highly regarded across the country. The tarts supposedly originated in a bakery in Hokkaido’s capital of Sapporo, obviously using those quality dairy products. Hokkaido is one of my top bucket-list destinations, not only for the food, but for the nature (flowers, volcanoes, etc.), hot springs, skiing, and so much more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These cheese tarts should not be confused with the popular Hong Kong egg tarts or Portuguese/Macanese pastéis de nata, as those tarts are filled with a silky sweet custard, while cheese tarts are made with oozy cheese mousse. The crusts on the other two are typically puff pastry-like, while cheese tart shells are more comparable to a cookie.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;fun-fact-these-tarts-typically-contain-three-types-of-cheese-cream-cheese-mascarpone-cheese-and-the-most-surprising-one-parmesan-cheese-the-parmesan-does-not-make-these-tarts-savory---i-think-that-a-small-amount-adds-slight-saltiness-and-nuttiness-that-balances-the-sweetness-of-this-dessert&quot;&gt;Fun fact: these tarts typically contain THREE types of cheese: cream cheese, mascarpone cheese, and the most surprising one, parmesan cheese! The parmesan does NOT make these tarts savory - I think that a small amount adds slight saltiness and nuttiness that balances the sweetness of this dessert.&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My first experience with a cheese tart was in Taiwan, where I tried a boba-filled one - if you know me, you know I love boba on anything and everything. Although the boba added a chewy texture, it was the cheese itself that really stood out. Since then, I’ve been on the look out for a cheese tart near me. When I saw &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/p/CDmiUUdHTPM/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;this post&lt;/a&gt; by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/jeaniuseats/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;@jeaniuseats&lt;/a&gt;, I was ECSTATIC!! The location of Pinklady was perfect, as my dad and I stop by Mott Street almost monthly, so I made it a target stop on our next trip.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pinklady may not be the first cheese tart in Manhattan, but they are one of the only NYC businesses really specializing in cheese tarts. They only sell two products, one being their array of tarts, and the other being their housemade rice yogurt drinks, which I’ve heard lovely things about too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The store’s giant yellow sign sticks out like a sore thumb on Chinatown’s “unofficial Main Street” that’s decorated with the lucky Chinese color of red all over. There’s no seating inside, which I wouldn’t expect to change after the pandemic, given the store’s small space. There’s a few back-of-the-house staff, but it’s been one person taking my order and packing it up the two times I’ve been there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me start off by saying the staff there are so friendly - they really care about making sure you know all the temperatures you can enjoy your tarts at (more on that later) and just making you feel like a human, which is not always an easy find at bakeries and restaurants.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Upon entrance, you’ll see that there are “sneeze guard” dividers to protect the tarts from any customers (who must wear a mask inside too), and the tarts are lined up on Silpats and plastic trays. They currently offer five flavors of &lt;strong&gt;original cheese&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;matcha&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;ube&lt;/strong&gt; (purple yam), &lt;strong&gt;chocolate&lt;/strong&gt;, and &lt;strong&gt;strawberry-filled chocolate&lt;/strong&gt;. I’ve tried all but the chocolate one, since I’m not the &lt;em&gt;biggest&lt;/em&gt; fan of chocolate (I’m prepared to get some hate mail…). My favorite is the matcha, because the matcha accompanies the cheese perfectly, but you really can’t go wrong with any of them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/nyceats/pinklady/pinkladycenter.JPG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;Inside of the Matcha Cheese&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, about those temperatures I was talking about, there are four ways to enjoy these tarts. It’s almost like four different dessert types that range from firm + cheesecake-like to molten lava tarts. Putting the tart in the fridge will make the flowy inside firm up like a cheesecake, while putting it in the oven / air-fryer will make the inside hot and ooze of lava cheese. The other two ways are the most similar, which are just warming the tarts up in the microwave and eating it plain-Jane room temperature. My personal favorite is room-temperature, because I still get a slightly flowy inside while the tart retains a cheesecake-esque texture on the outer parts of the filling, but even just the versatility of how this dessert can be consumed is so unique.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While I do love myself a flaky HK egg tart crust, Pinklady double bakes their tart shells, making for a crispier, slightly toasted tartlet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was beyond satisfied with my stop at Pinklady. My dad and I fought over the last cheese tart, because they’re just that good (we ended up splitting it). Opening at the peak of the pandemic in April is no easy feat, and although there are many old staples in Chinatown that deserve an equal amount of appreciation, Pinklady is a great addition to an already fantastic, robust neighborhood dessert scene. Be sure to pay a visit at your next stop in Chinatown!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/nyceats/pinklady/pinklady3.JPG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;Left to Right: Original, Matcha, Chocolate Strawberry&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="nyceats" /><summary type="html">Inspired by the Hokkaido Cheese in Japan, Pinklady Cheese Tart is a new Chinatown small business selling creamy cheese tarts located at 11 Mott Street. You might be unfamiliar with the Hokkaido cheese tarts that Pinklady is inspired by. Hokkaido, the northernmost Japanese island, has a massive countryside that can support a successful dairy industry. According to japan-guide.com, the island produce’s half of Japan’s milk, and their dairy products are highly regarded across the country. The tarts supposedly originated in a bakery in Hokkaido’s capital of Sapporo, obviously using those quality dairy products. Hokkaido is one of my top bucket-list destinations, not only for the food, but for the nature (flowers, volcanoes, etc.), hot springs, skiing, and so much more. These cheese tarts should not be confused with the popular Hong Kong egg tarts or Portuguese/Macanese pastéis de nata, as those tarts are filled with a silky sweet custard, while cheese tarts are made with oozy cheese mousse. The crusts on the other two are typically puff pastry-like, while cheese tart shells are more comparable to a cookie. Fun fact: these tarts typically contain THREE types of cheese: cream cheese, mascarpone cheese, and the most surprising one, parmesan cheese! The parmesan does NOT make these tarts savory - I think that a small amount adds slight saltiness and nuttiness that balances the sweetness of this dessert. My first experience with a cheese tart was in Taiwan, where I tried a boba-filled one - if you know me, you know I love boba on anything and everything. Although the boba added a chewy texture, it was the cheese itself that really stood out. Since then, I’ve been on the look out for a cheese tart near me. When I saw this post by @jeaniuseats, I was ECSTATIC!! The location of Pinklady was perfect, as my dad and I stop by Mott Street almost monthly, so I made it a target stop on our next trip. Pinklady may not be the first cheese tart in Manhattan, but they are one of the only NYC businesses really specializing in cheese tarts. They only sell two products, one being their array of tarts, and the other being their housemade rice yogurt drinks, which I’ve heard lovely things about too. The store’s giant yellow sign sticks out like a sore thumb on Chinatown’s “unofficial Main Street” that’s decorated with the lucky Chinese color of red all over. There’s no seating inside, which I wouldn’t expect to change after the pandemic, given the store’s small space. There’s a few back-of-the-house staff, but it’s been one person taking my order and packing it up the two times I’ve been there. Let me start off by saying the staff there are so friendly - they really care about making sure you know all the temperatures you can enjoy your tarts at (more on that later) and just making you feel like a human, which is not always an easy find at bakeries and restaurants. Upon entrance, you’ll see that there are “sneeze guard” dividers to protect the tarts from any customers (who must wear a mask inside too), and the tarts are lined up on Silpats and plastic trays. They currently offer five flavors of original cheese, matcha, ube (purple yam), chocolate, and strawberry-filled chocolate. I’ve tried all but the chocolate one, since I’m not the biggest fan of chocolate (I’m prepared to get some hate mail…). My favorite is the matcha, because the matcha accompanies the cheese perfectly, but you really can’t go wrong with any of them. Inside of the Matcha Cheese Now, about those temperatures I was talking about, there are four ways to enjoy these tarts. It’s almost like four different dessert types that range from firm + cheesecake-like to molten lava tarts. Putting the tart in the fridge will make the flowy inside firm up like a cheesecake, while putting it in the oven / air-fryer will make the inside hot and ooze of lava cheese. The other two ways are the most similar, which are just warming the tarts up in the microwave and eating it plain-Jane room temperature. My personal favorite is room-temperature, because I still get a slightly flowy inside while the tart retains a cheesecake-esque texture on the outer parts of the filling, but even just the versatility of how this dessert can be consumed is so unique. While I do love myself a flaky HK egg tart crust, Pinklady double bakes their tart shells, making for a crispier, slightly toasted tartlet. I was beyond satisfied with my stop at Pinklady. My dad and I fought over the last cheese tart, because they’re just that good (we ended up splitting it). Opening at the peak of the pandemic in April is no easy feat, and although there are many old staples in Chinatown that deserve an equal amount of appreciation, Pinklady is a great addition to an already fantastic, robust neighborhood dessert scene. Be sure to pay a visit at your next stop in Chinatown! Left to Right: Original, Matcha, Chocolate Strawberry</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/nyceats/pinklady/pinklady1.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/nyceats/pinklady/pinklady1.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry></feed>