<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-09-23T19:45:30-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">CarissaEats</title><entry><title type="html">Cheese (Bread) Please!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/recipes/2020/09/23/cheesebread.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Cheese (Bread) Please!" /><published>2020-09-23T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2020-09-23T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/recipes/2020/09/23/cheesebread</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/recipes/2020/09/23/cheesebread.html">&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/recipes/cheesebread/cheesebread3.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;singleimage&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;apologies-for-all-the-cringey-cheese-puns-on-the-way&quot;&gt;Apologies for all the cringey cheese puns on the way…&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Inspired by the Brazilian cheese bread, &lt;strong&gt;pão de queijo&lt;/strong&gt;, this naturally gluten-free tapioca cheese bread is not what you might first think of when you hear “bread”, but its airiness, chewiness, and exterior crunchiness will be sure to win over even the most passionate bread purists. I want to preface this by saying this cheese bread is by no means authentic or traditional, but it still contains the two basic ingredients of cheese and tapioca flour.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;brazilian-cheese-bread-history-according-to-eater-the-first-instance-of-pão-de-queijo-was-likely-produced-with-the-tapioca-starch-17th-century-slave-communities-collected-during-the-processing-of-cassava-plants-to-supplement-their-meager-daily-rations-but-cheese-wasnt-incorporated-until-the-beginning-of-the-20th-century&quot;&gt;Brazilian Cheese Bread History: According to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eater.com/2016/8/8/12402578/pao-de-queijo-brazilian-cheese-bread-gluten-free&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Eater&lt;/a&gt;, the first instance of pão de queijo was likely produced with the tapioca starch 17th-century slave communities collected “during the processing of cassava plants to supplement their meager daily rations”, but cheese wasn’t incorporated until the beginning of the 20th century.&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This recipe is as simple as it gets for bread. As long as you have tapioca flour, the other ingredients are very likely already in your pantry/fridge. I adapted this recipe from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.allrecipes.com/recipe/98554/brazilian-cheese-bread-pao-de-queijo/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Allrecipes.com&lt;/a&gt;, whose second step requires a saucepan to boil the liquid ingredients together, but a microwave to melt the butter did the trick for me. After that, it’s just a progression of dumping ingredients into a bowl and pouring the batter into a muffin tin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I recommend using a Pyrex liquid measuring cup to do all your mixing in, as it makes pouring into a muffin tin even easier, but a regular mixing bowl and spoon will do the job as well. The recipe I adapted mine from implies that the mixture should be solid enough to drop small balls of it onto a sheet pan, but mine comes out as a thicker-than-cake batter. Regardless, I’ve never had a time where I didn’t absolutely devour these bread bites, so I’m doing something right!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just a quick 18 minutes in the oven later, and you’ll find a toasted cheese aroma circulating through your kitchen. The golden-brown tops will let you know that they’re ready to go - the inside may be &lt;em&gt;slightly&lt;/em&gt; underbaked, but there should be no liquid left whatsoever. This cheese bread is incredibly addictive - I make them to “share” with my dad, but once I start, I can’t hold myself back from eating more, which my grandma gets very upset about when I need to eat dinner in the next 20 minutes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They’ve been perfectly shaped by the muffin mold the past two times I’ve made these, but even if they come out with a hole on the bottom, I promise they’re still DELICIOUS! I used too much butter the first couple times, which is partly why the ones below are more golden (no complaints there). You can see the difference in the photos below. Plus, you can use the hole as a vehicle for any condiments you might want to add.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table class=&quot;home&quot;&gt;
    &lt;td class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/recipes/cheesebread/cheesebread4.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;singleimage&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;overlayblogphotos&quot;&gt;1st Time Cheese Breads (still really &lt;em&gt;goud-a&lt;/em&gt;)&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;td class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/recipes/cheesebread/cheesebread1.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;singleimage&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;overlayblogphotos&quot;&gt;After they went through some ~character development~&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/td&gt;            
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now let’s get on with the recipe and &lt;em&gt;cheese&lt;/em&gt; the day!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;tapioca-cheese-bread&quot;&gt;Tapioca Cheese Bread&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&quot;yields-12-breads-in-a-mini-muffin-tin&quot;&gt;Yields 12 breads in a mini muffin tin&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ingredients&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1 cup tapioca flour&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;2 tablespoons warm melted butter&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;⅓ cup milk or soy milk&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;⅓ cup grated Parmesan or gouda cheese (more or less, based on your preferred cheesiness)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1 beaten egg&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;½ teaspoon salt&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;⅛ teaspoon of granulated garlic (optional)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Preheat your oven to 375°F, or 190°C.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Combine milk, warm melted butter, beaten egg, and salt.
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Be sure to thoroughly mix, as you do not want the egg to cook at all.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Stir in the tapioca flour in two parts and mix until smooth.
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Luckily, you don’t have to worry about overmixing as you would with regular bread, since there’s no gluten in this recipe!&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Combining tapioca flour and liquids can create a slimy texture, so you may struggle to mix at first.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Add the cheese of your choice and stir well.
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;I’ve only tried Parmesan and gouda, but any lower-moisture cheeses would definitely work.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fill each mold basically full, but not to the point where any batter spreads out of the individual cup.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bake until the tops are lightly golden brown for 15-20 minutes. Aren’t they &lt;em&gt;cheesy&lt;/em&gt; on the eyes?
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Because of the butter and oils from the cheese, the breads should come right out of a non-stick muffin tray.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Serve with honey, jam, or marinara sauce.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/recipes/cheesebread/cheesebread2.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;singleimage&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="recipes" /><summary type="html">Apologies for all the cringey cheese puns on the way… Inspired by the Brazilian cheese bread, pão de queijo, this naturally gluten-free tapioca cheese bread is not what you might first think of when you hear “bread”, but its airiness, chewiness, and exterior crunchiness will be sure to win over even the most passionate bread purists. I want to preface this by saying this cheese bread is by no means authentic or traditional, but it still contains the two basic ingredients of cheese and tapioca flour. Brazilian Cheese Bread History: According to Eater, the first instance of pão de queijo was likely produced with the tapioca starch 17th-century slave communities collected “during the processing of cassava plants to supplement their meager daily rations”, but cheese wasn’t incorporated until the beginning of the 20th century. This recipe is as simple as it gets for bread. As long as you have tapioca flour, the other ingredients are very likely already in your pantry/fridge. I adapted this recipe from Allrecipes.com, whose second step requires a saucepan to boil the liquid ingredients together, but a microwave to melt the butter did the trick for me. After that, it’s just a progression of dumping ingredients into a bowl and pouring the batter into a muffin tin. I recommend using a Pyrex liquid measuring cup to do all your mixing in, as it makes pouring into a muffin tin even easier, but a regular mixing bowl and spoon will do the job as well. The recipe I adapted mine from implies that the mixture should be solid enough to drop small balls of it onto a sheet pan, but mine comes out as a thicker-than-cake batter. Regardless, I’ve never had a time where I didn’t absolutely devour these bread bites, so I’m doing something right! Just a quick 18 minutes in the oven later, and you’ll find a toasted cheese aroma circulating through your kitchen. The golden-brown tops will let you know that they’re ready to go - the inside may be slightly underbaked, but there should be no liquid left whatsoever. This cheese bread is incredibly addictive - I make them to “share” with my dad, but once I start, I can’t hold myself back from eating more, which my grandma gets very upset about when I need to eat dinner in the next 20 minutes. They’ve been perfectly shaped by the muffin mold the past two times I’ve made these, but even if they come out with a hole on the bottom, I promise they’re still DELICIOUS! I used too much butter the first couple times, which is partly why the ones below are more golden (no complaints there). You can see the difference in the photos below. Plus, you can use the hole as a vehicle for any condiments you might want to add. 1st Time Cheese Breads (still really goud-a) After they went through some ~character development~ Now let’s get on with the recipe and cheese the day! Tapioca Cheese Bread Yields 12 breads in a mini muffin tin Ingredients 1 cup tapioca flour 2 tablespoons warm melted butter ⅓ cup milk or soy milk ⅓ cup grated Parmesan or gouda cheese (more or less, based on your preferred cheesiness) 1 beaten egg ½ teaspoon salt ⅛ teaspoon of granulated garlic (optional) Directions Preheat your oven to 375°F, or 190°C. Combine milk, warm melted butter, beaten egg, and salt. Be sure to thoroughly mix, as you do not want the egg to cook at all. Stir in the tapioca flour in two parts and mix until smooth. Luckily, you don’t have to worry about overmixing as you would with regular bread, since there’s no gluten in this recipe! Combining tapioca flour and liquids can create a slimy texture, so you may struggle to mix at first. Add the cheese of your choice and stir well. I’ve only tried Parmesan and gouda, but any lower-moisture cheeses would definitely work. Fill each mold basically full, but not to the point where any batter spreads out of the individual cup. Bake until the tops are lightly golden brown for 15-20 minutes. Aren’t they cheesy on the eyes? Because of the butter and oils from the cheese, the breads should come right out of a non-stick muffin tray. Serve with honey, jam, or marinara sauce.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">With All My Tart 💖</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/nyceats/2020/09/16/pinklady.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="With All My Tart 💖" /><published>2020-09-16T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2020-09-16T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/nyceats/2020/09/16/pinklady</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/nyceats/2020/09/16/pinklady.html">&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/nyceats/pinklady/pinklady1.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;singleimage&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Inspired by the Hokkaido Cheese in Japan, &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/pinkladycheesetart/?hl=en&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Pinklady Cheese Tart&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; is a new Chinatown small business selling creamy cheese tarts located at 11 Mott Street.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You might be unfamiliar with the Hokkaido cheese tarts that Pinklady is inspired by. Hokkaido, the northernmost Japanese island, has a massive countryside that can support a successful dairy industry. According to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.japan-guide.com/e/e5312.html&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;japan-guide.com&lt;/a&gt;, the island produce’s half of Japan’s milk, and their dairy products are highly regarded across the country. The tarts supposedly originated in a bakery in Hokkaido’s capital of Sapporo, obviously using those quality dairy products. Hokkaido is one of my top bucket-list destinations, not only for the food, but for the nature (flowers, volcanoes, etc.), hot springs, skiing, and so much more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These cheese tarts should not be confused with the popular Hong Kong egg tarts or Portuguese/Macanese pastéis de nata, as those tarts are filled with a silky sweet custard, while cheese tarts are made with oozy cheese mousse. The crusts on the other two are typically puff pastry-like, while cheese tart shells are more comparable to a cookie.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;fun-fact-these-tarts-typically-contain-three-types-of-cheese-cream-cheese-mascarpone-cheese-and-the-most-surprising-one-parmesan-cheese-the-parmesan-does-not-make-these-tarts-savory---i-think-that-a-small-amount-adds-slight-saltiness-and-nuttiness-that-balances-the-sweetness-of-this-dessert&quot;&gt;Fun fact: these tarts typically contain THREE types of cheese: cream cheese, mascarpone cheese, and the most surprising one, parmesan cheese! The parmesan does NOT make these tarts savory - I think that a small amount adds slight saltiness and nuttiness that balances the sweetness of this dessert.&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My first experience with a cheese tart was in Taiwan, where I tried a boba-filled one - if you know me, you know I love boba on anything and everything. Although the boba added a chewy texture, it was the cheese itself that really stood out. Since then, I’ve been on the look out for a cheese tart near me. When I saw &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/p/CDmiUUdHTPM/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;this post&lt;/a&gt; by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/jeaniuseats/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;@jeaniuseats&lt;/a&gt;, I was ECSTATIC!! The location of Pinklady was perfect, as my dad and I stop by Mott Street almost monthly, so I made it a target stop on our next trip.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pinklady may not be the first cheese tart in Manhattan, but they are one of the only NYC businesses really specializing in cheese tarts. They only sell two products, one being their array of tarts, and the other being their housemade rice yogurt drinks, which I’ve heard lovely things about too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The store’s giant yellow sign sticks out like a sore thumb on Chinatown’s “unofficial Main Street” that’s decorated with the lucky Chinese color of red all over. There’s no seating inside, which I wouldn’t expect to change after the pandemic, given the store’s small space. There’s a few back-of-the-house staff, but it’s been one person taking my order and packing it up the two times I’ve been there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me start off by saying the staff there are so friendly - they really care about making sure you know all the temperatures you can enjoy your tarts at (more on that later) and just making you feel like a human, which is not always an easy find at bakeries and restaurants.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Upon entrance, you’ll see that there are “sneeze guard” dividers to protect the tarts from any customers (who must wear a mask inside too), and the tarts are lined up on Silpats and plastic trays. They currently offer five flavors of &lt;strong&gt;original cheese&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;matcha&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;ube&lt;/strong&gt; (purple yam), &lt;strong&gt;chocolate&lt;/strong&gt;, and &lt;strong&gt;strawberry-filled chocolate&lt;/strong&gt;. I’ve tried all but the chocolate one, since I’m not the &lt;em&gt;biggest&lt;/em&gt; fan of chocolate (I’m prepared to get some hate mail…). My favorite is the matcha, because the matcha accompanies the cheese perfectly, but you really can’t go wrong with any of them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/nyceats/pinklady/pinkladycenter.JPG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;singleimage&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;Inside of the Matcha Cheese&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, about those temperatures I was talking about, there are four ways to enjoy these tarts. It’s almost like four different dessert types that range from firm + cheesecake-like to molten lava tarts. Putting the tart in the fridge will make the flowy inside firm up like a cheesecake, while putting it in the oven / air-fryer will make the inside hot and ooze of lava cheese. The other two ways are the most similar, which are just warming the tarts up in the microwave and eating it plain-Jane room temperature. My personal favorite is room-temperature, because I still get a slightly flowy inside while the tart retains a cheesecake-esque texture on the outer parts of the filling, but even just the versatility of how this dessert can be consumed is so unique.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While I do love myself a flaky HK egg tart crust, Pinklady double bakes their tart shells, making for a crispier, slightly toasted tartlet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was beyond satisfied with my stop at Pinklady. My dad and I fought over the last cheese tart, because they’re just that good (we ended up splitting it). Opening at the peak of the pandemic in April is no easy feat, and although there are many old staples in Chinatown that deserve an equal amount of appreciation, Pinklady is a great addition to an already fantastic, robust neighborhood dessert scene. Be sure to pay a visit at your next stop in Chinatown!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/nyceats/pinklady/pinklady3.JPG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;singleimage&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;Left to Right: Original, Matcha, Chocolate Strawberry&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="nyceats" /><summary type="html">Inspired by the Hokkaido Cheese in Japan, Pinklady Cheese Tart is a new Chinatown small business selling creamy cheese tarts located at 11 Mott Street. You might be unfamiliar with the Hokkaido cheese tarts that Pinklady is inspired by. Hokkaido, the northernmost Japanese island, has a massive countryside that can support a successful dairy industry. According to japan-guide.com, the island produce’s half of Japan’s milk, and their dairy products are highly regarded across the country. The tarts supposedly originated in a bakery in Hokkaido’s capital of Sapporo, obviously using those quality dairy products. Hokkaido is one of my top bucket-list destinations, not only for the food, but for the nature (flowers, volcanoes, etc.), hot springs, skiing, and so much more. These cheese tarts should not be confused with the popular Hong Kong egg tarts or Portuguese/Macanese pastéis de nata, as those tarts are filled with a silky sweet custard, while cheese tarts are made with oozy cheese mousse. The crusts on the other two are typically puff pastry-like, while cheese tart shells are more comparable to a cookie. Fun fact: these tarts typically contain THREE types of cheese: cream cheese, mascarpone cheese, and the most surprising one, parmesan cheese! The parmesan does NOT make these tarts savory - I think that a small amount adds slight saltiness and nuttiness that balances the sweetness of this dessert. My first experience with a cheese tart was in Taiwan, where I tried a boba-filled one - if you know me, you know I love boba on anything and everything. Although the boba added a chewy texture, it was the cheese itself that really stood out. Since then, I’ve been on the look out for a cheese tart near me. When I saw this post by @jeaniuseats, I was ECSTATIC!! The location of Pinklady was perfect, as my dad and I stop by Mott Street almost monthly, so I made it a target stop on our next trip. Pinklady may not be the first cheese tart in Manhattan, but they are one of the only NYC businesses really specializing in cheese tarts. They only sell two products, one being their array of tarts, and the other being their housemade rice yogurt drinks, which I’ve heard lovely things about too. The store’s giant yellow sign sticks out like a sore thumb on Chinatown’s “unofficial Main Street” that’s decorated with the lucky Chinese color of red all over. There’s no seating inside, which I wouldn’t expect to change after the pandemic, given the store’s small space. There’s a few back-of-the-house staff, but it’s been one person taking my order and packing it up the two times I’ve been there. Let me start off by saying the staff there are so friendly - they really care about making sure you know all the temperatures you can enjoy your tarts at (more on that later) and just making you feel like a human, which is not always an easy find at bakeries and restaurants. Upon entrance, you’ll see that there are “sneeze guard” dividers to protect the tarts from any customers (who must wear a mask inside too), and the tarts are lined up on Silpats and plastic trays. They currently offer five flavors of original cheese, matcha, ube (purple yam), chocolate, and strawberry-filled chocolate. I’ve tried all but the chocolate one, since I’m not the biggest fan of chocolate (I’m prepared to get some hate mail…). My favorite is the matcha, because the matcha accompanies the cheese perfectly, but you really can’t go wrong with any of them. Inside of the Matcha Cheese Now, about those temperatures I was talking about, there are four ways to enjoy these tarts. It’s almost like four different dessert types that range from firm + cheesecake-like to molten lava tarts. Putting the tart in the fridge will make the flowy inside firm up like a cheesecake, while putting it in the oven / air-fryer will make the inside hot and ooze of lava cheese. The other two ways are the most similar, which are just warming the tarts up in the microwave and eating it plain-Jane room temperature. My personal favorite is room-temperature, because I still get a slightly flowy inside while the tart retains a cheesecake-esque texture on the outer parts of the filling, but even just the versatility of how this dessert can be consumed is so unique. While I do love myself a flaky HK egg tart crust, Pinklady double bakes their tart shells, making for a crispier, slightly toasted tartlet. I was beyond satisfied with my stop at Pinklady. My dad and I fought over the last cheese tart, because they’re just that good (we ended up splitting it). Opening at the peak of the pandemic in April is no easy feat, and although there are many old staples in Chinatown that deserve an equal amount of appreciation, Pinklady is a great addition to an already fantastic, robust neighborhood dessert scene. Be sure to pay a visit at your next stop in Chinatown! Left to Right: Original, Matcha, Chocolate Strawberry</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Wasa-bi Happy 😊 Yama Sushi</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/nyceats/2020/07/03/yamasushi.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Wasa-bi Happy 😊 Yama Sushi" /><published>2020-07-03T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2020-07-03T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/nyceats/2020/07/03/yamasushi</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/nyceats/2020/07/03/yamasushi.html">&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/nyceats/yamasushi/lunchbento.JPG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;singleimage&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.yama-nyc.com/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Yama Sushi&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; is definitely a spot you’d skip over at first glance. It has an unassuming, dark exterior to go along with its basement location, so it wouldn’t be somewhere I’d choose initially, but this restaurant is my dad’s favorite place in New York. About 20 years ago, my dad used to commute to work in Manhattan before he switched to working at home, but he discovered Yama with his coworkers in the early days of his job. The basement-esque location we go to now is different than the one he used to go to, but he says this one is just as good!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My dad loves to eat fish, especially sashimi, and even though I’m really not a big fan of fish, I do like sashimi and sushi. I hope that I’ll be able to explore Japan one day to try authentic food, but for now, Yama serves high-quality, thinly sliced sashimi fish that keeps my family super happy. The “&lt;strong&gt;sashimi entree&lt;/strong&gt;” of assorted sashimi is my dad’s favorite meal to eat. The sashimi is sliced thinner than a lot of sushi restaurants do, with pieces that are longer too. They are served on top of perilla leaves that are a perfect palate cleanser, and eating rice in between slices is recommended too. I wish I could tell you the types of fish in this selection, but I can definitely say there’s salmon and tuna (sorry!).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/nyceats/yamasushi/yamasashimi.JPG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;singleimage&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;
        Sashimi Entree!
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While my sister and dad get the sashimi entree, I opt for a &lt;strong&gt;hot dish-sushi combo bento box&lt;/strong&gt;. A bento is simply a box of an assortment of rice/noodles, meat, &amp;amp; vegetables that’s very popular throughout East Asia. The photo at the very top is the lunch version, where you can choose 2 entrees out of many options, such as tonkatsu, ginger pork, tempura, sushi, hamachi kama, just to name a few. I love their chicken karaage, and even though I haven’t had a huge amount of karaage, this is my personal favorite! I also get their sushi, which is nigiri-style, which is just a slice of raw fish over sushi rice. I have noticed that the raw fish used on the sushi is warmer and not as high-quality as the sashimi alone, but it’s still great. The steam from the rice does wlightly warm the raw fish a bit, so it’s not the very chilled temperature that the sashimi retains. The box is accompanied with fresh orange slices and broiled fish - even for those aren’t the biggest fish fans (me), this fish is so tender, flaky, and well-flavored!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The dinner boxes work a little differently, as you don’t get as much control on what comes with the box, besides your choice of beef or chicken teriyaki and sushi or sashimi. The box comes with shrimp and vegetable tempura, fried shrimp shumai, rice, and ginger dressed salad. It’s perfect for people who want to sample multiple things, which is great for people who are a little indecisive when it comes to food (me, again).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/nyceats/yamasushi/dinnerbento.JPG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;singleimage&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;
        Beef Teriyaki Dinner Bento
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another dish we’ve tried is the &lt;strong&gt;spicy tuna crispy rice&lt;/strong&gt;. One of the most popular dishes in American-Japanese restaurants, Yama makes it look incredibly fancy. This dish is just a fried sushi rice “platform” topped with spicy tuna and more mayo/chives. It’s pretty simple, but it’s a dish that combines crunch with some light spice. I think it’s a great introduction to those who’ve never had raw fish!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/nyceats/yamasushi/crispyrice.jpg&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;singleimage&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been going to Yama for a few years now, and I really feel fully satisfied every time. Japanese food is something that can be so excited, and while I’m not sure that Yama is super authentic, I can confidently say that they serve very high-quality fish that is sliced a little differently than your typical sushi restaurant. Yama is a very relaxed setting, and the portions are well-priced for the amount. If you work in the city or are just in the mood for a casual sushi lunch with quality you know you can trust, Yama is your place!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/nyceats/yamasushi/sashimilayout.JPG&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;singleimage&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;
    Sashimi + Dinner Bento
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="nyceats" /><summary type="html">Yama Sushi is definitely a spot you’d skip over at first glance. It has an unassuming, dark exterior to go along with its basement location, so it wouldn’t be somewhere I’d choose initially, but this restaurant is my dad’s favorite place in New York. About 20 years ago, my dad used to commute to work in Manhattan before he switched to working at home, but he discovered Yama with his coworkers in the early days of his job. The basement-esque location we go to now is different than the one he used to go to, but he says this one is just as good! My dad loves to eat fish, especially sashimi, and even though I’m really not a big fan of fish, I do like sashimi and sushi. I hope that I’ll be able to explore Japan one day to try authentic food, but for now, Yama serves high-quality, thinly sliced sashimi fish that keeps my family super happy. The “sashimi entree” of assorted sashimi is my dad’s favorite meal to eat. The sashimi is sliced thinner than a lot of sushi restaurants do, with pieces that are longer too. They are served on top of perilla leaves that are a perfect palate cleanser, and eating rice in between slices is recommended too. I wish I could tell you the types of fish in this selection, but I can definitely say there’s salmon and tuna (sorry!). Sashimi Entree! While my sister and dad get the sashimi entree, I opt for a hot dish-sushi combo bento box. A bento is simply a box of an assortment of rice/noodles, meat, &amp;amp; vegetables that’s very popular throughout East Asia. The photo at the very top is the lunch version, where you can choose 2 entrees out of many options, such as tonkatsu, ginger pork, tempura, sushi, hamachi kama, just to name a few. I love their chicken karaage, and even though I haven’t had a huge amount of karaage, this is my personal favorite! I also get their sushi, which is nigiri-style, which is just a slice of raw fish over sushi rice. I have noticed that the raw fish used on the sushi is warmer and not as high-quality as the sashimi alone, but it’s still great. The steam from the rice does wlightly warm the raw fish a bit, so it’s not the very chilled temperature that the sashimi retains. The box is accompanied with fresh orange slices and broiled fish - even for those aren’t the biggest fish fans (me), this fish is so tender, flaky, and well-flavored! The dinner boxes work a little differently, as you don’t get as much control on what comes with the box, besides your choice of beef or chicken teriyaki and sushi or sashimi. The box comes with shrimp and vegetable tempura, fried shrimp shumai, rice, and ginger dressed salad. It’s perfect for people who want to sample multiple things, which is great for people who are a little indecisive when it comes to food (me, again). Beef Teriyaki Dinner Bento Another dish we’ve tried is the spicy tuna crispy rice. One of the most popular dishes in American-Japanese restaurants, Yama makes it look incredibly fancy. This dish is just a fried sushi rice “platform” topped with spicy tuna and more mayo/chives. It’s pretty simple, but it’s a dish that combines crunch with some light spice. I think it’s a great introduction to those who’ve never had raw fish! I’ve been going to Yama for a few years now, and I really feel fully satisfied every time. Japanese food is something that can be so excited, and while I’m not sure that Yama is super authentic, I can confidently say that they serve very high-quality fish that is sliced a little differently than your typical sushi restaurant. Yama is a very relaxed setting, and the portions are well-priced for the amount. If you work in the city or are just in the mood for a casual sushi lunch with quality you know you can trust, Yama is your place! Sashimi + Dinner Bento</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">It’s So Fluffy, I’m Gonna ~~</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/nyceats/2020/07/02/fluffy-pancakes.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="It’s So Fluffy, I’m Gonna ~~" /><published>2020-07-02T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2020-07-02T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/nyceats/2020/07/02/fluffy-pancakes</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/nyceats/2020/07/02/fluffy-pancakes.html">&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot; text-align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/nyceats/pancake/fluffypinkcropped.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;singleimage&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://taiyakinyc.com/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Taiyaki NYC&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; is known for their Japanese fish-shaped cones filled with soft serve ice cream. The texture of the cones are a little bit like waffles, but so much better. Traditionally, they’re stuffed with anko, or sweet red azuki bean paste, but Taiyaki offers them with custard filling too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;…BUT! Today, we’re talking about their fluffy pancakes! Although they’ve been popular in Japan for a while now, fluffy pancakes have just started making their splash in New York City. It’s really no surprise that these pancakes are gaining so much popularity - their taller-than-average height and jiggly movement make for a fun dish to eat. This is achieved through separating the egg yolks from the egg whites, the latter of which is beaten until stiff peaks are attained. This meringue is gently folded into the batter, which makes these pancakes extra fluffy because of the air bubbles formed during this process. However, these pancakes are so much more than their stunning appearance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was shocked that these pancakes were just as tasty as how stunning they looked. Given that a good part of the batter is that meringue, my initial expectation was that it would mostly taste of egg whites. I really was surprised by the great balance in taste - they have a really subtle, but just strong enough, sweetness, custard-y taste, and slight browning on the outside. Since I don’t like my desserts too sweet, these pancakes really were everything I wanted!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot; text-align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/nyceats/pancake/fluffywhite.JPG&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;singleimage&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Taiyaki NYC offers these pancakes in two ways. The pancakes I tried were topped with a soft matcha cream sauce and a crispy mini anko-filled taiyaki, and served with a side of whipped cream, but you can also get them your classic style with a pat of butter, powdered sugar, whipped cream, and a side of syrup. Since these pancakes are just so good on their own, either way will taste absolutely fantastic!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I found out about these pancakes that were taking NYC by storm through &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/taiyakinyc&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;@taiyakinyc&lt;/a&gt; on Instagram and was incredibly excited to try them out, but Taiyaki NYC only sells these cakes from Fridays to Sundays, 11am-2pm at their Manhattan, Brooklyn, and Boston locations for now, to ensure that their product is quality-controlled. So, my first soufflé pancake experience was actually at the Smorgasburg Outdoor Food Market that takes place from late March to October in Williamsburg. A stand, &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/Fluffysnyc/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Fluffy’s&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, was a new vendor for the 2019 season that specializes in soufflé pancakes. The only difference I could find was that Fluffy’s pancakes were slightly undercooked, which you even might be able to notice in the photo below. This is probably due to the overwhelming lines at their stand - Fluffy’s was undoubtedly one of the most popular vendors at the market. Fluffy’s also offers a lot more variety in flavors offered, including blueberry cheesecake (pictured below), crème brûlée (yes, sounds incredible!), Nutella, and a rotating vegan option too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot; text-align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/nyceats/pancake/fluffysmorg.JPG&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;singleimage&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;Blueberry Cheesecake Pancakes&lt;/div&gt;  
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wherever you find your fluffy soufflé pancakes, I have no doubt that you’ll enjoy them. From what I’ve seen, a reasonable &lt;em&gt;New York City&lt;/em&gt; price for about 2 pancakes will run ~$10-$12. I’ve seen some places run their prices up to $20 for two, not so tall, fluffy pancakes, which I can’t justify buying whatsoever. Taiyaki NYC makes an absolutely fantastic pancake, as does Fluffy’s *, and I highly recommend that if the time (Fridays-Sundays, 11am-2pm) and price work for you, have these pancakes as a really lovely end-of-the-week treat 🥞.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;-understandably-smorgasburg-is-not-operating-during-the-covid-19-pandemic&quot;&gt;* Understandably, Smorgasburg is not operating during the COVID-19 pandemic.&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot; text-align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/nyceats/pancake/fluffytaiyaki.JPG&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;singleimage&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="nyceats" /><summary type="html">Taiyaki NYC is known for their Japanese fish-shaped cones filled with soft serve ice cream. The texture of the cones are a little bit like waffles, but so much better. Traditionally, they’re stuffed with anko, or sweet red azuki bean paste, but Taiyaki offers them with custard filling too. …BUT! Today, we’re talking about their fluffy pancakes! Although they’ve been popular in Japan for a while now, fluffy pancakes have just started making their splash in New York City. It’s really no surprise that these pancakes are gaining so much popularity - their taller-than-average height and jiggly movement make for a fun dish to eat. This is achieved through separating the egg yolks from the egg whites, the latter of which is beaten until stiff peaks are attained. This meringue is gently folded into the batter, which makes these pancakes extra fluffy because of the air bubbles formed during this process. However, these pancakes are so much more than their stunning appearance. I was shocked that these pancakes were just as tasty as how stunning they looked. Given that a good part of the batter is that meringue, my initial expectation was that it would mostly taste of egg whites. I really was surprised by the great balance in taste - they have a really subtle, but just strong enough, sweetness, custard-y taste, and slight browning on the outside. Since I don’t like my desserts too sweet, these pancakes really were everything I wanted! Taiyaki NYC offers these pancakes in two ways. The pancakes I tried were topped with a soft matcha cream sauce and a crispy mini anko-filled taiyaki, and served with a side of whipped cream, but you can also get them your classic style with a pat of butter, powdered sugar, whipped cream, and a side of syrup. Since these pancakes are just so good on their own, either way will taste absolutely fantastic! I found out about these pancakes that were taking NYC by storm through @taiyakinyc on Instagram and was incredibly excited to try them out, but Taiyaki NYC only sells these cakes from Fridays to Sundays, 11am-2pm at their Manhattan, Brooklyn, and Boston locations for now, to ensure that their product is quality-controlled. So, my first soufflé pancake experience was actually at the Smorgasburg Outdoor Food Market that takes place from late March to October in Williamsburg. A stand, Fluffy’s, was a new vendor for the 2019 season that specializes in soufflé pancakes. The only difference I could find was that Fluffy’s pancakes were slightly undercooked, which you even might be able to notice in the photo below. This is probably due to the overwhelming lines at their stand - Fluffy’s was undoubtedly one of the most popular vendors at the market. Fluffy’s also offers a lot more variety in flavors offered, including blueberry cheesecake (pictured below), crème brûlée (yes, sounds incredible!), Nutella, and a rotating vegan option too. Blueberry Cheesecake Pancakes Wherever you find your fluffy soufflé pancakes, I have no doubt that you’ll enjoy them. From what I’ve seen, a reasonable New York City price for about 2 pancakes will run ~$10-$12. I’ve seen some places run their prices up to $20 for two, not so tall, fluffy pancakes, which I can’t justify buying whatsoever. Taiyaki NYC makes an absolutely fantastic pancake, as does Fluffy’s *, and I highly recommend that if the time (Fridays-Sundays, 11am-2pm) and price work for you, have these pancakes as a really lovely end-of-the-week treat 🥞. * Understandably, Smorgasburg is not operating during the COVID-19 pandemic.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Gyu-Kaku Japanese BBQ</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/nyceats/2020/07/01/gyu-kaku.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Gyu-Kaku Japanese BBQ" /><published>2020-07-01T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2020-07-01T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/nyceats/2020/07/01/gyu-kaku</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/nyceats/2020/07/01/gyu-kaku.html">&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot; text-align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/nyceats/gyukaku/gyugrill.jpg&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;singleimage&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;
        Pork belly, Bistro Hanger Steak, Spicy Pork, and Assorted Veggie Packet
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With over 700 locations world wide, the global franchise restaurant chain, Gyu-Kaku, is definitely not unique to NYC, but I do live close to the city, so Manhattan is the most accessible place for me to enjoy their Japanese barbecue. According to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gyu-kaku.com/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;restaurant’s website&lt;/a&gt;, the name, Gyu-Kaku, means “Horn of the Bull” in Japanese. The chain strives to replicate an authentic yakiniku, or grilled meat barbecue, dining experience that isn’t so easy to find outside of Japan. Although I’ve never been to Japan, what matters is that Gyu-Kaku still serves high-quality dishes prepared with lots of care.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The real charm about this place is how worth it the food is, ESPECIALLY if you go during their “Happy Hour”, where they offer many dishes at a discounted price (GO DURING HAPPY HOUR!!). You get so much food for a reasonable price, making this one of my all-time favorite meals. I leave feeling so whole-hearted every time without my dad needing to spend way too much.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At Gyu-Kaku, yakiniku is grill-it-yourself! You can &lt;em&gt;kind of&lt;/em&gt; think about it like Korean BBQ, but the taste is REALLY quite different from Korean barbecue. However, if you like KBBQ, I have no doubts that you’ll LOVE yakinuku! They are both very unique dining experiences, as in my opinion, a Korean BBQ meal is only complete with a large set of banchan side dishes, such as your typical kimchi, Kongnamul bean sprouts, mung bean jelly, among MANY, many others (I am by no means an expert on either KBBQ or yakiniku, so I’m sure I’m missing a lot) that are meant to be enjoyed alongside the meal, whereas yakiniku can be enjoyed with simpler accompaniments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot; text-align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/nyceats/gyukaku/gyukakulayout.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;singleimage&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;The Layout&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So the first order of business: the meat! They offer TONS of different types of meat, such as chicken, duck, pork belly, salmon, BBQ calamari, Japanese-style pork sausage, and of course, beef. I would say the stars of the show are the beef preparations, however, as their beef options range from classic thin beef tongue to premium USDA Prime kalbi short ribs. You can choose from meat marinated in their signature marinades* OR just naked meat with some salt + pepper - you can’t go wrong with either!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;-all-of-their-sauces--marinades-are-gluten-free&quot;&gt;* All of their sauces + marinades are gluten-free!!&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My personal favorite meat (beef) options are the garlic-marinated bistro hanger steak, ultra-thin, super-fatty toro beef, and of course for a treat, the kalbi short ribs marinated in sweet soy tare. Those might be my favorites, but ANY of their meat options, beyond just beef, are absolutely fantastic. Do yourself a favor and take advantage of the sauce bottle trio on the side of your table!! The best sauce is the combo of all three, ponzu, sweet soy, and “spicy”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know that as a yakiniku restaurant, the premise behind the whole place is their grilled meat. But the things that keep me coming back are their incredible plates of cooked dishes that make you feel so cozy inside.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been coming to Gyu-Kaku for as long as I can remember. My mom used to work in the city, and this spot was a favorite among her and her coworkers. When my sister and I were first introduced, we couldn’t stop coming back!! So this place really brings back a lot of fond memories that make my heart warm every time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot; text-align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/nyceats/gyukaku/garlicnoodles.JPG&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;singleimage&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;Is your mouth watering yet?!&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first dish that I’d like to talk about is their &lt;strong&gt;garlic noodles&lt;/strong&gt;. Let me tell you, if Gyu-Kaku ONLY sold these noodles, I’d be okay with it. This is the first dish I ever ate Gyu-Kaku, and I’ve loved them for as long as I can remember. The dish is made with thick, udon-style, egg noodles that are coated in a slightly sweetened garlic sauce and vegetables. You have the choice of ground chicken, vegetables, or shrimp. They’re served on a cast-iron plate, which slightly browns the outsides of the noodles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot; text-align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/nyceats/gyukaku/tunariceportrait.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;singleimage&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;The &quot;Volcano&quot;!&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another dish I love is their absolutely non-traditional, but no less mouthwatering, &lt;strong&gt;spicy tuna volcano&lt;/strong&gt;. It’s a crispy fried block of rice topped with spicy tuna over a layer of Japanese shoyu BBQ sauce. Enough said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These two dishes are some of their best-sellers, and it’s not difficult to see why. These might be my two favorites, but not far behind (at all) are any of their &lt;strong&gt;bibimbap rice dishes&lt;/strong&gt; that achieve glorious browning from their hot stone bowls and their &lt;strong&gt;tuna poké nachos&lt;/strong&gt; - something about a fried wonton skin just feels right, you know?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot; text-align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/nyceats/gyukaku/wontonnachos.JPG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;singleimage&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;Tuna Poké Nachos&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gyu-Kaku will forever have a special place in my heart, as it has been since I was young. This restaurant chain makes food that is so effortlessly comforting and tasty. I can confidently say that I’ve never had a bad dish from here, despite the overwhelmingly large menu. Even though the place isn’t catered towards vegetarians, they make some great grilled veggies (with or without a touch of butter), of which I recommend the corn, and salads too. If you aren’t stuffed by the end, they also serve great desserts, like crêpe cake slices from Lady M and chocolate lava cakes, of which I’ve included photos below. I highly recommmend this place for any and all occasions, as they serve well-priced food that leaves you feeling happier than a traditional “5-star” meal would.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table class=&quot;home&quot;&gt;
    &lt;td class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/nyceats/gyukaku/lavagyu.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;td class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/nyceats/gyukaku/crepecakebday.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;/td&gt;            
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;note-just-to-clarify-these-photos-are-from-several-different-times-ive-eaten-at-gyu-kaku-over-the-years&quot;&gt;Note: &lt;em&gt;Just to clarify, these photos are from several different times I’ve eaten at Gyu-Kaku over the years.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h6&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="nyceats" /><summary type="html">Pork belly, Bistro Hanger Steak, Spicy Pork, and Assorted Veggie Packet With over 700 locations world wide, the global franchise restaurant chain, Gyu-Kaku, is definitely not unique to NYC, but I do live close to the city, so Manhattan is the most accessible place for me to enjoy their Japanese barbecue. According to the restaurant’s website, the name, Gyu-Kaku, means “Horn of the Bull” in Japanese. The chain strives to replicate an authentic yakiniku, or grilled meat barbecue, dining experience that isn’t so easy to find outside of Japan. Although I’ve never been to Japan, what matters is that Gyu-Kaku still serves high-quality dishes prepared with lots of care. The real charm about this place is how worth it the food is, ESPECIALLY if you go during their “Happy Hour”, where they offer many dishes at a discounted price (GO DURING HAPPY HOUR!!). You get so much food for a reasonable price, making this one of my all-time favorite meals. I leave feeling so whole-hearted every time without my dad needing to spend way too much. At Gyu-Kaku, yakiniku is grill-it-yourself! You can kind of think about it like Korean BBQ, but the taste is REALLY quite different from Korean barbecue. However, if you like KBBQ, I have no doubts that you’ll LOVE yakinuku! They are both very unique dining experiences, as in my opinion, a Korean BBQ meal is only complete with a large set of banchan side dishes, such as your typical kimchi, Kongnamul bean sprouts, mung bean jelly, among MANY, many others (I am by no means an expert on either KBBQ or yakiniku, so I’m sure I’m missing a lot) that are meant to be enjoyed alongside the meal, whereas yakiniku can be enjoyed with simpler accompaniments. The Layout So the first order of business: the meat! They offer TONS of different types of meat, such as chicken, duck, pork belly, salmon, BBQ calamari, Japanese-style pork sausage, and of course, beef. I would say the stars of the show are the beef preparations, however, as their beef options range from classic thin beef tongue to premium USDA Prime kalbi short ribs. You can choose from meat marinated in their signature marinades* OR just naked meat with some salt + pepper - you can’t go wrong with either!! * All of their sauces + marinades are gluten-free!! My personal favorite meat (beef) options are the garlic-marinated bistro hanger steak, ultra-thin, super-fatty toro beef, and of course for a treat, the kalbi short ribs marinated in sweet soy tare. Those might be my favorites, but ANY of their meat options, beyond just beef, are absolutely fantastic. Do yourself a favor and take advantage of the sauce bottle trio on the side of your table!! The best sauce is the combo of all three, ponzu, sweet soy, and “spicy”. I know that as a yakiniku restaurant, the premise behind the whole place is their grilled meat. But the things that keep me coming back are their incredible plates of cooked dishes that make you feel so cozy inside. I’ve been coming to Gyu-Kaku for as long as I can remember. My mom used to work in the city, and this spot was a favorite among her and her coworkers. When my sister and I were first introduced, we couldn’t stop coming back!! So this place really brings back a lot of fond memories that make my heart warm every time. Is your mouth watering yet?! The first dish that I’d like to talk about is their garlic noodles. Let me tell you, if Gyu-Kaku ONLY sold these noodles, I’d be okay with it. This is the first dish I ever ate Gyu-Kaku, and I’ve loved them for as long as I can remember. The dish is made with thick, udon-style, egg noodles that are coated in a slightly sweetened garlic sauce and vegetables. You have the choice of ground chicken, vegetables, or shrimp. They’re served on a cast-iron plate, which slightly browns the outsides of the noodles. The &quot;Volcano&quot;! Another dish I love is their absolutely non-traditional, but no less mouthwatering, spicy tuna volcano. It’s a crispy fried block of rice topped with spicy tuna over a layer of Japanese shoyu BBQ sauce. Enough said. These two dishes are some of their best-sellers, and it’s not difficult to see why. These might be my two favorites, but not far behind (at all) are any of their bibimbap rice dishes that achieve glorious browning from their hot stone bowls and their tuna poké nachos - something about a fried wonton skin just feels right, you know? Tuna Poké Nachos Gyu-Kaku will forever have a special place in my heart, as it has been since I was young. This restaurant chain makes food that is so effortlessly comforting and tasty. I can confidently say that I’ve never had a bad dish from here, despite the overwhelmingly large menu. Even though the place isn’t catered towards vegetarians, they make some great grilled veggies (with or without a touch of butter), of which I recommend the corn, and salads too. If you aren’t stuffed by the end, they also serve great desserts, like crêpe cake slices from Lady M and chocolate lava cakes, of which I’ve included photos below. I highly recommmend this place for any and all occasions, as they serve well-priced food that leaves you feeling happier than a traditional “5-star” meal would. Note: Just to clarify, these photos are from several different times I’ve eaten at Gyu-Kaku over the years.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Seattle</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/beyond/2020/06/03/seattle.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Seattle" /><published>2020-06-03T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2020-06-03T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/beyond/2020/06/03/seattle</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/beyond/2020/06/03/seattle.html">&lt;table&gt;
    &lt;td class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/seattle/platelunchcrop.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;overlayblogphotos&quot;&gt;Korean Sizzling Spicy Pork Belly Rice Bowl from Byte Food Truck&lt;/div&gt;        
    &lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;td class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/seattle/pikeplace.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;overlayblogphotos&quot;&gt;@ Pike Place Market&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/td&gt;            
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome to one of my favorite cities!! 😊 While it’s known for the constant rain, the Seattle summer weather is absolutely perfect - mid-70s, shining sun until 9PM, and minimal rain. What you wouldn’t expect, though, are the unique attractions, beautiful landscape, and some of the best food you’ll find around! See all the places I went below…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-destinations&quot;&gt;The Destinations&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;Foods:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;div id=&quot;foods&quot;&gt;
    &lt;h5&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mollymoon.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;Molly Moon's Homemade Ice Cream&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Okay, but first, dessert - who said dessert can't come first?! &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mollymoon.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;Molly Moon's&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, one of Seattle's most popular ice cream shops, was the first on my list.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot; text-align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/seattle/mollymoons.JPG&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;singleimage&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;Fresh Strawberry + &quot;Yeti&quot; Ice Cream&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;According to their website, their &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mollymoon.com/flavors&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; Yeti&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; ice cream flavor is their signature sweet cream ice cream, but swirled with vanilla bean caramel and &quot;yeti&quot; granola, which are both made in-house, along with Theo chocolate bits. They make the creamiest ice cream, and knowing that everything is sourced locally, with no artificial additives, makes this ice cream even more lovable!!&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;h5&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://dintaifungusa.com/menu/soup-dumplings/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Din Tai Fung&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt; 
    &lt;p&gt;SOUP-er good! &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://dintaifungusa.com/menu/soup-dumplings/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Din Tai Fung&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; (DTF), an international Shanghainese food chain originating from Taiwan that specializes in &lt;em&gt;xiaolongbao (XLB)&lt;/em&gt;, better known as soup dumplings. This restaurant is one of my favorites from Asia, as my dad introduced it to me on our trip to China in 2018. I had always been a fan of xiaolongbao, but there's something so special about the way DTF prepares their ultra-thin wrappers and piping hot soup inside. While DTF is pricy for xiaolongbao, many will agree that indulging in these small dumplings of heaven are worth it. Please, DTF, come to the East Coast.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot; text-align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/seattle/dtfseattle.JPG&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;singleimage&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;All 10 lil xiaolongbao for me 😁&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;I got just the plain Kurobata pork soup dumplings (the cheapest XLB option), but they also sell crab + pork ones that are my favorite kind. DTF also serves an even more indulgent option - the truffle Kurobata pork ones. If you love the unique taste of truffle, these are definitely for you.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;h5&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.portagebaycafe.com/south-lake-union&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;Portage Bay Cafe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt; 
    &lt;p&gt;Banana - ooo - nana. 🍌 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.portagebaycafe.com/south-lake-union&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Portage Bay Cafe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; is a very popular local Seattle brunch chain that serves a wide variety of benedicts, French toasts, pancakes, eggs, + assorted breakfast staples. Known for their breakfast bar, customers that order off the &quot;breakfast bar&quot; section are able to top their meal off with a &quot;selection of seasonal fruit, nuts, &amp;amp; whipped cream&quot;. I ordered the bananas foster french toast and topped it off with their fresh strawberries - so apPEELing 😋&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot; text-align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/seattle/bftoast.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;singleimage&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;Bananas Foster French Toast with the kraken rum &amp;amp; caramel sauce&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;h5&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://getyourhotcakes.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;Hot Cakes Molten Chocolate Cakery&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;I &lt;em&gt;lava&lt;/em&gt; chocolate lava cakes!!&lt;/p&gt;         
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot; text-align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/seattle/hotcakes.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;singleimage&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Dark Decadence&lt;/em&gt; Cake&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;And &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://getyourhotcakes.com/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Hot Cakes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; serves up a GOOOOOD one. They are a dessert shop serving up the highest quality molten chocolate cakes, cookies, thick milkshakes, and warm dessert drinks. Their original cake, which was first served back in 2008, the Dark Decadence, is crafted with Theo chocolate, dry-burned caramel, nib toffee, + vanilla ice cream. They pride themselves on their dry-burned caramel, which takes long periods of intense concentration and patience (you can read more about it &lt;a href=&quot;https://getyourhotcakes.com/pages/dry-burned-caramel&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;). It's worth it though - you can taste the quality in each bite of this cake + its sidekicks. &lt;strong&gt;A must-stop when in Seattle!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;h5&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/fbseattle/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;Facebook South Lake Union&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt; 
    &lt;p&gt;To kick-off Intern Family Weekend, Facebook Seattle hosted a Kick-Off Social. We enjoyed appetizers (which we &lt;em&gt;easily&lt;/em&gt; turned into a meal) provided by Facebook catering. All the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businessinsider.com/facebook-cafeteria-food-is-amazing-2015-2&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;hype about the Facebook cafeterias&lt;/a&gt; is for a reason - they're redefining the term &lt;em&gt;cafeteria&lt;/em&gt;. Facebook offices also include microkitchens on every floor, where employees are allowed to grab snacks + drinks as they please.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot; text-align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/seattle/fbappetizers.JPG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;singleimage&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;div id=&quot;fbappetizerdescription&quot;&gt;Teriyaki Chicken Skewers, Peanut Lettuce Wraps, Popcorn Tofu with Sesame BBQ Sauce, and Soba Noodle Salad (not pictured)&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p id=&quot;fbappetizerdescriptionmobile&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Teriyaki Chicken Skewers, Peanut Lettuce Wraps, Popcorn Tofu with Sesame BBQ Sauce, and Soba Noodle Salad (not pictured)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;button id=&quot;showfoods&quot; class=&quot;showmorephotosbutton&quot; onclick=&quot;toggleFoods()&quot;&gt;( + ) show me the food!&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;Places:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;div id=&quot;places&quot;&gt;
    &lt;h5&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://uvillage.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;University Village&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Antonia stayed at the University of Washington over the summer, making &lt;a href=&quot;https://uvillage.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;University Village&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; a convenient stop. UVillage is an open-air shopping complex, with numerous gourmet eateries + shops. It's easily one of the most beautiful shopping centers I've been to.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;h5&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/fbseattle/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;Facebook South Lake Union&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Let me just start off by saying how BEAUTIFUL the Facebook campus is. Here's just a few photos:&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;div&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/seattle/panorama.JPG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; id=&quot;panorama&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/seattle/otherfbview.JPG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; id=&quot;fbphoto1&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/seattle/couch.JPG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; id=&quot;fbphoto2&quot; class=&quot;buttonphotos&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;button id=&quot;showmorephotosfacebook&quot; class=&quot;showmorephotosbutton&quot; onclick=&quot;toggleImages()&quot;&gt;( + ) show more Facebook campus photos!&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Just wow, right? 😍&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;You can even see the Space Needle from the rooftop, among many other Seattle attractions. Seriously, Facebook Seattle is a real destination if you get the chance!!&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;h5&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.starbucks.com/coffeehouse/store-design/1st-and-pike&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;Pike Place Market + Great Gum Wall + Original Starbucks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot; text-align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/seattle/gumwall2.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;singleimage&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;@ the Gum Wall! (with my silly sister)&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;    
    &lt;p&gt;We checked out the original Starbucks and tried the Pike Place blend and blackberry lemonade iced tea. Pike Place had a wide variety of local artisan shops and a fish market, which were all fun to explore.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;h5&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.starbucksreserve.com/en-us/locations/seattle&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;Starbucks Reserve Roastery in Capitol Hill&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot; text-align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/seattle/starbucksreserve.JPG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;singleimage&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;Stunning 😍&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;This is the first Starbucks Roastery in the world, where they opened in 2014 in the vibrant Capitol Hill district. They create 
        super innovative drinks and serve up pastries. Try to stop by here before you get a lava cake from &lt;a href=&quot;https://getyourhotcakes.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;Hot Cakes&lt;/a&gt;!
    &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;h5&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.chihulygardenandglass.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;Chihuly Garden and Glass&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot; text-align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/seattle/glassflowers.JPG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;singleimage&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The artwork here is absolutely stunning and pops with color everywhere - I'm seriously obsessed with the art here!&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;h5&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.spaceneedle.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;Space Needle&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot; text-align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/seattle/bubzsea.JPG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;singleimage&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;...but I mean, if you didn't see the Space Needle, did you &lt;em&gt;see&lt;/em&gt; Seattle?&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;h5&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://seattlegreatwheel.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;The Seattle Great Wheel @ Pier 57&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot; text-align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/seattle/greatwheel.JPG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;singleimage&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;h5&gt;Also check out: &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lonelyplanet.com/articles/a-guide-to-seattles-alki-beach&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;Alki Beach&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.soundersfc.com/tickets&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;CenturyLink Field&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mopop.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;Museum of Pop (MoPOP)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;button id=&quot;showplaces&quot; class=&quot;showmorephotosbutton&quot; onclick=&quot;togglePlaces()&quot;&gt;( + ) show me where to go!&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Seattle has a ton to see, with lots of modern aspects, but still retaining the incredible history of the Pacific Northwest. I went to Seattle to visit my older sister, Antonia, at her internship, but if you’re just looking for a relaxing vacation getaway, don’t sleep on Seattle!!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="beyond" /><summary type="html">Korean Sizzling Spicy Pork Belly Rice Bowl from Byte Food Truck @ Pike Place Market Welcome to one of my favorite cities!! 😊 While it’s known for the constant rain, the Seattle summer weather is absolutely perfect - mid-70s, shining sun until 9PM, and minimal rain. What you wouldn’t expect, though, are the unique attractions, beautiful landscape, and some of the best food you’ll find around! See all the places I went below… The Destinations Foods: Molly Moon's Homemade Ice Cream Okay, but first, dessert - who said dessert can't come first?! Molly Moon's, one of Seattle's most popular ice cream shops, was the first on my list. Fresh Strawberry + &quot;Yeti&quot; Ice Cream According to their website, their Yeti ice cream flavor is their signature sweet cream ice cream, but swirled with vanilla bean caramel and &quot;yeti&quot; granola, which are both made in-house, along with Theo chocolate bits. They make the creamiest ice cream, and knowing that everything is sourced locally, with no artificial additives, makes this ice cream even more lovable!! Din Tai Fung SOUP-er good! Din Tai Fung (DTF), an international Shanghainese food chain originating from Taiwan that specializes in xiaolongbao (XLB), better known as soup dumplings. This restaurant is one of my favorites from Asia, as my dad introduced it to me on our trip to China in 2018. I had always been a fan of xiaolongbao, but there's something so special about the way DTF prepares their ultra-thin wrappers and piping hot soup inside. While DTF is pricy for xiaolongbao, many will agree that indulging in these small dumplings of heaven are worth it. Please, DTF, come to the East Coast. All 10 lil xiaolongbao for me 😁 I got just the plain Kurobata pork soup dumplings (the cheapest XLB option), but they also sell crab + pork ones that are my favorite kind. DTF also serves an even more indulgent option - the truffle Kurobata pork ones. If you love the unique taste of truffle, these are definitely for you. Portage Bay Cafe Banana - ooo - nana. 🍌 Portage Bay Cafe is a very popular local Seattle brunch chain that serves a wide variety of benedicts, French toasts, pancakes, eggs, + assorted breakfast staples. Known for their breakfast bar, customers that order off the &quot;breakfast bar&quot; section are able to top their meal off with a &quot;selection of seasonal fruit, nuts, &amp;amp; whipped cream&quot;. I ordered the bananas foster french toast and topped it off with their fresh strawberries - so apPEELing 😋 Bananas Foster French Toast with the kraken rum &amp;amp; caramel sauce Hot Cakes Molten Chocolate Cakery I lava chocolate lava cakes!! Dark Decadence Cake And Hot Cakes serves up a GOOOOOD one. They are a dessert shop serving up the highest quality molten chocolate cakes, cookies, thick milkshakes, and warm dessert drinks. Their original cake, which was first served back in 2008, the Dark Decadence, is crafted with Theo chocolate, dry-burned caramel, nib toffee, + vanilla ice cream. They pride themselves on their dry-burned caramel, which takes long periods of intense concentration and patience (you can read more about it here). It's worth it though - you can taste the quality in each bite of this cake + its sidekicks. A must-stop when in Seattle! Facebook South Lake Union To kick-off Intern Family Weekend, Facebook Seattle hosted a Kick-Off Social. We enjoyed appetizers (which we easily turned into a meal) provided by Facebook catering. All the hype about the Facebook cafeterias is for a reason - they're redefining the term cafeteria. Facebook offices also include microkitchens on every floor, where employees are allowed to grab snacks + drinks as they please. Teriyaki Chicken Skewers, Peanut Lettuce Wraps, Popcorn Tofu with Sesame BBQ Sauce, and Soba Noodle Salad (not pictured) Teriyaki Chicken Skewers, Peanut Lettuce Wraps, Popcorn Tofu with Sesame BBQ Sauce, and Soba Noodle Salad (not pictured) ( + ) show me the food! Places: University Village Antonia stayed at the University of Washington over the summer, making University Village a convenient stop. UVillage is an open-air shopping complex, with numerous gourmet eateries + shops. It's easily one of the most beautiful shopping centers I've been to. Facebook South Lake Union Let me just start off by saying how BEAUTIFUL the Facebook campus is. Here's just a few photos: ( + ) show more Facebook campus photos! Just wow, right? 😍 You can even see the Space Needle from the rooftop, among many other Seattle attractions. Seriously, Facebook Seattle is a real destination if you get the chance!! Pike Place Market + Great Gum Wall + Original Starbucks @ the Gum Wall! (with my silly sister) We checked out the original Starbucks and tried the Pike Place blend and blackberry lemonade iced tea. Pike Place had a wide variety of local artisan shops and a fish market, which were all fun to explore. Starbucks Reserve Roastery in Capitol Hill Stunning 😍 This is the first Starbucks Roastery in the world, where they opened in 2014 in the vibrant Capitol Hill district. They create super innovative drinks and serve up pastries. Try to stop by here before you get a lava cake from Hot Cakes! Chihuly Garden and Glass The artwork here is absolutely stunning and pops with color everywhere - I'm seriously obsessed with the art here! Space Needle ...but I mean, if you didn't see the Space Needle, did you see Seattle? The Seattle Great Wheel @ Pier 57 Also check out: Alki Beach, CenturyLink Field, Museum of Pop (MoPOP) ( + ) show me where to go! Seattle has a ton to see, with lots of modern aspects, but still retaining the incredible history of the Pacific Northwest. I went to Seattle to visit my older sister, Antonia, at her internship, but if you’re just looking for a relaxing vacation getaway, don’t sleep on Seattle!!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Los Angeles</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/beyond/2020/06/02/losangeles.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Los Angeles" /><published>2020-06-02T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2020-06-02T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/beyond/2020/06/02/losangeles</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/beyond/2020/06/02/losangeles.html">&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot; text-align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/losangeles/laviews.JPG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;singleimage&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;
    ~ Long Beach Views ~
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WELCOME TO THE CITY OF ANGELS! Having lived in the same place my whole life on the East Coast, I had always been interested in life on the West Coast. New York City is a very fast city - everyone is always on the move and in a rush. Los Angeles is what some might consider NYC’s polar opposite. As die-hard New Yorkers say, if the only thing you can say about your city is that the weather is good, the city &lt;em&gt;probably&lt;/em&gt; just isn’t that good. SoCal is known for its warmer weather throughout the year, but there’s so much more to this wonderful city than just the weather.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L.A. goes at a slower pace than NYC, giving it a more relaxed feel. But, with both cities, there are great things and some not-so-fantastic things. NYC is a city made to be explored through public transportation and by foot, especially given Manhattan’s smart grid design. You pretty much &lt;em&gt;need&lt;/em&gt; a car to get around, which means the notorious L.A. traffic. However, my sister says the public transportation isn’t as terrible as people say it is, but…NYC definitely wins in that one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Between the two, my winner is… actually L.A.!! Many will disagree, but L.A. is such an inviting, exciting city that has endless free activities to enjoy and a food scene that I &lt;em&gt;personally&lt;/em&gt; love more. Don’t get me wrong, NYC is an absolute food paradise, but I guess my taste buds are just happier in the L.A. sunshine ☀️. Also, my mom spent a few years in California when she first immigrated to the U.S., so maybe it’s just in my blood?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So my older sister, Antonia, actually goes to college in the L.A. area, so for Thanksgiving 2018, my dad and I went to spend time with her. We were only able to explore L.A. for about three days, so we didn’t get to see a whole lot, but that can be a good thing - L.A. keeps me coming back for more, and that means that I have something to look forward to the next time I return.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out the places I ate and visited during my Thanksgiving trip!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;we-went-all-over-la-metro-area-including-san-gabriel-valley-long-beach-hollywood-little-tokyo-and-more-so-itll-definitely-be-a-drive-around&quot;&gt;We went all over L.A. metro area, including San Gabriel Valley, Long Beach, Hollywood, Little Tokyo, and more, so it’ll definitely be a drive around!&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-destinations&quot;&gt;The Destinations&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;Foods:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;div id=&quot;califoods&quot;&gt;
    &lt;h5&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.chinchikurin-usa.com/menu/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;
    Chinchikurin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot; text-align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/losangeles/okonomiyaki.JPG&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;singleimage&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;
            GOAM - Green Onions and Mayo
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;          
    &lt;p&gt;
    Eating at &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.chinchikurin-usa.com/menu/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;
    Chinchikurin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; was my first time trying okonomiyaki. Since then, this dish has been 
    one of my all-time favorites! They serve Hiroshima okonomiyaki, which is one of 
    two main styles of okonomiyaki. Okonomiyaki is a savory pancake with okonomi- meaning 
    &quot;as you like&quot; and -yaki meaning &quot;cooked&quot;. Osaka style is a batter with all ingredients being 
    mixed inside, whereas each ingredient in the Hiroshima style is separated into its own layer, 
    allowing each layer to provide its own unique taste + texture. There's typically 11 (WOW!) layers, 
    with grilled noodles, vegetables, crepe-like batter, meat, and many more. 
    &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Chinchikurin offers 9 ways to eat your Hiroshima okonomiyaki, and each way has its 
    own specific toppings. My family tried 3 ways, as each pancake can be eaten as a single portion. 
    We shared the GOAM (pictured above), which is green onions and mayo, the B&amp;amp;C, or the basil &amp;amp; 
    cheese, and the Chinchikurinyaki, which has the shioburiyaki ground beef mixture inside. All 
    okonomiyakis served have &quot;The Classic&quot; 
    as their base, which can be ordered plain without toppings. However, the toppings make these pancakes 
    even more exciting! It's such a fun experience to eat here, as you're able to use the &quot;hera&quot; (miniature spatula) 
    to cut into the okonomiyaki that's sitting utop a heated grill. Get the B&amp;amp;C if you like cheese - it was my favorite!! 
    Chinchikurin also has a takoyaki window if you just want a quick snack walking through Little Tokyo! I absolutely love 
    this place. 
    &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;h5&gt;
    &lt;a href=&quot;https://unclejohnsdtla.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;
    Uncle John's Cafe&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;/h5&gt;
    &lt;table class=&quot;home&quot;&gt;
        &lt;td class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
            &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/losangeles/unclejohns.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
            &lt;div class=&quot;overlayblogphotos&quot;&gt;Steak + Eggs&lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;td class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
            &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/losangeles/spicyporkchop.JPG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
            &lt;div class=&quot;overlayblogphotos&quot;&gt;Spicy Pork Chops + Chow Mein&lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/td&gt;            
    &lt;/table&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;
        I am a big fan of Buzzfeed's &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL5vtqDuUM1DmXwYYAQcyUwtcalp_SesZD&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Worth It&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; series, a show that compares a food dish at three different price points to determine which one is the most worth it for its price, hosted by Steven Lim and Andrew Ilnyckyj. For their steak episode, the one at the lowest price point of $12 was &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://unclejohnsdtla.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;Uncle John's Cafe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;'s steak and eggs dish. Uncle John's is an American-Chinese diner that serves up your favorite diner classics, like hot cakes and French toast, but also mixing up your egg dishes with chashu BBQ pork and honey garlic chicken wings. It's like a super fun, diner-centric American-Chinese takeout restaurant. Obviously, I had to try the affordable steak that was greatly loved by both Steven and Andrew!
    &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;
        I tried their famous $12 steak and eggs * that's served with your choice of side and toast. I chose mine to go with fried rice, white toast, and sunny-side up eggs, and boy, these portions are HUGE - TOTALLY WORTH IT! The fried rice was very plain, as it seemed like it was only tossed in soy sauce and scallions. The eggs were just how I liked them, with some slight browning on the edges and runny yolks. The steak was a bit chewier, but it was cooked to a great temperature and well-seasoned. 
    &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;
        The real star of Uncle John's is the spicy pork chops. They're lightly fried and really pack a punch of flavor. The chops have a slight kick, but are also really well-seasoned. My dad got the pork chops with a side of chow mein, which we all really enjoyed. I'd say that this place is a great place if you're looking for a cheap meal with a whole lot of food. Uncle John's also trades in their diner classics for Cajun seafood at night, which I will definitely be trying the next time I come back to visit!
    &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;h6&gt;
    * &lt;em&gt;The price of the steak and eggs has slowly gone up due to the increasing popularity, so I've seen on Yelp that
        it's now around $14. 
    &lt;/em&gt;
    &lt;/h6&gt;
    &lt;h5&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mussoandfrankgrill.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;
    Musso &amp;amp; Frank Grill&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot; text-align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/losangeles/mussoandfrank.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;singleimage&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;
            Ribeyes, Mac &amp;amp; Cheese, Lamb Chops, Sauteed Onions
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;
        I know Hollywood is pretty much a place that most locals want to avoid, but I was on a mission to find a good steakhouse! After doing some light research, I stumbled upon &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mussoandfrankgrill.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;Musso &amp;amp; Frank Grill&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, the oldest restaurant in Hollywood since its opening in 1919. The restaurant has an extensive menu that covers all your favorite steakhouse classics and is also super old-school and is pretty dark-lit. When my family eats steak, we like to eat ribeye, so we got one bone-in and one boneless. Both had very defined grill marks and were each very flavorful, but sadly, the portions were really small for the price, which was disappointing. We also got the French-cut lamb chops, which paired well with the mint jelly on the side. We also got some sauteed onions and mac &amp;amp; cheese, which are my go-to steakhouse sides. Overall, I really did enjoy the meal and loved the setting that gives you an idea of what it was like 100 years ago, but the portions were smaller than expected. I would recommend Musso &amp;amp; Frank as one to try if you're in Hollywood!
    &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;h5&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theosawa.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;
    Osawa Pasadena&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot; text-align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/losangeles/salmonlover.JPG&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;singleimage&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;
            Salmon Lover Sushi Roll
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theosawa.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;Osawa Pasadena&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; is an authentic Japanese restaurant in Pasadena that not only serves up your standard sushi and sashimi, but also hot dishes that aren't frequently seen in Japanese restaurants across America. My dad and sister ordered the chef's choice sashimi lunch, which I was able to try and see how fresh the fish was. We also tried the kurobota pork ginger, which definitely had a more subtle flavor. The pork worked really well with the slaw on the side and is a dish that I definitely recommend! I also had the salmon lover roll, which had fresh AND cooked salmon incorporated into the roll - the name itself should tell you that this roll is for salmon lovers!! Osawa also has shabu counter, which my sister indulges in for special occasions. I look forward to being able to try that in the future!
    &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;h5&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.aftersicecream.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;Afters Ice Cream&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot; text-align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/losangeles/aftersicecream.JPG&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;singleimage&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;
            Triple Scoop!
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.aftersicecream.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;Afters Ice Cream&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; has 27 (and counting!) SoCal locations and is famous for their MilkyBun, a warm donut stuffed with ice cream and toppings of your choice. I don't believe that Afters is a franchise, so all locations are quality-controlled and should be consistent. The Pasadena location is styled as a gas-station and gives off a retro feeling that oddly fits so well with ice cream. My dad always gets a triple scoop that the three of us split, as it's a lot cheaper to get a triple scoop than three individual singles. We tried their Jasmine milk tea, cookie butter, and Vietnamese coffee flavors, which were happy to find that their tastes matched their names. Afters doesn't use artificial flavorings, so each taste was true to their promised flavors. We also tried their MilkyBun, which was just as good as a donut-ice cream pair sounds (amazing 😋).
    &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;h5&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.onezo.us/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;OneZo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot; text-align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/losangeles/onezo.JPG&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;singleimage&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;
            Brown Sugar Boba
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;
        Something remarkable to me is how bubble tea shops in L.A. are not just the regular global franchises, like Kung Fu Tea, Gong Cha, CoCo, etc., but rather smaller localized chains or mom and pop shops. On the East Coast, bubble tea shops are almost purely these chains, with very few small businesses completely specializing in bubble tea. &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.onezo.us/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;OneZo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; has expanded more, even opening up a location in Manhattan, but OneZo is unique as it creates its boba pearls from scratch, meaning there are no additives or artificial flavorings. They're able to control the product from start to finish, which makes you feel a little bit better about drinking bubble tea. They claim to be the world's first bubble tea brand to serve made-in-house fresh boba, which is certainly difficult to find. I got the brown sugar boba milk, which had perfectly chewy tapioca pearls coated in a sticky brown sugar mixture. This place has many locations throughout California and is slowly making its way throughout the U.S.. OneZo is an absolute MUST-TRY!
    &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;h5&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.factoryteabar.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;Factory Tea Bar&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot; text-align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/losangeles/ftb.JPG&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;singleimage&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;
            Strawberry Green Tea with Boba Pearls and Lychee Jelly (ft. Antonia)
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.factoryteabar.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;Factory Tea Bar&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; (FTB) is a popular boba tea spot located in San Gabriel, with an additional location at USC. This is one of my sister's favorite spots to get boba tea, so she took us to the San Gabriel location when visiting. Immediately upon arrival, we noticed that the place was bustling with people. There were people playing board games and just sitting on the couch, and this was around 9:30PM! We ordered our drinks, which took about 10 minutes to prepare, but the wait was worth it! The boba pearls were as chewy as we liked. FTB also serves classic Asian snack foods, like popcorn chicken, fried gyoza, sweet potato fries, &amp;amp; more, and they also have an extensive drink menu with lots of topping options.                       
    &lt;/p&gt;          
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;button id=&quot;showcalifoods&quot; class=&quot;showmorephotosbutton&quot; onclick=&quot;toggleCaliFoods()&quot;&gt;( + ) show me the food!&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;Places:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;div id=&quot;caliplaces&quot;&gt;
    &lt;h5&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://sanpedro.com/san-pedro-area-points-interest/korean-bell-friendship/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Korean Friendship Bell&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
    &lt;table class=&quot;home&quot;&gt;
        &lt;td class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
            &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/losangeles/koreanfriendship.JPG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;td class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
            &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/losangeles/kfbview.JPG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;td class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
            &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/losangeles/palmtreesunset.JPG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;/td&gt;                        
    &lt;/table&gt;          
    &lt;p&gt;
        The &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://sanpedro.com/san-pedro-area-points-interest/korean-bell-friendship/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Korean Friendship Bell&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; is a bell and pavilion located in San Pedro, next to Long Beach. The bell was donated by the Republic of Korea in 1976 to signify the strong friendship between the U.S. and Korea, as well as to honor the Korean War Veterans. The patterns of the bell are modeled after the Bronze Bell of King Songdok that was built in 771 A.D. and is still on display today. The pavilion was stunning, as you are able to go up close and see the intricate design of the bell. It is set with a background view of Long Beach, and you are even able to see Los Angeles from afar. It is a little bit of a drive from Downtown L.A. but it is a must-see in my opinion!         
    &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;h5&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://downtownla.com/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Downtown L.A.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot; text-align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/losangeles/dtla.JPG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;singleimage&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;
        This is really the high-rise, typical city part of L.A., where you can find art galleries, markets, Little Tokyo, Chinatown, and lots more. Because of our limited time there, we really just window-shopped, &quot;people watched&quot;, walked through the Japanese Village Plaza, and checked out Little Tokyo. There are endless things to find in DTLA, as it has great wall art and lots of areas to do some light flea-market shopping + walking.        
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;button id=&quot;showcaliplaces&quot; class=&quot;showmorephotosbutton&quot; onclick=&quot;toggleCaliPlaces()&quot;&gt;( + ) show me where to go!&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the rest of the time, we did some sightseeing, like seeing the Queen Mary Ship, a cruise ship that my dad and sister went on about 15 years ago, as well as visiting the Museum of Selfies, seeing Antonia’s school, and exploring Pasadena and its surrounding areas. We definitely had a packed 3 days, where we enjoyed some of the best food and saw a few beautiful sights in L.A.. I cannot wait till my next time in L.A., because I clearly have lots more to see in what this huge city has to offer!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot; text-align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/losangeles/queenmary.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;singleimage&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;
    At the Queen Mary Ship 🚢
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="beyond" /><summary type="html">~ Long Beach Views ~ WELCOME TO THE CITY OF ANGELS! Having lived in the same place my whole life on the East Coast, I had always been interested in life on the West Coast. New York City is a very fast city - everyone is always on the move and in a rush. Los Angeles is what some might consider NYC’s polar opposite. As die-hard New Yorkers say, if the only thing you can say about your city is that the weather is good, the city probably just isn’t that good. SoCal is known for its warmer weather throughout the year, but there’s so much more to this wonderful city than just the weather. L.A. goes at a slower pace than NYC, giving it a more relaxed feel. But, with both cities, there are great things and some not-so-fantastic things. NYC is a city made to be explored through public transportation and by foot, especially given Manhattan’s smart grid design. You pretty much need a car to get around, which means the notorious L.A. traffic. However, my sister says the public transportation isn’t as terrible as people say it is, but…NYC definitely wins in that one. Between the two, my winner is… actually L.A.!! Many will disagree, but L.A. is such an inviting, exciting city that has endless free activities to enjoy and a food scene that I personally love more. Don’t get me wrong, NYC is an absolute food paradise, but I guess my taste buds are just happier in the L.A. sunshine ☀️. Also, my mom spent a few years in California when she first immigrated to the U.S., so maybe it’s just in my blood? So my older sister, Antonia, actually goes to college in the L.A. area, so for Thanksgiving 2018, my dad and I went to spend time with her. We were only able to explore L.A. for about three days, so we didn’t get to see a whole lot, but that can be a good thing - L.A. keeps me coming back for more, and that means that I have something to look forward to the next time I return. Check out the places I ate and visited during my Thanksgiving trip! We went all over L.A. metro area, including San Gabriel Valley, Long Beach, Hollywood, Little Tokyo, and more, so it’ll definitely be a drive around! The Destinations Foods: Chinchikurin GOAM - Green Onions and Mayo Eating at Chinchikurin was my first time trying okonomiyaki. Since then, this dish has been one of my all-time favorites! They serve Hiroshima okonomiyaki, which is one of two main styles of okonomiyaki. Okonomiyaki is a savory pancake with okonomi- meaning &quot;as you like&quot; and -yaki meaning &quot;cooked&quot;. Osaka style is a batter with all ingredients being mixed inside, whereas each ingredient in the Hiroshima style is separated into its own layer, allowing each layer to provide its own unique taste + texture. There's typically 11 (WOW!) layers, with grilled noodles, vegetables, crepe-like batter, meat, and many more. Chinchikurin offers 9 ways to eat your Hiroshima okonomiyaki, and each way has its own specific toppings. My family tried 3 ways, as each pancake can be eaten as a single portion. We shared the GOAM (pictured above), which is green onions and mayo, the B&amp;amp;C, or the basil &amp;amp; cheese, and the Chinchikurinyaki, which has the shioburiyaki ground beef mixture inside. All okonomiyakis served have &quot;The Classic&quot; as their base, which can be ordered plain without toppings. However, the toppings make these pancakes even more exciting! It's such a fun experience to eat here, as you're able to use the &quot;hera&quot; (miniature spatula) to cut into the okonomiyaki that's sitting utop a heated grill. Get the B&amp;amp;C if you like cheese - it was my favorite!! Chinchikurin also has a takoyaki window if you just want a quick snack walking through Little Tokyo! I absolutely love this place. Uncle John's Cafe Steak + Eggs Spicy Pork Chops + Chow Mein I am a big fan of Buzzfeed's Worth It series, a show that compares a food dish at three different price points to determine which one is the most worth it for its price, hosted by Steven Lim and Andrew Ilnyckyj. For their steak episode, the one at the lowest price point of $12 was Uncle John's Cafe's steak and eggs dish. Uncle John's is an American-Chinese diner that serves up your favorite diner classics, like hot cakes and French toast, but also mixing up your egg dishes with chashu BBQ pork and honey garlic chicken wings. It's like a super fun, diner-centric American-Chinese takeout restaurant. Obviously, I had to try the affordable steak that was greatly loved by both Steven and Andrew! I tried their famous $12 steak and eggs * that's served with your choice of side and toast. I chose mine to go with fried rice, white toast, and sunny-side up eggs, and boy, these portions are HUGE - TOTALLY WORTH IT! The fried rice was very plain, as it seemed like it was only tossed in soy sauce and scallions. The eggs were just how I liked them, with some slight browning on the edges and runny yolks. The steak was a bit chewier, but it was cooked to a great temperature and well-seasoned. The real star of Uncle John's is the spicy pork chops. They're lightly fried and really pack a punch of flavor. The chops have a slight kick, but are also really well-seasoned. My dad got the pork chops with a side of chow mein, which we all really enjoyed. I'd say that this place is a great place if you're looking for a cheap meal with a whole lot of food. Uncle John's also trades in their diner classics for Cajun seafood at night, which I will definitely be trying the next time I come back to visit! * The price of the steak and eggs has slowly gone up due to the increasing popularity, so I've seen on Yelp that it's now around $14. Musso &amp;amp; Frank Grill Ribeyes, Mac &amp;amp; Cheese, Lamb Chops, Sauteed Onions I know Hollywood is pretty much a place that most locals want to avoid, but I was on a mission to find a good steakhouse! After doing some light research, I stumbled upon Musso &amp;amp; Frank Grill, the oldest restaurant in Hollywood since its opening in 1919. The restaurant has an extensive menu that covers all your favorite steakhouse classics and is also super old-school and is pretty dark-lit. When my family eats steak, we like to eat ribeye, so we got one bone-in and one boneless. Both had very defined grill marks and were each very flavorful, but sadly, the portions were really small for the price, which was disappointing. We also got the French-cut lamb chops, which paired well with the mint jelly on the side. We also got some sauteed onions and mac &amp;amp; cheese, which are my go-to steakhouse sides. Overall, I really did enjoy the meal and loved the setting that gives you an idea of what it was like 100 years ago, but the portions were smaller than expected. I would recommend Musso &amp;amp; Frank as one to try if you're in Hollywood! Osawa Pasadena Salmon Lover Sushi Roll Osawa Pasadena is an authentic Japanese restaurant in Pasadena that not only serves up your standard sushi and sashimi, but also hot dishes that aren't frequently seen in Japanese restaurants across America. My dad and sister ordered the chef's choice sashimi lunch, which I was able to try and see how fresh the fish was. We also tried the kurobota pork ginger, which definitely had a more subtle flavor. The pork worked really well with the slaw on the side and is a dish that I definitely recommend! I also had the salmon lover roll, which had fresh AND cooked salmon incorporated into the roll - the name itself should tell you that this roll is for salmon lovers!! Osawa also has shabu counter, which my sister indulges in for special occasions. I look forward to being able to try that in the future! Afters Ice Cream Triple Scoop! Afters Ice Cream has 27 (and counting!) SoCal locations and is famous for their MilkyBun, a warm donut stuffed with ice cream and toppings of your choice. I don't believe that Afters is a franchise, so all locations are quality-controlled and should be consistent. The Pasadena location is styled as a gas-station and gives off a retro feeling that oddly fits so well with ice cream. My dad always gets a triple scoop that the three of us split, as it's a lot cheaper to get a triple scoop than three individual singles. We tried their Jasmine milk tea, cookie butter, and Vietnamese coffee flavors, which were happy to find that their tastes matched their names. Afters doesn't use artificial flavorings, so each taste was true to their promised flavors. We also tried their MilkyBun, which was just as good as a donut-ice cream pair sounds (amazing 😋). OneZo Brown Sugar Boba Something remarkable to me is how bubble tea shops in L.A. are not just the regular global franchises, like Kung Fu Tea, Gong Cha, CoCo, etc., but rather smaller localized chains or mom and pop shops. On the East Coast, bubble tea shops are almost purely these chains, with very few small businesses completely specializing in bubble tea. OneZo has expanded more, even opening up a location in Manhattan, but OneZo is unique as it creates its boba pearls from scratch, meaning there are no additives or artificial flavorings. They're able to control the product from start to finish, which makes you feel a little bit better about drinking bubble tea. They claim to be the world's first bubble tea brand to serve made-in-house fresh boba, which is certainly difficult to find. I got the brown sugar boba milk, which had perfectly chewy tapioca pearls coated in a sticky brown sugar mixture. This place has many locations throughout California and is slowly making its way throughout the U.S.. OneZo is an absolute MUST-TRY! Factory Tea Bar Strawberry Green Tea with Boba Pearls and Lychee Jelly (ft. Antonia) Factory Tea Bar (FTB) is a popular boba tea spot located in San Gabriel, with an additional location at USC. This is one of my sister's favorite spots to get boba tea, so she took us to the San Gabriel location when visiting. Immediately upon arrival, we noticed that the place was bustling with people. There were people playing board games and just sitting on the couch, and this was around 9:30PM! We ordered our drinks, which took about 10 minutes to prepare, but the wait was worth it! The boba pearls were as chewy as we liked. FTB also serves classic Asian snack foods, like popcorn chicken, fried gyoza, sweet potato fries, &amp;amp; more, and they also have an extensive drink menu with lots of topping options. ( + ) show me the food! Places: Korean Friendship Bell The Korean Friendship Bell is a bell and pavilion located in San Pedro, next to Long Beach. The bell was donated by the Republic of Korea in 1976 to signify the strong friendship between the U.S. and Korea, as well as to honor the Korean War Veterans. The patterns of the bell are modeled after the Bronze Bell of King Songdok that was built in 771 A.D. and is still on display today. The pavilion was stunning, as you are able to go up close and see the intricate design of the bell. It is set with a background view of Long Beach, and you are even able to see Los Angeles from afar. It is a little bit of a drive from Downtown L.A. but it is a must-see in my opinion! Downtown L.A. This is really the high-rise, typical city part of L.A., where you can find art galleries, markets, Little Tokyo, Chinatown, and lots more. Because of our limited time there, we really just window-shopped, &quot;people watched&quot;, walked through the Japanese Village Plaza, and checked out Little Tokyo. There are endless things to find in DTLA, as it has great wall art and lots of areas to do some light flea-market shopping + walking. ( + ) show me where to go! For the rest of the time, we did some sightseeing, like seeing the Queen Mary Ship, a cruise ship that my dad and sister went on about 15 years ago, as well as visiting the Museum of Selfies, seeing Antonia’s school, and exploring Pasadena and its surrounding areas. We definitely had a packed 3 days, where we enjoyed some of the best food and saw a few beautiful sights in L.A.. I cannot wait till my next time in L.A., because I clearly have lots more to see in what this huge city has to offer! At the Queen Mary Ship 🚢</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">New Orleans</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/beyond/2020/06/01/nola.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="New Orleans" /><published>2020-06-01T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2020-06-01T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/beyond/2020/06/01/nola</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/beyond/2020/06/01/nola.html">&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot; text-align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images//beyond/nola/bourbonst.JPG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;singleimage&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;Bourbon Street&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome to The Big Easy, a city full of jazz, crazy good food, and of course, Mardi Gras! New Orleans (NOLA) is truly a city like no other. Yes, every city has its own unique charms, but NOLA has a distinctive, one-of-a-kind style and such a vibrant scene with endless things to do. New Orleans has high-rise buildings, but no one thinks of New Orleans with the high-rise reputation that NYC has. NOLA is in the Gulf Coast region, which means fresh seafood and maybe even a ~steamboat tour~ if you’d like (we did not, but you definitely can!).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m so ready to share some restaurants I found in the exciting and multicultural food scene of New Orleans. This city is known for its Creole cuisine and French influences, but is also popular for its Vietnamese food, which makes sense, as both Louisiana and Vietnamese food are lightly French-inspired amongst many other influences. Scroll down below to check out the eats of this lively city!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-destinations&quot;&gt;The Destinations&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;Foods:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;div id=&quot;nolafoods&quot;&gt;
    &lt;h5&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.maypoprestaurant.com/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Maypop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
    &lt;table class=&quot;home&quot;&gt;
        &lt;td class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
            &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images//beyond/nola/bonemarrowfullimage.JPG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
            &lt;div class=&quot;overlayblogphotos&quot;&gt;
            Bone Marrow Dish
            &lt;/div&gt;  
        &lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;td class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
            &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images//beyond/nola/bluecrabnoodles.JPG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
            &lt;div class=&quot;overlayblogphotos&quot;&gt;
            Hand-Pulled Blue Crab Mapo Tofu Noodles
            &lt;/div&gt;  
        &lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/table&gt;          
    &lt;p&gt;
        New Orleans was actually a half-way on a very lengthy road trip that began in Florida and would conclude back at home in New Jersey. So after a few hour long car ride from Miramar Beach, our first stop was at &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.maypoprestaurant.com/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Maypop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, a Southeast Asian-inspired, contemporary Louisiana restaurant (I know, a mouthful). The restaurant has a classy feel, but it is still casual enough to walk in for a fun, enjoyable brunch, lunch, or dinner.
    &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;
        Bone marrow is a very luxury item, and it's definitely not an easy dish to do well. I will say, I've never had a bad bone marrow dish in my life - the buttery and fatty inside is irresistible! This bone marrow is likely the best bone marrow dish I've had. It's topped with oxtail, sweet, caramelized onions, and gravy juices. It had such a complex, umami flavor that paired amazingly with the naan. I'm sure the dish has evolved a bit since I went, but I have no doubt that it's still just as good. We also tried the blue crab mapo tofu hand-pulled noodles, which was every bit as exciting as it sounds. The noodles had a great chew, and the sauce was slightly spiced, but definitely nothing too overwhelming. They also gave us these curry beignets as a starter, which is just about the best replacement for free restaurant bread you can get. 
    &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;h5&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dickiebrennanssteakhouse.com/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Dickie Brennan's Steakhouse&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
    &lt;table class=&quot;home&quot;&gt;
        &lt;td class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
            &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images//beyond/nola/dbsteak.JPG&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
            &lt;div class=&quot;overlayblogphotos&quot;&gt;
            Prime Cowboy Ribeye
            &lt;/div&gt;  
        &lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;td class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
            &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images//beyond/nola/cornbrulee.JPG&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
            &lt;div class=&quot;overlayblogphotos&quot;&gt;
            Corn Brûlée
            &lt;/div&gt;  
        &lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/table&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dickiebrennanssteakhouse.com/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Dickie Brennan's Steakhouse&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; is an award-winning classic steakhouse, but with a Creole twist. The steak was tasty, as expected, but it was made 100000x better by the Creole butter it was topped with! Definitely get the corn brulee too - this brûléed, sweet, but a little savory, silky corn pudding is the perfect accompaniment to your steak. This restaurant is perfect for special occasions, but it is also very packed, so I'd be sure to get a reservation!            
    &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;h5&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://frenchmarketrestaurant.com/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;The Original French Market Restaurant and Bar&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot; text-align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images//beyond/nola/bbqshrimpgrits.JPG&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;singleimage&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;
            BBQ Shrimp + Grits
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;
        After walking through the French Quarter for an afternoon, we did a quick search through Google Maps to stumble upon &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://frenchmarketrestaurant.com/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;The Original French Market Restaurant and Bar&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, a family-owned Creole kitchen that prides themselves on making everything from scratch. We tried their raw oysters on the half shell, BBQ shrimp and grits (pictured above), jambalaya, and the Louisiana crab cakes that are smothered in a crawfish cream sauce. The restaurant is in a great location, and it serves up a taste of New Orleans that feels comforting in this bustling city. 
    &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;h5&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://shop.cafedumonde.com/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Café du Monde&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot; text-align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images//beyond/nola/cafedumonde.JPG&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;singleimage&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;
            Classic Beignets
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;
        Arguably the most famous foodie destination of NOLA, &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://shop.cafedumonde.com/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Café du Monde&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; serves up beignets and several variations of café au lait. Did you even go to NOLA if you didn't eat a beignet?!
    &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;
        Café du Monde has been doing their beignets since 1862, 24 hours a day (except Christmas day). These light and airy pockets of dough topped with mountains of powdered sugar are an irresistible treat. I was only in NOLA for two days, so I only had the opportunity to try beignets once, which was at Café du Monde, so I'm not &lt;em&gt;actually&lt;/em&gt; sure where the best beignets are! I was extremely happy after trying Café du Monde's beignets, so I would highly recommend it anyways 😊.
    &lt;/p&gt;                    
    &lt;h5&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://willajean.com/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Willa Jean&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot; text-align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images//beyond/nola/willajean.JPG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;singleimage&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;
            Cookies + Milk
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://willajean.com/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Willa Jean&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; is a Southern-style restaurant named after Chef Partner Kelly Fields’ grandmother. I went after our meal at Maypop to get their famous chocolate chip cookies and milk combination, which I shared with my sister. The cookies weren't extremely special in terms of taste, but they were perfectly soft and had a good amount of chocolate. I enjoyed their Tahitian vanilla milk as well. The retro-chic restaurant/café was still busy even at ~9PM (not sure if eating late is just a New Orleans cultural thing), and it is well-reviewed online for their food. Since I only had the cookies, I can't say much about anything else, except that the decor of the place is very aesthetic!
    &lt;/p&gt;                                
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;button id=&quot;shownolafoods&quot; class=&quot;showmorephotosbutton&quot; onclick=&quot;toggleNolaFoods()&quot;&gt;( + ) show me the food!&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Places:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;div id=&quot;nolaplaces&quot;&gt;
    &lt;h5&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.neworleans.com/plan/streets/bourbon-street/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bourbon Street / French Quarter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
    &lt;table class=&quot;home&quot;&gt;
        &lt;td class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
            &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images//beyond/nola/nolarooftop.JPG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;td class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
            &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images//beyond/nola/nolastview.JPG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;/td&gt;            
    &lt;/table&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;
        The &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.neworleans.com/plan/streets/bourbon-street/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;French Quarter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; is the heart of New Orleans and one of the famous neighborhoods in America. You can find colorful buildings, Cajun food, and an endless assortment of activities here. There's jazz music playing throughout the streets, and you definitely won't be bored wherever you walk. The thirteen-block Bourbon Street has lots of nightlife for adults and is a whole street of celebration &amp;amp; joy.         
    &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;h5&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.neworleans.com/plan/neighborhoods/uptown-garden-district/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Garden District&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
    &lt;table class=&quot;home&quot;&gt;
        &lt;td class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
            &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images//beyond/nola/gardendistrict.JPG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;td class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
            &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images//beyond/nola/gardendistrict2.JPG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;td class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
            &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images//beyond/nola/gardendistrict3.JPG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/table&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;
        The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.neworleans.com/plan/neighborhoods/uptown-garden-district/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Garden District&lt;/a&gt; is a lovely neighborhood and somewhat peaceful getaway from the lively French Quarter. Its streets are lined with oak trees and is filled with a large variety of homes, ranging from charming cottages to impressive multistory mansions, as well as stunning lush gardens to see. There are boutique shops and small cafés located in the district available to visit too.          
    &lt;/p&gt; 
    &lt;h5&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.stlouiscathedral.org/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Saint Louis Cathedral&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
    &lt;table class=&quot;home&quot;&gt;
        &lt;td class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
            &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images//beyond/nola/stlouiscathedral.JPG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;td class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
            &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images//beyond/nola/nolaxmas.JPG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/table&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.stlouiscathedral.org/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Saint Louis Cathedral&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, the oldest cathedral in North America*, is one of New Orleans' most famous landmarks. Despite its old age, this cathedral is still well-preserved, as its triple steeples still shine nicely, and the building itself is still so purely clean. Upon the arrival Adrien De Pauger of France on 3/29/1721, the cathedral began its construction alongside Engineer-in-Chief of Louisiana, LeBlond de la Tour. The Cathedral-Basilica has been in use since 1727 and is named after King of France, Louis IX. The cathedral sits right by the Mississippi River and is conveniently located in the French Quarter, making this historic, beautiful sight difficult to miss.
    &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;h6&gt;* according to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.stlouiscathedral.org/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;www.stlouiscathedral.org&lt;/a&gt;; above information is 
    provided from the Saint Louis Cathedral official website. &lt;/h6&gt;                                
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;button id=&quot;shownolaplaces&quot; class=&quot;showmorephotosbutton&quot; onclick=&quot;toggleNolaPlaces()&quot;&gt;( + ) show me where to go!&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being a self-proclaimed foodie, I have always wanted to visit New Orleans for its one-of-a-kind culture and uniquely diverse cuisine, and our road trip back to New Jersey allowed for it to be a perfect stop. My trip, while short, did not disappoint, as I got to eat my heart out and experience a small taste of what NOLA is like. Life here is like an exciting, all-day party, and I’d love to return someday!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="beyond" /><summary type="html">Bourbon Street Welcome to The Big Easy, a city full of jazz, crazy good food, and of course, Mardi Gras! New Orleans (NOLA) is truly a city like no other. Yes, every city has its own unique charms, but NOLA has a distinctive, one-of-a-kind style and such a vibrant scene with endless things to do. New Orleans has high-rise buildings, but no one thinks of New Orleans with the high-rise reputation that NYC has. NOLA is in the Gulf Coast region, which means fresh seafood and maybe even a ~steamboat tour~ if you’d like (we did not, but you definitely can!). I’m so ready to share some restaurants I found in the exciting and multicultural food scene of New Orleans. This city is known for its Creole cuisine and French influences, but is also popular for its Vietnamese food, which makes sense, as both Louisiana and Vietnamese food are lightly French-inspired amongst many other influences. Scroll down below to check out the eats of this lively city! The Destinations Foods: Maypop Bone Marrow Dish Hand-Pulled Blue Crab Mapo Tofu Noodles New Orleans was actually a half-way on a very lengthy road trip that began in Florida and would conclude back at home in New Jersey. So after a few hour long car ride from Miramar Beach, our first stop was at Maypop, a Southeast Asian-inspired, contemporary Louisiana restaurant (I know, a mouthful). The restaurant has a classy feel, but it is still casual enough to walk in for a fun, enjoyable brunch, lunch, or dinner. Bone marrow is a very luxury item, and it's definitely not an easy dish to do well. I will say, I've never had a bad bone marrow dish in my life - the buttery and fatty inside is irresistible! This bone marrow is likely the best bone marrow dish I've had. It's topped with oxtail, sweet, caramelized onions, and gravy juices. It had such a complex, umami flavor that paired amazingly with the naan. I'm sure the dish has evolved a bit since I went, but I have no doubt that it's still just as good. We also tried the blue crab mapo tofu hand-pulled noodles, which was every bit as exciting as it sounds. The noodles had a great chew, and the sauce was slightly spiced, but definitely nothing too overwhelming. They also gave us these curry beignets as a starter, which is just about the best replacement for free restaurant bread you can get. Dickie Brennan's Steakhouse Prime Cowboy Ribeye Corn Brûlée Dickie Brennan's Steakhouse is an award-winning classic steakhouse, but with a Creole twist. The steak was tasty, as expected, but it was made 100000x better by the Creole butter it was topped with! Definitely get the corn brulee too - this brûléed, sweet, but a little savory, silky corn pudding is the perfect accompaniment to your steak. This restaurant is perfect for special occasions, but it is also very packed, so I'd be sure to get a reservation! The Original French Market Restaurant and Bar BBQ Shrimp + Grits After walking through the French Quarter for an afternoon, we did a quick search through Google Maps to stumble upon The Original French Market Restaurant and Bar, a family-owned Creole kitchen that prides themselves on making everything from scratch. We tried their raw oysters on the half shell, BBQ shrimp and grits (pictured above), jambalaya, and the Louisiana crab cakes that are smothered in a crawfish cream sauce. The restaurant is in a great location, and it serves up a taste of New Orleans that feels comforting in this bustling city. Café du Monde Classic Beignets Arguably the most famous foodie destination of NOLA, Café du Monde serves up beignets and several variations of café au lait. Did you even go to NOLA if you didn't eat a beignet?! Café du Monde has been doing their beignets since 1862, 24 hours a day (except Christmas day). These light and airy pockets of dough topped with mountains of powdered sugar are an irresistible treat. I was only in NOLA for two days, so I only had the opportunity to try beignets once, which was at Café du Monde, so I'm not actually sure where the best beignets are! I was extremely happy after trying Café du Monde's beignets, so I would highly recommend it anyways 😊. Willa Jean Cookies + Milk Willa Jean is a Southern-style restaurant named after Chef Partner Kelly Fields’ grandmother. I went after our meal at Maypop to get their famous chocolate chip cookies and milk combination, which I shared with my sister. The cookies weren't extremely special in terms of taste, but they were perfectly soft and had a good amount of chocolate. I enjoyed their Tahitian vanilla milk as well. The retro-chic restaurant/café was still busy even at ~9PM (not sure if eating late is just a New Orleans cultural thing), and it is well-reviewed online for their food. Since I only had the cookies, I can't say much about anything else, except that the decor of the place is very aesthetic! ( + ) show me the food! Places: Bourbon Street / French Quarter The French Quarter is the heart of New Orleans and one of the famous neighborhoods in America. You can find colorful buildings, Cajun food, and an endless assortment of activities here. There's jazz music playing throughout the streets, and you definitely won't be bored wherever you walk. The thirteen-block Bourbon Street has lots of nightlife for adults and is a whole street of celebration &amp;amp; joy. Garden District The Garden District is a lovely neighborhood and somewhat peaceful getaway from the lively French Quarter. Its streets are lined with oak trees and is filled with a large variety of homes, ranging from charming cottages to impressive multistory mansions, as well as stunning lush gardens to see. There are boutique shops and small cafés located in the district available to visit too. Saint Louis Cathedral Saint Louis Cathedral, the oldest cathedral in North America*, is one of New Orleans' most famous landmarks. Despite its old age, this cathedral is still well-preserved, as its triple steeples still shine nicely, and the building itself is still so purely clean. Upon the arrival Adrien De Pauger of France on 3/29/1721, the cathedral began its construction alongside Engineer-in-Chief of Louisiana, LeBlond de la Tour. The Cathedral-Basilica has been in use since 1727 and is named after King of France, Louis IX. The cathedral sits right by the Mississippi River and is conveniently located in the French Quarter, making this historic, beautiful sight difficult to miss. * according to www.stlouiscathedral.org; above information is provided from the Saint Louis Cathedral official website. ( + ) show me where to go! Being a self-proclaimed foodie, I have always wanted to visit New Orleans for its one-of-a-kind culture and uniquely diverse cuisine, and our road trip back to New Jersey allowed for it to be a perfect stop. My trip, while short, did not disappoint, as I got to eat my heart out and experience a small taste of what NOLA is like. Life here is like an exciting, all-day party, and I’d love to return someday!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Menya Sandaime</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jerseyeats/2019/12/10/menya.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Menya Sandaime" /><published>2019-12-10T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-12-10T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jerseyeats/2019/12/10/menya</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jerseyeats/2019/12/10/menya.html">&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot; text-align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/jerseyeats/menyasandaime/menya.JPG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;singleimage&quot; /&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before I start, I have to say that I would eat the noodles at Menya Sandaime every day, if I could.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to their website, they continue to use a traditional Japanese recipe that has been passed through three generations. Their Tokyo-style broth takes over 12 hours to prepare, and they make their noodles in-house. Seriously, you can even see the room where they make their noodles in their 1st Fort Lee location! With their quality and time-intensive ingredients, this restaurant is dangerously tempting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot; text-align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/jerseyeats/menyasandaime/menyaramen.jpg&quot; height=&quot;200px&quot; class=&quot;singleimage&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;2 Tonkotsu Ramens&lt;/div&gt;  
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The pork broth here is so fatty and indulgent, and pairs so well with their housemade noodles. I’ve tried their &lt;strong&gt;tonkotsu&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;black ramen&lt;/strong&gt; dishes, which both have a tonkotsu broth base. The difference between these two dishes is that the black ramen has the addition of a smoky seafood flavor. For those who might be scared off by this, it’s really not that fishy, and I actually like this addition a lot. My favorite between these two is the &lt;strong&gt;original tonkotsu&lt;/strong&gt;, but you can’t go wrong with either. If you like some spice, their karakuchi ramen has the spicy version of the tonkotsu ramen. These are the three ramen options that are topped with bean sprouts, scallions, spinach, marinated egg, &amp;amp; grilled pork belly. The tonkotsu ramen is $9.50 at the Fort Lee locations, while the black and karakuchi ramen are $10.50.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now I’d like to talk about my favorite dish here - the &lt;strong&gt;tsukemen&lt;/strong&gt; ($11). Tsukemen is a ramen variation* where the noodles are plated separately from the broth. These dipping noodles are slowly gaining popularity in the U.S., but you might be wondering - it sounds just like deconstructed ramen, so why am I paying $1.50 more to get ramen plated separately?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;-tsukemen-is-very-different-from-ramen-and-should-be-eaten-by-dipping-a-small-portion-of-noodles-into-the-broth-the-noodles-should-not-be-poured-directly-into-the-broth&quot;&gt;* &lt;em&gt;Tsukemen is very different from ramen and should be eaten by dipping a small portion of noodles into the broth. The noodles should not be poured directly into the broth!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot; text-align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/jerseyeats/menyasandaime/menya2.JPG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;singleimage&quot; /&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What separates tsukemen from traditional ramen are 1. their noodles and 2. the broth. I prefer the tsukemen noodles that are comparably thicker and chewier than the tonkotsu ramen noodles. The tsukemen broth is slightly thicker than the tonkotsu broth, which makes sense for the noodles to absorb more broth. The tsukemen broth is a very similar broth base to the black ramen, which comes with a smoky seafood flavor as well. However, the tsukemen broth comes with small chunks of onions and pork, which pairs really well with the noodles. The tsukemen noodles are topped with bean sprouts, scallions, spinach, marinated egg, &amp;amp; grilled pork belly (it comes with one extra piece than the ramen😊).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;tsukemen-is-perfect-for-the-summer-too-as-the-noodles-arent-soaking-in-a-hot-broth&quot;&gt;Tsukemen is perfect for the summer too, as the noodles aren’t soaking in a hot broth.&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Their pork is unbelievably tasty - it’s perfectly fatty and slightly charred. Pork belly is one of the integral components of a ramen dish, and I’d say that you can usually judge how good a ramen place is by their pork. If you don’t like red meat, they also offer a shrimp option to substitute the pork, which my dad once ordered in addition to to the pork belly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot; text-align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/jerseyeats/menyasandaime/tonkotsumenyashirmp.jpg&quot; height=&quot;200px&quot; class=&quot;singleimage&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;Tonkotsu Ramens - (Top) Shrimp + Pork Belly&lt;/div&gt;  
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Menya also offers amazing &lt;strong&gt;gyoza&lt;/strong&gt; ($5.60), or Japanese pan-fried dumplings, which a framed newspaper on their wall claims is the best. Dumplings are different EVERYWHERE you get them, and Menya’s gyoza certainly do not disappoint! As you can see, they have a thin crispy sheet that connects all these dumplings together, which is probably created by pouring a small amount of water + starch into the pan; this allows for an added crisp that elevates the already existing flavor of the meat filling. I’d say these are a must-have side to your noodles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot; text-align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/jerseyeats/menyasandaime/menyagyoza.jpg&quot; height=&quot;200px&quot; class=&quot;singleimage&quot; /&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Menya opened a second Fort Lee location off Bergen Boulevard that offers specialty items not sold at their original location, such as chicken kara-age, pork buns, chicken teriyaki &amp;amp; grilled pork belly dons (rice bowls), as well as an extended list of noodle add-ons. I’ve only tried the &lt;strong&gt;pork buns&lt;/strong&gt; (1/$3, 2/$5), which I honestly didn’t have high expectations for. Not because I doubted how good the pork would be, but because I didn’t know how worth it the buns would be, since they use the same pork belly in the ramen. However, I was very pleasantly surprised by these buns - they blew my expectations out of the water! Somehow, the pork reimagined in the bao bun was a totally different, yet still as indulgent, experience than the ramen dishes. The buns are slathered in spicy mayo and topped with scallions, which were a refreshing complement to the charred pork belly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot; text-align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/jerseyeats/menyasandaime/menyabuns.jpg&quot; height=&quot;200px&quot; class=&quot;singleimage&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m not too adventurous when I come here, as I usually get the same dishes every time, but I have complete confidence that all their dishes are just as amazing as the ones I routinely eat. Ramen can cost $20+ in Manhattan, and Menya’s pricing is unbeatable. If I go to the city with my dad, we typically stop by Menya on our way home, instead of eating overpriced and under-delivering noodles. These warming and filling noodles are the greatest meal on a snowy winter night, but somehow also on a warm summer day. I cannot stress how extraordinary these noodles are!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table class=&quot;home&quot;&gt;
    &lt;td class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/jerseyeats/menyasandaime/menya3.jpg&quot; height=&quot;200px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt; 
    &lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;td class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/jerseyeats/menyasandaime/takeoutmenya.JPG&quot; height=&quot;200px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;/td&gt; 
&lt;/table&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="jerseyeats" /><summary type="html">Before I start, I have to say that I would eat the noodles at Menya Sandaime every day, if I could. According to their website, they continue to use a traditional Japanese recipe that has been passed through three generations. Their Tokyo-style broth takes over 12 hours to prepare, and they make their noodles in-house. Seriously, you can even see the room where they make their noodles in their 1st Fort Lee location! With their quality and time-intensive ingredients, this restaurant is dangerously tempting. 2 Tonkotsu Ramens The pork broth here is so fatty and indulgent, and pairs so well with their housemade noodles. I’ve tried their tonkotsu and black ramen dishes, which both have a tonkotsu broth base. The difference between these two dishes is that the black ramen has the addition of a smoky seafood flavor. For those who might be scared off by this, it’s really not that fishy, and I actually like this addition a lot. My favorite between these two is the original tonkotsu, but you can’t go wrong with either. If you like some spice, their karakuchi ramen has the spicy version of the tonkotsu ramen. These are the three ramen options that are topped with bean sprouts, scallions, spinach, marinated egg, &amp;amp; grilled pork belly. The tonkotsu ramen is $9.50 at the Fort Lee locations, while the black and karakuchi ramen are $10.50. Now I’d like to talk about my favorite dish here - the tsukemen ($11). Tsukemen is a ramen variation* where the noodles are plated separately from the broth. These dipping noodles are slowly gaining popularity in the U.S., but you might be wondering - it sounds just like deconstructed ramen, so why am I paying $1.50 more to get ramen plated separately? * Tsukemen is very different from ramen and should be eaten by dipping a small portion of noodles into the broth. The noodles should not be poured directly into the broth! What separates tsukemen from traditional ramen are 1. their noodles and 2. the broth. I prefer the tsukemen noodles that are comparably thicker and chewier than the tonkotsu ramen noodles. The tsukemen broth is slightly thicker than the tonkotsu broth, which makes sense for the noodles to absorb more broth. The tsukemen broth is a very similar broth base to the black ramen, which comes with a smoky seafood flavor as well. However, the tsukemen broth comes with small chunks of onions and pork, which pairs really well with the noodles. The tsukemen noodles are topped with bean sprouts, scallions, spinach, marinated egg, &amp;amp; grilled pork belly (it comes with one extra piece than the ramen😊). Tsukemen is perfect for the summer too, as the noodles aren’t soaking in a hot broth. Their pork is unbelievably tasty - it’s perfectly fatty and slightly charred. Pork belly is one of the integral components of a ramen dish, and I’d say that you can usually judge how good a ramen place is by their pork. If you don’t like red meat, they also offer a shrimp option to substitute the pork, which my dad once ordered in addition to to the pork belly. Tonkotsu Ramens - (Top) Shrimp + Pork Belly Menya also offers amazing gyoza ($5.60), or Japanese pan-fried dumplings, which a framed newspaper on their wall claims is the best. Dumplings are different EVERYWHERE you get them, and Menya’s gyoza certainly do not disappoint! As you can see, they have a thin crispy sheet that connects all these dumplings together, which is probably created by pouring a small amount of water + starch into the pan; this allows for an added crisp that elevates the already existing flavor of the meat filling. I’d say these are a must-have side to your noodles. Menya opened a second Fort Lee location off Bergen Boulevard that offers specialty items not sold at their original location, such as chicken kara-age, pork buns, chicken teriyaki &amp;amp; grilled pork belly dons (rice bowls), as well as an extended list of noodle add-ons. I’ve only tried the pork buns (1/$3, 2/$5), which I honestly didn’t have high expectations for. Not because I doubted how good the pork would be, but because I didn’t know how worth it the buns would be, since they use the same pork belly in the ramen. However, I was very pleasantly surprised by these buns - they blew my expectations out of the water! Somehow, the pork reimagined in the bao bun was a totally different, yet still as indulgent, experience than the ramen dishes. The buns are slathered in spicy mayo and topped with scallions, which were a refreshing complement to the charred pork belly. I’m not too adventurous when I come here, as I usually get the same dishes every time, but I have complete confidence that all their dishes are just as amazing as the ones I routinely eat. Ramen can cost $20+ in Manhattan, and Menya’s pricing is unbeatable. If I go to the city with my dad, we typically stop by Menya on our way home, instead of eating overpriced and under-delivering noodles. These warming and filling noodles are the greatest meal on a snowy winter night, but somehow also on a warm summer day. I cannot stress how extraordinary these noodles are!!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Katsune Donkatsu Café</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jerseyeats/2019/12/09/katsune.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Katsune Donkatsu Café" /><published>2019-12-09T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-12-09T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jerseyeats/2019/12/09/katsune</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jerseyeats/2019/12/09/katsune.html">&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot; text-align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/jerseyeats/katsune/katsucover.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;singleimage&quot; /&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://katsuneusa.business.site/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Katsune Donkatsu Café&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; is a modest counter-serve café setting decorated only by picnic-patterned tables. Katsu is a popular Japanese/Korean deep fried panko breaded meat cutlet served with “Bull Dog” tonkatsu sauce, a Japanese sauce sweetened with fruit and vegetables.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Katsune is one of the few Bergen County restaurants totally dedicated to katsu-style dishes, and they’ve mastered it. The restaurant has lengthier and flatter panko breadcrumbs that make their katsu flakier than all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The café serves up the standard pork donkatsu, as well as the famous &lt;strong&gt;cheese “Cordon Bleu” donkatsu&lt;/strong&gt; (pork - &lt;em&gt;pictured below&lt;/em&gt;), chicken, ebi (shrimp), beef and pork patty (menchi) katsu dishes. They also serve up a “Wang Donkatsu”, a much larger, even crispier, pounded flat donkatsu. A side of made-in-house curry can be added to all dishes too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Their cheese donkatsu comes with a generous stuffing of mozzarella cheese that makes for the picture-perfect cheese pull. Katsune also keeps their pork tenderloin so juicy after frying, something that’s difficult to accomplish in deep-fried meat dishes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot; text-align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/jerseyeats/katsune/katsune.jpg&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;singleimage&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;Pork Cordon Bleu (Cheese Donkatsu)&lt;/div&gt;  
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All dishes are served with a side of steamed white rice, corn, Japanese-style coleslaw, and soy sauce pickles. They are also accompanied by the standard “Bull Dog” tonkatsu sauce, as well as a homemade banana sauce that’s surprisingly addictive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The unassuming exterior of the restaurant might not bring you in right away, but the flakiest katsu in Bergen County (maybe even in the NYC area…) makes this a place you’ll regret not eating at. Katsune Donkatsu for the win!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="jerseyeats" /><summary type="html">Katsune Donkatsu Café is a modest counter-serve café setting decorated only by picnic-patterned tables. Katsu is a popular Japanese/Korean deep fried panko breaded meat cutlet served with “Bull Dog” tonkatsu sauce, a Japanese sauce sweetened with fruit and vegetables. Katsune is one of the few Bergen County restaurants totally dedicated to katsu-style dishes, and they’ve mastered it. The restaurant has lengthier and flatter panko breadcrumbs that make their katsu flakier than all. The café serves up the standard pork donkatsu, as well as the famous cheese “Cordon Bleu” donkatsu (pork - pictured below), chicken, ebi (shrimp), beef and pork patty (menchi) katsu dishes. They also serve up a “Wang Donkatsu”, a much larger, even crispier, pounded flat donkatsu. A side of made-in-house curry can be added to all dishes too. Their cheese donkatsu comes with a generous stuffing of mozzarella cheese that makes for the picture-perfect cheese pull. Katsune also keeps their pork tenderloin so juicy after frying, something that’s difficult to accomplish in deep-fried meat dishes. Pork Cordon Bleu (Cheese Donkatsu) All dishes are served with a side of steamed white rice, corn, Japanese-style coleslaw, and soy sauce pickles. They are also accompanied by the standard “Bull Dog” tonkatsu sauce, as well as a homemade banana sauce that’s surprisingly addictive. The unassuming exterior of the restaurant might not bring you in right away, but the flakiest katsu in Bergen County (maybe even in the NYC area…) makes this a place you’ll regret not eating at. Katsune Donkatsu for the win!</summary></entry></feed>