<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-08-02T17:57:23-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">CarissaEats</title><subtitle>A food and travel blog by @CarissaEats, where I share my favorite small businesses, easy recipes, and travel adventures.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Noodles.</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/stories/noodles" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Noodles." /><published>2021-08-02T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2021-08-02T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/stories/noodles</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/stories/noodles">&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/stories/noodle/jersey/mitsuwa.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;Santouka Ramen&lt;/div&gt;    
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yup, you read that right. Noodles. In virtually every culture, an iconic noodle dish exists – Italian &lt;em&gt;pasta&lt;/em&gt;, Japanese &lt;em&gt;udon&lt;/em&gt;, Korean &lt;em&gt;japchae&lt;/em&gt;, Jewish &lt;em&gt;kugel&lt;/em&gt;, Singaporean &lt;em&gt;laksa&lt;/em&gt;, Filipino &lt;em&gt;pancit&lt;/em&gt;, Dominican &lt;em&gt;espaguetis&lt;/em&gt; – you get the point. So where did this versatile ingredient / base originate? What was the catalyst for its widespread popularity? How are noodles the foundation to many fusion cuisines? How can plant-based eaters enjoy this dish that’s typically accompanied by meat? And then I’m excited to share my dream noodle list.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you don’t know I love noodles, &lt;em&gt;udon know me&lt;/em&gt;. Be prepared for all the noodle puns I could think of (and find online).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;origins&quot;&gt;🌟Origins&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;popularization&quot;&gt;📈Popularization&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;role-in-fusion-cuisine&quot;&gt;🌏Role in Fusion Cuisine&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to The Spruce Eats &lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:1&quot; role=&quot;doc-noteref&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:1&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot; rel=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;, people imported Chinese and Indian populations to the Caribbean.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hapamag.com/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Hapa Mag&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, “a collaborative publication by hapas, for everyone,” offers a multitude of perspectives on what it means to be “Hapa”, a term coined for those of multiracial, specifically Asian, descent. We absolutely try to put everyone in a box, but not everyone identifies with just a single box and that’s perfect. One article I found particularly enlightening, in the context of Chinese-Caribbean culture, was &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hapamag.com/issue-008/2019/6/3/the-chinese-part-is-the-jamaican-part&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;The Chinese Part *Is* The Jamaican Part&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, which discusses the&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;plant-based&quot;&gt;🥦Plant-Based&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;dream-noodle-list&quot;&gt;💭Dream Noodle List&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;sources&quot;&gt;Sources:&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot; role=&quot;doc-endnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:1&quot; role=&quot;doc-endnote&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.thespruceeats.com/chinese-cultural-influences-on-caribbean-cuisine-2137727&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Chinese Cultural Influences on Modern Caribbean Cuisine&lt;/a&gt; by Hector Rodriguez &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:1&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot; role=&quot;doc-backlink&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="stories" /><summary type="html">Santouka Ramen Yup, you read that right. Noodles. In virtually every culture, an iconic noodle dish exists – Italian pasta, Japanese udon, Korean japchae, Jewish kugel, Singaporean laksa, Filipino pancit, Dominican espaguetis – you get the point. So where did this versatile ingredient / base originate? What was the catalyst for its widespread popularity? How are noodles the foundation to many fusion cuisines? How can plant-based eaters enjoy this dish that’s typically accompanied by meat? And then I’m excited to share my dream noodle list. If you don’t know I love noodles, udon know me. Be prepared for all the noodle puns I could think of (and find online). 🌟Origins 📈Popularization 🌏Role in Fusion Cuisine According to The Spruce Eats 1, people imported Chinese and Indian populations to the Caribbean. Hapa Mag, “a collaborative publication by hapas, for everyone,” offers a multitude of perspectives on what it means to be “Hapa”, a term coined for those of multiracial, specifically Asian, descent. We absolutely try to put everyone in a box, but not everyone identifies with just a single box and that’s perfect. One article I found particularly enlightening, in the context of Chinese-Caribbean culture, was The Chinese Part *Is* The Jamaican Part, which discusses the 🥦Plant-Based 💭Dream Noodle List Sources: Chinese Cultural Influences on Modern Caribbean Cuisine by Hector Rodriguez &amp;#8617;</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/stories/noodle/jersey/mitsuwa.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/stories/noodle/jersey/mitsuwa.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Life Update</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/stories/life-update-1" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Life Update" /><published>2021-04-21T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2021-04-21T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/stories/life-update-1</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/stories/life-update-1">&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/stories/doufuhuavectorart.png&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;  
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hey everyone! So I’ve been pretty MIA on here and on Instagram, so I just wanted to keep you all updated on where I’ve been.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I do have a lot on my mind, regarding where I’m at and what I want to do, so bear with me while I explain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;First thing&lt;/strong&gt;: I’m moving. I’ll be going to college next year, but my dad is also moving! I’ve lived in [redacted town, out of an abundance of caution] my entire life, and it’s rather bittersweet to move. On one hand, I’ve always felt safe living in my house, which has been a huge privilege to have. This town is the only place I’ve ever known as “home”, which is a true luxury that many people yearn for. While my sister and I took our daily walk the other day, I began reminiscing on all of the staples in my town: the multitude of pizza shops, the (now-closed) cookware store, the diner, among many others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And then, there’s the “sweet” part of moving: I would love a fresh start. My family was actually supposed to move three years ago, but those plans fell through. My family went through a big loss nearly five years ago, and the house sometimes feels like a never-ending reminder of that loss and all events leading up to it. Plus, the opportunity to have a fresh start feels more appealing than ever, since the last year has felt very stagnant due to the pandemic – which is absolutely not a terrible thing – but to have the ability to move by choice is exciting. We’ll be heading to &lt;strong&gt;Orlando&lt;/strong&gt;, which I can only imagine will be a bit of a culture shock. Although I don’t live in the most diverse place, I’m still surrounded by a lot of people who look like me. We’ll be living in a suburb in the Orlando metro area, so it’ll just be a peaceful summer at a new home. So &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.publix.com/shop-online/in-store-pickup&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Publix&lt;/a&gt;, here I come!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We could be moving in just a couple weeks, so packing time has commenced! Packing the home you’ve lived in for 17 years is bound to have 17 years worth of stuff (x4 for everyone who lives here), and we are &lt;em&gt;that&lt;/em&gt; hoarding family. I would love to spend my free time working on this blog, but until we get up out of this house, most of my time will go to packing. On top of school, I’ve been a little more stressed than usual, but we just have to keep going. July and August will be months of weekly blogging at the minimum, though, I promise!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Next thing&lt;/strong&gt;: I have a lot of content in mind – three articles unlike anything I’ve ever posted! Restaurant recommendations and a few stories make up most of my content here, but I’m ecstatic to write the following pieces, some of which delve into identity and culture. Here’s a little tease for each one:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Noodles&lt;/strong&gt;: Noodles are popular in a multitude of cultures. Where did this versatile ingredient / base originate? What was the catalyst for its widespread popularity? How are noodles the foundation to many fusion (intercultural) cuisines? How can plant-based eaters enjoy this dish that’s typically accompanied by meat? And then I’m excited to share my dream noodle list.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More Than Sesame Chicken&lt;/strong&gt;: BIPOC are often flattened to their ethnic identity in the food industry (and beyond), whereas their white peers are allowed to venture into any cuisine they want. “More Than Sesame Chicken” discusses my Chinese-American experience and how that impacts my love for food in America. I’ll also dispel the melting pot myth and talk a bit about what it means to be Asian in America.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bro-Ritos Taco Kit&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.broritosfoodtruck.com/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bro-Ritos Food Truck&lt;/a&gt; (flagship in Hackensack) launched a taco kit in early February 2021. The taco kit consists of their signature “Red Salt”, 12 tortillas, and their taco hot (or mild) sauce. Y’all, that Red Salt is really just out of this world. I still have a little left, but only because we want to savor it forever. This taco kit gives you all the directions to making a taco with different proteins – I’ll show how I made them with shrimp in this post. I would 10000000% recommend anyone who &lt;em&gt;can&lt;/em&gt; buy this kit to &lt;a href=&quot;https://broritosfoodtruck.square.site/product/tacokit/46?cs=true&amp;amp;cst=custom&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;buy it&lt;/a&gt;. The “Red Salt” veers on the sweet side, which I prefer anyway, but my taste buds were dancing after trying this salt.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Those are just some of the things I wanted to share with y’all today, since I haven’t been posting much lately. I have exciting projects to come, so I appreciate your patience 😊&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="stories" /><summary type="html">Hey everyone! So I’ve been pretty MIA on here and on Instagram, so I just wanted to keep you all updated on where I’ve been. I do have a lot on my mind, regarding where I’m at and what I want to do, so bear with me while I explain. First thing: I’m moving. I’ll be going to college next year, but my dad is also moving! I’ve lived in [redacted town, out of an abundance of caution] my entire life, and it’s rather bittersweet to move. On one hand, I’ve always felt safe living in my house, which has been a huge privilege to have. This town is the only place I’ve ever known as “home”, which is a true luxury that many people yearn for. While my sister and I took our daily walk the other day, I began reminiscing on all of the staples in my town: the multitude of pizza shops, the (now-closed) cookware store, the diner, among many others. And then, there’s the “sweet” part of moving: I would love a fresh start. My family was actually supposed to move three years ago, but those plans fell through. My family went through a big loss nearly five years ago, and the house sometimes feels like a never-ending reminder of that loss and all events leading up to it. Plus, the opportunity to have a fresh start feels more appealing than ever, since the last year has felt very stagnant due to the pandemic – which is absolutely not a terrible thing – but to have the ability to move by choice is exciting. We’ll be heading to Orlando, which I can only imagine will be a bit of a culture shock. Although I don’t live in the most diverse place, I’m still surrounded by a lot of people who look like me. We’ll be living in a suburb in the Orlando metro area, so it’ll just be a peaceful summer at a new home. So Publix, here I come! We could be moving in just a couple weeks, so packing time has commenced! Packing the home you’ve lived in for 17 years is bound to have 17 years worth of stuff (x4 for everyone who lives here), and we are that hoarding family. I would love to spend my free time working on this blog, but until we get up out of this house, most of my time will go to packing. On top of school, I’ve been a little more stressed than usual, but we just have to keep going. July and August will be months of weekly blogging at the minimum, though, I promise! Next thing: I have a lot of content in mind – three articles unlike anything I’ve ever posted! Restaurant recommendations and a few stories make up most of my content here, but I’m ecstatic to write the following pieces, some of which delve into identity and culture. Here’s a little tease for each one: Noodles: Noodles are popular in a multitude of cultures. Where did this versatile ingredient / base originate? What was the catalyst for its widespread popularity? How are noodles the foundation to many fusion (intercultural) cuisines? How can plant-based eaters enjoy this dish that’s typically accompanied by meat? And then I’m excited to share my dream noodle list. More Than Sesame Chicken: BIPOC are often flattened to their ethnic identity in the food industry (and beyond), whereas their white peers are allowed to venture into any cuisine they want. “More Than Sesame Chicken” discusses my Chinese-American experience and how that impacts my love for food in America. I’ll also dispel the melting pot myth and talk a bit about what it means to be Asian in America. Bro-Ritos Taco Kit: Bro-Ritos Food Truck (flagship in Hackensack) launched a taco kit in early February 2021. The taco kit consists of their signature “Red Salt”, 12 tortillas, and their taco hot (or mild) sauce. Y’all, that Red Salt is really just out of this world. I still have a little left, but only because we want to savor it forever. This taco kit gives you all the directions to making a taco with different proteins – I’ll show how I made them with shrimp in this post. I would 10000000% recommend anyone who can buy this kit to buy it. The “Red Salt” veers on the sweet side, which I prefer anyway, but my taste buds were dancing after trying this salt. Those are just some of the things I wanted to share with y’all today, since I haven’t been posting much lately. I have exciting projects to come, so I appreciate your patience 😊</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/stories/doufuhuavectorart.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/stories/doufuhuavectorart.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Recipe Spotlights #1</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/recipes/recipe-spotlights-1" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Recipe Spotlights #1" /><published>2021-02-24T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2021-02-24T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/recipes/recipe-spotlights-1</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/recipes/recipe-spotlights-1">&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/recipes/spotlights/recipespotlights.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome to my new recipe series, where I’m highlighting BIPOC creatives in the food industry!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This first release of the BIPOC Recipe Series spotlights Black recipe creators. I chose mostly independent creatives, because independent creatives have complete control over their narratives, meaning they are Black stories told by Black people. So without further ado, here are five Black recipe creators and food storytelling communities comprised of Black voices!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://jikoni.co/recipes/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Jikoni&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: Jikoni means kitchen in Swahili. According to their website, Jikoni focuses on African culture and people, as African cuisine and stories are underrepresented in the culinary world. By looking through the lens of cuisine, people can learn about culture. “All roads to lead to Africa” for Jikoni.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc8n9VxRO2ei45mXzZAJluA/videos&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Lady of Q&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: Sylvie Curry of &lt;em&gt;The American Barbecue Showdown&lt;/em&gt; often used Asian-inspired flavors in their barbecue, but their range of cuisines spans all around the world. Sylvie may be a barbecue pitmaster, but that doesn’t stop them from crafting mouth-watering, non-BBQ recipes like the &lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/4FHmPPgP6MA&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Alaskan Seafood Feasts&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/DRN3Iyw9O1o&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Korean Crispy Corn Dogs&lt;/a&gt;. Their YouTube channel has content discussing their time and how they got on the show, but also recipes from well before their TV show stint. Sylvie deserves all the subscribers and fans, so be sure to hit the subscribe button!&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://meikoandthedish.com/tag/recipe/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Meiko and The Dish&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: Meiko Temple spent time in a Corporate America career of marketing and design, but ultimately, they found their passion in food. And what better way to combine design and culinary skills (along with a love for food!) than this beautiful blog! Meiko’s personal favorites are listed on the &lt;a href=&quot;https://meikoandthedish.com/about-meiko/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;About&lt;/a&gt; page, and the recipes are colorful, creative, and culinary delights (re: &lt;a href=&quot;https://meikoandthedish.com/pink-spaghetti-beet-pesto/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Pink Spaghetti&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;https://meikoandthedish.com/elote-corn-chowder/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Elote Corn Chowder&lt;/a&gt;)!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;-vegan-or-plant-forward&quot;&gt;🌱 Vegan (or Plant-Forward)&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.baumassfoods.com/category/recipes/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;baumassfoods&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: Hilaire Baumgartner follows a mostly vegan diet (“zero meat (even fish), very limited dairy, and very little egg”, according to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.baumassfoods.com/about/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;About&lt;/a&gt; page). Hilaire is making “bomb-ass, plant-forward food” and is showing the world that a plant-based lifestyle, if accessible, is as enjoyable as (if not better and more sustainable than) one with meat. I mean, are you &lt;em&gt;kidding&lt;/em&gt; me with these &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.baumassfoods.com/triple-chocolate-pistachio-cookies/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;triple chocolate pistachio cookies&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.baumassfoods.com/bbq-jackfruit-bean-bowls-with-cornbread-croutons-and-coleslaw/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;bbq jackfruit bean bowls with cornbread croutons and coleslaw&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.baumassfoods.com/20-minute-creamy-skillet-lasagna/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;skillet lasagna&lt;/a&gt;?! Warning: You may want to eat your screen after scrolling through their recipe feed. After all, Hilaire &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; a commercial food photographer in addition to running this blog, so the stunning visuals should come as no surprise.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cocoverdevegan.com/food-blog&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;coco verde vegan&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: The Rodriguez Flores family is cooking up various plant-based foods and Latinx vegan dishes. They are Afro-Dominican and are passionate about food, welfare and social justice. Their Instagram captions are in both English and Spanish. Their Instagram feed pops of color, but also consists of heart-warming family photos.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;ways-to-support-bipoc-bloggers&quot;&gt;Ways to Support BIPOC Bloggers:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Many sites are supported by ads. If you use an ad blocker, please turn it off or remove it. If you see any ads that appeal to you (and look safe), click on them, as this may help the creatives get that revenue.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Just show them some ❤️. Hit that follow button if you feel like you identify with their mission. Drive their Instagram engagement up by &lt;strong&gt;saving&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;sharing&lt;/strong&gt;, or any other interactions. Followers aren’t always the goal, but enthusiastic and dedicated members of their Instagram communities are. Subscribe, like, and comment on YouTube channels, if they have them!&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sign up for their Recipe Newsletters (typically a lightbox that appears on the screen or on the bottom).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;If their website has them, leave a review &lt;em&gt;if&lt;/em&gt; you try their recipes &lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt; love them.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;supporting-blogs-doesnt-seem-like-it-means-much-but-black-indigenous-and-people-of-color-are-underrepresented-in-creative-spaces-uplifting-the-bipoc-voices-that-do-exist-also-creates-more-space-for-future-creatives-to-leave-their-mark-bipoc-stories-are-beautiful-diverse-and-meaningful--remember-that-the-bipoc-community-isnt-a-monolith-and-sub-communities-face-different-experiences&quot;&gt;Supporting blogs doesn’t seem like it means much, but Black, Indigenous, and People of Color are underrepresented in creative spaces. Uplifting the BIPOC voices that do exist also creates more space for future creatives to leave their mark. BIPOC stories are beautiful, diverse, and meaningful – remember that the BIPOC community isn’t a monolith and sub-communities face different experiences.&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;-to-be-copyright-conscious-i-didnt-include-any-photos-from-their-blogs&quot;&gt;* To be copyright conscious, I didn’t include any photos from their blogs.&lt;/h6&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="recipes" /><summary type="html">Welcome to my new recipe series, where I’m highlighting BIPOC creatives in the food industry! This first release of the BIPOC Recipe Series spotlights Black recipe creators. I chose mostly independent creatives, because independent creatives have complete control over their narratives, meaning they are Black stories told by Black people. So without further ado, here are five Black recipe creators and food storytelling communities comprised of Black voices! Jikoni: Jikoni means kitchen in Swahili. According to their website, Jikoni focuses on African culture and people, as African cuisine and stories are underrepresented in the culinary world. By looking through the lens of cuisine, people can learn about culture. “All roads to lead to Africa” for Jikoni. Lady of Q: Sylvie Curry of The American Barbecue Showdown often used Asian-inspired flavors in their barbecue, but their range of cuisines spans all around the world. Sylvie may be a barbecue pitmaster, but that doesn’t stop them from crafting mouth-watering, non-BBQ recipes like the Alaskan Seafood Feasts and Korean Crispy Corn Dogs. Their YouTube channel has content discussing their time and how they got on the show, but also recipes from well before their TV show stint. Sylvie deserves all the subscribers and fans, so be sure to hit the subscribe button! Meiko and The Dish: Meiko Temple spent time in a Corporate America career of marketing and design, but ultimately, they found their passion in food. And what better way to combine design and culinary skills (along with a love for food!) than this beautiful blog! Meiko’s personal favorites are listed on the About page, and the recipes are colorful, creative, and culinary delights (re: Pink Spaghetti or Elote Corn Chowder)! 🌱 Vegan (or Plant-Forward) baumassfoods: Hilaire Baumgartner follows a mostly vegan diet (“zero meat (even fish), very limited dairy, and very little egg”, according to the About page). Hilaire is making “bomb-ass, plant-forward food” and is showing the world that a plant-based lifestyle, if accessible, is as enjoyable as (if not better and more sustainable than) one with meat. I mean, are you kidding me with these triple chocolate pistachio cookies, bbq jackfruit bean bowls with cornbread croutons and coleslaw, and skillet lasagna?! Warning: You may want to eat your screen after scrolling through their recipe feed. After all, Hilaire is a commercial food photographer in addition to running this blog, so the stunning visuals should come as no surprise. coco verde vegan: The Rodriguez Flores family is cooking up various plant-based foods and Latinx vegan dishes. They are Afro-Dominican and are passionate about food, welfare and social justice. Their Instagram captions are in both English and Spanish. Their Instagram feed pops of color, but also consists of heart-warming family photos. Ways to Support BIPOC Bloggers: Many sites are supported by ads. If you use an ad blocker, please turn it off or remove it. If you see any ads that appeal to you (and look safe), click on them, as this may help the creatives get that revenue. Just show them some ❤️. Hit that follow button if you feel like you identify with their mission. Drive their Instagram engagement up by saving, sharing, or any other interactions. Followers aren’t always the goal, but enthusiastic and dedicated members of their Instagram communities are. Subscribe, like, and comment on YouTube channels, if they have them! Sign up for their Recipe Newsletters (typically a lightbox that appears on the screen or on the bottom). If their website has them, leave a review if you try their recipes and love them. Supporting blogs doesn’t seem like it means much, but Black, Indigenous, and People of Color are underrepresented in creative spaces. Uplifting the BIPOC voices that do exist also creates more space for future creatives to leave their mark. BIPOC stories are beautiful, diverse, and meaningful – remember that the BIPOC community isn’t a monolith and sub-communities face different experiences. * To be copyright conscious, I didn’t include any photos from their blogs.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/recipes/spotlights/recipespotlights.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/recipes/spotlights/recipespotlights.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Who Wants A Pita Me? 🥙</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/recipes/pitaplatter" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Who Wants A Pita Me? 🥙" /><published>2021-02-17T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2021-02-17T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/recipes/pitaplatter</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/recipes/pitaplatter">&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/recipes/platter/platter3.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Humm&lt;/em&gt;-us where the heart is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I get a little carried away with the puns during recipe posts, so bear with me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My family had some pantry stuff we wanted to consume right away, so I came up with the idea to make a three-ish piece platter, with homemade pita, eggs in purgatory (kinda), and avocado hummus!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These recipes are by no-means authentic – however, they are inspired by the meals I had in Tel Aviv, where the food is very veggie-centric and extraordinarily fresh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first recipe will be &lt;strong&gt;eggs in purgatory&lt;/strong&gt;, akin to the North African &lt;em&gt;shakshuka&lt;/em&gt;. Eggs in purgatory is called Uova in Purgatorio, but &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.savoringitaly.com/eggs-in-purgatory-uova-in-purgatorio/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;the name may vary depending on the region of Italy&lt;/a&gt;. The eggs are “souls” seeking purification in the red-hot tomato sauce of purgatory. I struggled to find a formal history on this dish on the internet. I was able to find a bit about shakshuka, although I couldn’t find any sources by a chef of Tunisian (Tunisia is said to be &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.themediterraneandish.com/shakshuka-recipe/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;its place of origin&lt;/a&gt;) descent, so I didn’t want to include anything from an “untrustworthy” source. But a little tidbit I can include is that shakshuka is supposedly “&lt;a href=&quot;https://momentmag.com/talk-of-the-table-shakshuka/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;an onomatopoeia for ‘all mixed up’&lt;/a&gt;”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, let’s eat!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;eggs-in-purgatory&quot;&gt;Eggs in Purgatory:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;div id=&quot;recipe1&quot;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;*Adapted from &lt;a href=&quot;https://addapinch.com/eggs-purgatory-recipe/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;Add A Pinch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ingredients&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;2 tomatoes (I used one large and one medium)&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;2 tsp garlic oil (olive oil works great too!)&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;¼ cup tomato/marinara sauce&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;4-5 eggs (depending on what you want the egg-to-sauce ratio to be)&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;salt + pepper to taste&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;red pepper flakes&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;¼ red or white onion (optional, if your tomato sauce doesn’t have a lot of onions)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ul&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Dice your tomatoes into ½ to ¾ inch thick pieces. &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Pour the oil and place your diced tomatoes and onions (if you want) into the pan.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Cook your tomatoes over medium-low heat for about 20 minutes, stirring occasionally. &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Your tomatoes should release quite a bit of water. Fear not -- your tomato sauce probably has tomato paste, which will help thicken your base quite a bit. &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Add your tomato sauce to the “stewed” tomatoes. Continue cooking over medium-low heat for 4 minutes. &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Season with salt and pepper generously. &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Use a spatula or spoon to create little “wells” where the eggs can sit in.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Crack the eggs into the well and cover the skillet. Cook the eggs for about 3-4 minutes, or until the egg whites are completely set. Once the egg yolks are cooked to your desired doneness, pull the skillet off the heat. &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;The egg yolks will continue to cook as it’s off the heat, so pull it off a little bit before you want them to be done.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Cover the skillet and cook until the whites of the eggs are set and the egg yolks are cooked to the desired level of doneness. &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Finish off with as many red pepper flakes as you’re comfortable with.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;

  &lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/recipes/platter/platter1.jpg&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;button id=&quot;showrecipe1&quot; class=&quot;showmorephotosbutton&quot; onclick=&quot;toggleContent('recipe1', 'showrecipe1', '( - ) sounds good, but...next!', '( + ) show me the recipe!')&quot;&gt;( + ) show me the recipe!&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;homemade-pita&quot;&gt;Homemade Pita:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;div id=&quot;recipe2&quot;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;*Adapted from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.themediterraneandish.com/homemade-pita-bread-recipe/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;The Mediterranean Dish&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ingredients&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;½ cup water&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;1 tsp active dry yeast&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;½ tsp sugar&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;1 ½ cup all-purpose flour&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;1 tsp salt&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;3 ½ tbsp garlic oil (olive oil works great too!)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ul&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Pita Sponge&lt;/strong&gt;: Combine the yeast, sugar, ½ cup of water, and ¼ cup of flour in a large mixing bowl. Leave the mixture uncovered for 15 minutes in a warm place. It should be bubbly (but don’t worry if it’s not &lt;em&gt;too&lt;/em&gt; bubbly -- &lt;a href=&quot;/assets/images/recipes/platter/cooking/pitasponge.jpg&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;see mine&lt;/a&gt;!)&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The One-Bowl Wonder&lt;/strong&gt;: Add salt, 2 tbsp oil, and about 1 more cup of flour into the mixture. It should be quite sticky and not look like a perfect dough. Keep adding flour by the tablespoons, but keep the flour to a minimum. &lt;em&gt;However much flour it takes to get the dough to stop sticking to your hands is the perfect amount&lt;/em&gt;. Knead the dough to collect the stray bits into the dough. &lt;a href=&quot;/assets/images/recipes/platter/cooking/middough.jpg&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;Here’s what the dough may look like at this point&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Keep kneading in the bowl or on a floured surface for about 5 minutes. Cover the bowl with a damp towel and let it rest for about 10 minutes. Keep kneading until the bowl is &lt;em&gt;pretty&lt;/em&gt; clean. 1. 1. Pick up the dough and add oil into the bowl. &lt;a href=&quot;/assets/images/recipes/platter/cooking/abouttorest.jpg&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;Place the dough in the bowl and coat lightly in the oil&lt;/a&gt;. Cover the bowl with plastic wrap and place the bowl in a warm place for an hour (or &lt;a href=&quot;/assets/images/recipes/platter/cooking/risendough.jpg&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;until the dough doubles in size&lt;/a&gt;). &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Deflate the dough and then divide the dough into four equal pieces. Shape those four pieces into balls and let them rest for 10 minutes. Cover the dough balls with a damp towel. &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;The technique I saw in several videos was taking the dough balls and tucking the dough from the top to the bottom. See &lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/NPiA69p4gqE?t=170&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;Food Wishes at 2:30&lt;/a&gt; for a visual!&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Flatten the pita dough balls. It should be super elastic, so you don’t even need a rolling pin (I didn’t!) -- just stretch it out in the air with your hands, like it’s a pizza. Stretch the piece until it’s ¼-½ inch thick. &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Heat a skillet with ½ tbsp of oil over medium heat. Drop a water droplet into the skillet, and once it starts to sizzle, you know it’s ready!&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Leave the flattened dough on the skillet for about 1 minute, before flipping it over to cook for another 1-2 minutes on the other side.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How do you know when it’s ready?&lt;/strong&gt; You can just pull it off once the pita puffs up or both sides have nice toasty spots. Not all pitas will puff up, but there’s no need to worry!&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Eat it with &lt;em&gt;anything&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;button id=&quot;showrecipe2&quot; class=&quot;showmorephotosbutton&quot; onclick=&quot;toggleContent('recipe2', 'showrecipe2', '( - ) sounds good, but...next!', '( + ) show me the recipe!')&quot;&gt;( + ) show me the recipe!&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;avocado-hummus&quot;&gt;Avocado Hummus:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;div id=&quot;recipe3&quot;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ingredients&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;2 medium sized avocados&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;15-oz can chickpeas, drained**&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;½ lemon (or ¾ tbsp vinegar)&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;garlic oil &lt;strong&gt;with the garlic intact&lt;/strong&gt;: reserve 2-3 garlic cloves and 3 tbsp of oil&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;salt + pepper to taste&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;aquafaba, only as needed&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;** DO NOT drain the liquid down the sink! It’s aquafaba, so pour it into a bowl -- use aquafaba in &lt;a href=&quot;https://tasty.co/article/whitneyjefferson/aquafaba-the-magic-bean-liquid&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;recipes like these&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Dump all ingredients except the avocados in a food processor or blender. Blend for about 2 minutes, until all the chickpeas are completely broken down. &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Add avocados to the mixture, and blend until creamy. It should take no more than 2 minutes.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Transfer to a bowl and serve immediately. If you do not plan on serving immediately, transfer and cover it in an airtight container. Squeezing lemon over it will preserve its green hue, but the hummus is still edible even if it darkens.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;button id=&quot;showrecipe3&quot; class=&quot;showmorephotosbutton&quot; onclick=&quot;toggleContent('recipe3', 'showrecipe3', '( - ) sounds good, but...next!', '( + ) show me the recipe!')&quot;&gt;( + ) show me the recipe!&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;garlic-oil&quot;&gt;Garlic Oil&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;div id=&quot;recipe4&quot;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ingredients&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;2-3 heads of garlic, cloves peeled.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;1 cup oil&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;I used vegetable oil, but the oil doesn't necessarily need to be neutral. It's up to you if you want the garlic or the oil taste to have the greater presence. &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Oils with lower smoke points can work fine, because you cook the garlic at a low temp!&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ul&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Cook the cloves of garlic in the oil for ~15 minutes. Stir occasionally.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;The garlic should only be &lt;em&gt;very lightly&lt;/em&gt; browned - not even golden brown. &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;button id=&quot;showrecipe4&quot; class=&quot;showmorephotosbutton&quot; onclick=&quot;toggleContent('recipe4', 'showrecipe4', '( - ) sounds good, but...next!', '( + ) show me the recipe!')&quot;&gt;( + ) show me the recipe!&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I used a wooden cutting board to lay out all the components of this meal, but that is by no means necessary. I received this cutting board for “Secret Santa”, so I’m putting it to good use! I added &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foodshouldtastegood.com/product/multigrain&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Food Should Taste Good&lt;/a&gt; Multigrain Tortilla Chips to the platter, and those chips pair well with my avocado hummus or even our Eggs in Purgatory. My dad enjoyed the platter, which made me feel really proud of myself! As a “chef” (honestly calling myself a chef is a little insulting to chefs, but I digress), I appreciate a little validation from others. While my pita, eggs in purgatory, and hummus are nontraditional, they form a cohesive meal altogether.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh, and if you want to make it vegan, just substitute those eggs for some cooked tofu! Every other component is vegan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/recipes/platter/platter2.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="recipes" /><summary type="html">Humm-us where the heart is. I get a little carried away with the puns during recipe posts, so bear with me. My family had some pantry stuff we wanted to consume right away, so I came up with the idea to make a three-ish piece platter, with homemade pita, eggs in purgatory (kinda), and avocado hummus! These recipes are by no-means authentic – however, they are inspired by the meals I had in Tel Aviv, where the food is very veggie-centric and extraordinarily fresh. The first recipe will be eggs in purgatory, akin to the North African shakshuka. Eggs in purgatory is called Uova in Purgatorio, but the name may vary depending on the region of Italy. The eggs are “souls” seeking purification in the red-hot tomato sauce of purgatory. I struggled to find a formal history on this dish on the internet. I was able to find a bit about shakshuka, although I couldn’t find any sources by a chef of Tunisian (Tunisia is said to be its place of origin) descent, so I didn’t want to include anything from an “untrustworthy” source. But a little tidbit I can include is that shakshuka is supposedly “an onomatopoeia for ‘all mixed up’”. Now, let’s eat! Eggs in Purgatory: *Adapted from Add A Pinch Ingredients 2 tomatoes (I used one large and one medium) 2 tsp garlic oil (olive oil works great too!) ¼ cup tomato/marinara sauce 4-5 eggs (depending on what you want the egg-to-sauce ratio to be) salt + pepper to taste red pepper flakes ¼ red or white onion (optional, if your tomato sauce doesn’t have a lot of onions) Directions Dice your tomatoes into ½ to ¾ inch thick pieces. Pour the oil and place your diced tomatoes and onions (if you want) into the pan. Cook your tomatoes over medium-low heat for about 20 minutes, stirring occasionally. Your tomatoes should release quite a bit of water. Fear not -- your tomato sauce probably has tomato paste, which will help thicken your base quite a bit. Add your tomato sauce to the “stewed” tomatoes. Continue cooking over medium-low heat for 4 minutes. Season with salt and pepper generously. Use a spatula or spoon to create little “wells” where the eggs can sit in. Crack the eggs into the well and cover the skillet. Cook the eggs for about 3-4 minutes, or until the egg whites are completely set. Once the egg yolks are cooked to your desired doneness, pull the skillet off the heat. The egg yolks will continue to cook as it’s off the heat, so pull it off a little bit before you want them to be done. Cover the skillet and cook until the whites of the eggs are set and the egg yolks are cooked to the desired level of doneness. Finish off with as many red pepper flakes as you’re comfortable with. ( + ) show me the recipe! Homemade Pita: *Adapted from The Mediterranean Dish Ingredients ½ cup water 1 tsp active dry yeast ½ tsp sugar 1 ½ cup all-purpose flour 1 tsp salt 3 ½ tbsp garlic oil (olive oil works great too!) Directions The Pita Sponge: Combine the yeast, sugar, ½ cup of water, and ¼ cup of flour in a large mixing bowl. Leave the mixture uncovered for 15 minutes in a warm place. It should be bubbly (but don’t worry if it’s not too bubbly -- see mine!) The One-Bowl Wonder: Add salt, 2 tbsp oil, and about 1 more cup of flour into the mixture. It should be quite sticky and not look like a perfect dough. Keep adding flour by the tablespoons, but keep the flour to a minimum. However much flour it takes to get the dough to stop sticking to your hands is the perfect amount. Knead the dough to collect the stray bits into the dough. Here’s what the dough may look like at this point. Keep kneading in the bowl or on a floured surface for about 5 minutes. Cover the bowl with a damp towel and let it rest for about 10 minutes. Keep kneading until the bowl is pretty clean. 1. 1. Pick up the dough and add oil into the bowl. Place the dough in the bowl and coat lightly in the oil. Cover the bowl with plastic wrap and place the bowl in a warm place for an hour (or until the dough doubles in size). Deflate the dough and then divide the dough into four equal pieces. Shape those four pieces into balls and let them rest for 10 minutes. Cover the dough balls with a damp towel. The technique I saw in several videos was taking the dough balls and tucking the dough from the top to the bottom. See Food Wishes at 2:30 for a visual! Flatten the pita dough balls. It should be super elastic, so you don’t even need a rolling pin (I didn’t!) -- just stretch it out in the air with your hands, like it’s a pizza. Stretch the piece until it’s ¼-½ inch thick. Heat a skillet with ½ tbsp of oil over medium heat. Drop a water droplet into the skillet, and once it starts to sizzle, you know it’s ready! Leave the flattened dough on the skillet for about 1 minute, before flipping it over to cook for another 1-2 minutes on the other side. How do you know when it’s ready? You can just pull it off once the pita puffs up or both sides have nice toasty spots. Not all pitas will puff up, but there’s no need to worry! Eat it with anything. ( + ) show me the recipe! Avocado Hummus: Ingredients 2 medium sized avocados 15-oz can chickpeas, drained** ½ lemon (or ¾ tbsp vinegar) garlic oil with the garlic intact: reserve 2-3 garlic cloves and 3 tbsp of oil salt + pepper to taste aquafaba, only as needed ** DO NOT drain the liquid down the sink! It’s aquafaba, so pour it into a bowl -- use aquafaba in recipes like these Directions Dump all ingredients except the avocados in a food processor or blender. Blend for about 2 minutes, until all the chickpeas are completely broken down. Add avocados to the mixture, and blend until creamy. It should take no more than 2 minutes. Transfer to a bowl and serve immediately. If you do not plan on serving immediately, transfer and cover it in an airtight container. Squeezing lemon over it will preserve its green hue, but the hummus is still edible even if it darkens. ( + ) show me the recipe! Garlic Oil Ingredients 2-3 heads of garlic, cloves peeled. 1 cup oil I used vegetable oil, but the oil doesn't necessarily need to be neutral. It's up to you if you want the garlic or the oil taste to have the greater presence. Oils with lower smoke points can work fine, because you cook the garlic at a low temp! Directions Cook the cloves of garlic in the oil for ~15 minutes. Stir occasionally. The garlic should only be very lightly browned - not even golden brown. ( + ) show me the recipe! I used a wooden cutting board to lay out all the components of this meal, but that is by no means necessary. I received this cutting board for “Secret Santa”, so I’m putting it to good use! I added Food Should Taste Good Multigrain Tortilla Chips to the platter, and those chips pair well with my avocado hummus or even our Eggs in Purgatory. My dad enjoyed the platter, which made me feel really proud of myself! As a “chef” (honestly calling myself a chef is a little insulting to chefs, but I digress), I appreciate a little validation from others. While my pita, eggs in purgatory, and hummus are nontraditional, they form a cohesive meal altogether. Oh, and if you want to make it vegan, just substitute those eggs for some cooked tofu! Every other component is vegan.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/recipes/platter/platter3.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/recipes/platter/platter3.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Making Mi-so Happy!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jerseyeats/misoteriyaki" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Making Mi-so Happy!" /><published>2021-01-20T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2021-01-20T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jerseyeats/misoteriyaki</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jerseyeats/misoteriyaki">&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/jerseyeats/miso/misoteriyaki1.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;Beef Teriyaki&lt;/div&gt;    
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Serving up everything from teri buns to Korean-style ramen to mixed tempura, &lt;a href=&quot;http://misoteriyaki.com/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Miso Teriyaki&lt;/a&gt; entered the Bergen County dining scene in March 2020. When I saw a teriyaki restaurant coming to Tenafly, it dawned on me that I haven’t had teriyaki in years. Apparently, it’s the unofficial signature dish of Seattle, which now makes me regret not eating it when I had the opportunity to go there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But alas, Miso arrived and according to their logo, they’re based in Seattle! I don’t know their full story, but I would love to interview them to get the full scoop on their roots and why they decided to bring their West Coast food over to &lt;em&gt;freezing Jersey&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Above, you can see their hand trimmed, char-broiled &lt;strong&gt;beef teriyaki&lt;/strong&gt;, which from some angles, kind of just looks like cooked beef. But wow, it packs a punch! If you love beef bulgogi, you may equally enjoy this. The classic “burnt” flavor is present, but not in an overwhelming way that turns you off – if you’ve ever had East Asian barbecue, you know the sensation! You can tell the marinade is deeply embedded throughout the beef and isn’t just added in the last few minutes of cooking. What an incredible dish!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I believe all the teriyaki dishes come with a small container of their teriyaki sauce, but I personally prefer the meat or “substance” (tofu, shrimp, salmon, etc.) of the dish by itself. Save that little sauce vessel for those huge portions of rice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/jerseyeats/miso/yakisoba.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;Chicken Yakisoba&lt;/div&gt;    
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay, vegetable galore in this noodle dish. The amount of veggies in their &lt;strong&gt;chicken yakisoba&lt;/strong&gt; would be my only criticism, but not for a dislike of veggies!! I enjoy vegetables, but felt there was an imbalance of noodle to vegetable. I found this a bit odd, since restaurants typically try to overload with carbs rather than the more expensive vegetables. I enjoyed the chicken and the noodles, as I’m a huuuuuuge “thick egg-type” noodle fan, as opposed to thinner spaghetti-like types. Note that they cook their noodles a little under al-dente, so if you prefer less chewy noodles, just request them to be “fully cooked”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/jerseyeats/miso/chickenkatsu.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Chicken Katsu&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/jerseyeats/miso/ribteriyaki.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt; 
        &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Rib Teriyaki&lt;/div&gt;  
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t know why, but &lt;strong&gt;chicken katsu&lt;/strong&gt; always hits the spot for me. It’s some part of a chicken covered in panko breadcrumbs, BUT OH MY I just love it. Miso serves a katsu sauce that’s not the traditional &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Bull-Dog-Vegetable-Fruit-Tonkatsu-Bottles/dp/B01N5DB4EW&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bull-Dog Tonkatsu Sauce&lt;/a&gt;. I wasn’t able to catch a photo of the sauce, but dare I say, it was better than the Bull-Dog? I may just be making that up – they could very well be the same. Anyway, Miso’s katsu was thinner than I liked, but that’s simply a preference. The katsu is a great pairing to an assortment of otherwise grilled meats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, to the right of the chicken katsu is the &lt;strong&gt;rib teriyaki&lt;/strong&gt;. It’s the winner of these four dishes for me! The ribs are laterally cut – the same way Korean galbi ribs* are. While I think the marinade is likely the same for both, I think the char has the ability to shine more on ribs. With thinner beef, too much char can overpower the taste of the meat itself, while these flanken (lateral) cut ribs need that mild burnt taste to draw out the flavor of the beef.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;fun-fact-if-youve-ever-heard-the-term-la-galbi-the-name-stems-from-either-1-the-korean-communitys-popularization-of-the-dish-in-los-angeles-or-2-the-lateral-cut-style-of-the-ribs&quot;&gt;*Fun fact: If you’ve ever heard the term LA Galbi, the name stems from either 1. the Korean community’s popularization of the dish in Los Angeles or 2. the lateral cut style of the ribs.&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Operating during the pandemic is already a huge challenge, but opening at the beginning of one adds its own obstacles to an already difficult time. I know Miso isn’t alone in this struggle, but if you have the means to support another business right now, keep Miso on your list! They deliver on their commitment to serve exceptional teriyaki, and I hope to try their fried rice and teri bun dishes soon as well.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="jerseyeats" /><summary type="html">Beef Teriyaki Serving up everything from teri buns to Korean-style ramen to mixed tempura, Miso Teriyaki entered the Bergen County dining scene in March 2020. When I saw a teriyaki restaurant coming to Tenafly, it dawned on me that I haven’t had teriyaki in years. Apparently, it’s the unofficial signature dish of Seattle, which now makes me regret not eating it when I had the opportunity to go there. But alas, Miso arrived and according to their logo, they’re based in Seattle! I don’t know their full story, but I would love to interview them to get the full scoop on their roots and why they decided to bring their West Coast food over to freezing Jersey. Above, you can see their hand trimmed, char-broiled beef teriyaki, which from some angles, kind of just looks like cooked beef. But wow, it packs a punch! If you love beef bulgogi, you may equally enjoy this. The classic “burnt” flavor is present, but not in an overwhelming way that turns you off – if you’ve ever had East Asian barbecue, you know the sensation! You can tell the marinade is deeply embedded throughout the beef and isn’t just added in the last few minutes of cooking. What an incredible dish! I believe all the teriyaki dishes come with a small container of their teriyaki sauce, but I personally prefer the meat or “substance” (tofu, shrimp, salmon, etc.) of the dish by itself. Save that little sauce vessel for those huge portions of rice. Chicken Yakisoba Okay, vegetable galore in this noodle dish. The amount of veggies in their chicken yakisoba would be my only criticism, but not for a dislike of veggies!! I enjoy vegetables, but felt there was an imbalance of noodle to vegetable. I found this a bit odd, since restaurants typically try to overload with carbs rather than the more expensive vegetables. I enjoyed the chicken and the noodles, as I’m a huuuuuuge “thick egg-type” noodle fan, as opposed to thinner spaghetti-like types. Note that they cook their noodles a little under al-dente, so if you prefer less chewy noodles, just request them to be “fully cooked”. Chicken Katsu Rib Teriyaki I don’t know why, but chicken katsu always hits the spot for me. It’s some part of a chicken covered in panko breadcrumbs, BUT OH MY I just love it. Miso serves a katsu sauce that’s not the traditional Bull-Dog Tonkatsu Sauce. I wasn’t able to catch a photo of the sauce, but dare I say, it was better than the Bull-Dog? I may just be making that up – they could very well be the same. Anyway, Miso’s katsu was thinner than I liked, but that’s simply a preference. The katsu is a great pairing to an assortment of otherwise grilled meats. Finally, to the right of the chicken katsu is the rib teriyaki. It’s the winner of these four dishes for me! The ribs are laterally cut – the same way Korean galbi ribs* are. While I think the marinade is likely the same for both, I think the char has the ability to shine more on ribs. With thinner beef, too much char can overpower the taste of the meat itself, while these flanken (lateral) cut ribs need that mild burnt taste to draw out the flavor of the beef. *Fun fact: If you’ve ever heard the term LA Galbi, the name stems from either 1. the Korean community’s popularization of the dish in Los Angeles or 2. the lateral cut style of the ribs. Operating during the pandemic is already a huge challenge, but opening at the beginning of one adds its own obstacles to an already difficult time. I know Miso isn’t alone in this struggle, but if you have the means to support another business right now, keep Miso on your list! They deliver on their commitment to serve exceptional teriyaki, and I hope to try their fried rice and teri bun dishes soon as well.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/jerseyeats/miso/misoteriyaki1.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/jerseyeats/miso/misoteriyaki1.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Summer in Asia</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/beyond/asia" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Summer in Asia" /><published>2021-01-20T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2021-01-20T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/beyond/asia</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/beyond/asia">&lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/china/heycha1.JPG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;
          Fruity Cheese Tea Trio
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/taiwan/taipeifood.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;
          Oyster Omelette + Noodle Soup
        &lt;/div&gt;        
    &lt;/div&gt;    
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reason I look back on Asia especially fondly is because the foods I’ve grown up eating and learned to love here in the states truly felt at home in Asia – which seems obvious, but only becomes more apparent when you finally go. Yes, the Asian food in America is undisputedly excellent, but the Asian food IN Asia is on another level. The meals can be so simple and “bare bones”, but are elevated when compared to how they taste in America. Chefs in the states who immigrated from Asia often need to adjust their flavorings to pander to a wide variety of taste buds, whereas chefs in China are catering to mostly Chinese consumers, allowing them to stick to their more traditional methods. These photos are from my summer in Asia in 2018, where I was introduced to so many new dishes and elevations of ones I already knew. My dad grew up in China, so he knows his way around and has some fun tidbits to add about some of the foods we tried, which only added to this incredible experience of staying in China. I will also preface this post by saying that a lot of the foods I’m sharing below are non-traditional, but I ate plenty of traditionally Cantonese dishes during my time - I was just enjoying the moment and couldn’t snap a photo!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This post will include mostly photos, but I’ll write about any foods that may need more of a description, connections to other cultures, or have a story I want to share. While I don’t have the exact restaurant names, keep these dishes on your list for the future!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Dishes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&quot;foods&quot;&gt;
  &lt;h5 id=&quot;guangzhou&quot;&gt;Guangzhou&lt;/h5&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Some people say Cantonese food is the most boring of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://hakkasan.com/stories/eight-culinary-traditions-china/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;Eight Chinese Cuisines&lt;/a&gt;, as it doesn’t pack the kick of Sichuan or Hunan cuisine, but the simplicity of the dishes is the most impressive part. You might be used to seeing Cantonese cuisine through &lt;em&gt;dim sum&lt;/em&gt; (to touch the heart) or &lt;em&gt;yum cha&lt;/em&gt; (to drink tea), which is typically drinking tea with smaller plates. Some popular dishes you might know of are rice rolls drowning in sweet soy sauce (a personal favorite of mine) and char siu (叉烧) bao (baked or steamed roast pork buns). &lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/china/gzchashu.jpg&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;~Fancy~ Char Siu&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/china/gzcafe.JPG&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Char Siu + Beef Chow Fun&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/china/garlicribs.jpg&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Crispy Garlic Ribs&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/china/riceroll.jpg&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;HK-style Cheung Fun&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Above are just a small sampling of Cantonese dishes I got a photo of: char siu, &lt;em&gt;gon chow ngau huo&lt;/em&gt; (beef chow fun), crispy garlic pork ribs, and HK-style cheung fun. Note the distinction between the cheung fun pictured above, and the Cantonese one; HK-style ones are literally tiny rolls, and Cantonese ones are unrolled (but still “rolls), longer, and thinner. It’s pretty much just the shape, but both are shockingly addictive. Enjoy HK-style cheung fun doused in hoisin + peanut sauces (as seen above), and Cantonese ones doused in sweet soy sauce. This is &lt;em&gt;important&lt;/em&gt;. This is NOT the soy sauce you eat with sushi, but a perfect umami and sweet combination that pares very well with the plainness of cheung fun. &lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/china/gzroastpork.jpg&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Siu Yuk Roast Pork&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;  
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/china/roastplatter2.jpg&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Assorted Roast Platter&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/china/gzdumplings.JPG&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Fried Dumplings&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/china/gzpuff.jpg&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;See below!&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Just a miscellaneous collection of food pictured above. Siu yuk, or roast pork, is CRISPY, and there’s no deep frying involved. This roast pork is stuffed with a variety of seasonings and hoisin sauce, which you’ll get a taste of once the pork is cut up. The picture next to the roast pork is a platter of the most popular Cantonese meats, which are char siu, siu yuk, roast duck (different from Peking duck!), as well as the not originally Cantonese drunken chicken. You also see the jellyfish salad, which doesn’t taste like seafood whatsoever.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Now, we all know what dumplings are, but what’s pictured on the right is still an enigma to me two years later. It’s this gorgeous fluffy pudding, soufflé/sponge cake thing covered in sliced nuts. I have virtually no idea what it’s actually intended to be, but it’s definitely something to try out if you ever come across it! &lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h5 id=&quot;taipei&quot;&gt;Taipei&lt;/h5&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/taiwan/beefnoodle1.JPG&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Beef Noodle Soup&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/taiwan/scallionpancake.jpg&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Scallion Pancake&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/taiwan/taipeicorndog.jpg&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Special Corn Dogs&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/taiwan/taiwanxlb.JPG&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Xiao Long Bao&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;The best food in Asia really comes from the no-frills restaurants and the famous Taiwanese night markets. We went to &lt;strong&gt;Raohe&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Shi Lin Night Markets&lt;/strong&gt;, IIRC, but there are plenty of lesser known ones that likely serve as equally good products. &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Those hand-pulled noodles and freshly-wrapped boiled dumplings were from this tiny, open-air shop a few blocks from the hotel we stayed at. And my GOSH, don't even get me started on those scallion pancakes. The scallion pancakes in America don't do these justice! You can get ham, cheese, egg, and a sweet-spicy sauce/glaze as toppings or just get it plain. Fantastic either way.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Those corn dogs are just like Korean corn dogs, which are dipped in rice batter, as opposed to traditional cornmeal batter, coated in panko, and stuffed with mozzarella cheese and/or a hot dog. They’re also dusted with granulated sugar and topped with ketchup, honey mustard, and/or or Japanese mayo. The last photo is &lt;em&gt;xiao long bao&lt;/em&gt;, which I don’t believe are originally Taiwanese, but you may recognize them from the &lt;a href=&quot;https://dintaifungusa.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;Din Tai Fung&lt;/a&gt; empire that is 100% from Taiwan.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h5 id=&quot;singapore&quot;&gt;Singapore&lt;/h5&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/singapore/chashu.jpg&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Chashu (top) and Steak (Bottom) Rice Bowls&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/singapore/frybasket.JPG&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Fry Basket&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/singapore/satay.JPG&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Mixed Satay&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/singapore/spicypork.jpg&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Suan Ni Bai Rou&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;The top two photos are from &lt;a href=&quot;https://pasarbella.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;PasarBella at Suntec City&lt;/a&gt;, an NYC-inspired food hall. I know some people are shaking their heads in disappointment for not eating traditionally Singaporean food, but I remember eating here more out of convenience than anything. Nonetheless, the food was delicious, and there's not really much else to say.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;This satay is from &lt;strong&gt;Newton Food Centre&lt;/strong&gt; -- fun fact, it's where Crazy Rich Asians filmed that intro scene of Nick, Rachel, Colin, and Araminta eat at a hawker centre! We also ate chili crab (one of the national Singaporean dishes), accompanied by mantou (steamed or fried buns - no stuffing), as well as roti prata and quite a few more dishes from various stalls. Next to it is the Sichuan &lt;em&gt;Suan Ni Bai Rou&lt;/em&gt; pork belly. I know this isn't quite Singaporean, but we did eat it in Singapore, so that's why it's under the Singapore &quot;category&quot;. It's a very famous Sichuan dish, and it consists of &lt;em&gt;ultra-thin&lt;/em&gt; pork belly doused in chili-garlic sauce. This is one of Antonia's favorite dishes, but be warned - describing the sauce as &lt;em&gt;just&lt;/em&gt; garlic is being modest. This dish is g a r l i c k y.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;h4 id=&quot;boba-sweets&quot;&gt;Boba + Sweets&lt;/h4&gt;
  &lt;h5 id=&quot;guangzhou&quot;&gt;Guangzhou&lt;/h5&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/china/heycha2.JPG&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Cheese Mango&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/china/heycha3.jpg&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Black Sugar Boba&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/china/gztart1.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Macanese Egg Tarts&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/china/milkfry.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Fried Milk&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;IT’S DESSERT TIMEEEE! I don’t have a preference for sweet or savory, but my sweet tooth was satisfied in Asia! The boba tea, the cheese tea, the tarts, EVERY dessert is incredible there. Above, you see some mango cheese tea, which is mango blended with ice topped with a lightly salted cheese foam, which I drank nearly every day on my journey. At the very top, you also see a strawberry cheese and grape cheese, which are solid competitors for best drink at HeyCha. You also see a black sugar boba, which is similar to brown sugar boba, a thicker and stickier drink topping, but with a more licorice-like taste. I prefer brown sugar, but black sugar boba tastes great, too. &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Below those drinks are Macanese egg tarts, which are inspired by Portuguese tarts, which are one of my favorite warm desserts. The Macanese egg tart shells are flakier and much more layered, compared to their Hong Kong-style counterparts with a crumblier, but still puff pastry-esque crust. Next, I’m ecstatic to present the incredible FRIED MILK!!! Don’t expect a drink to flow out once you bite in, but it’s a milk custard rolled in a thin wrapper (or sometimes a batter). It has only a subtle sweetness, which is ideal for me. I’ve never had the Spanish leche frita, but if it’s anything like this Cantonese variation, I am &lt;em&gt;in&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;h5 id=&quot;taipei&quot;&gt;Taipei&lt;/h5&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/taiwan/brownsugarbub.jpg&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Black Sugar Boba&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/taiwan/bubbletea.JPG&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Fiftea&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/taiwan/7_11_bub.jpg&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Original Boba&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/taiwan/chocolatebao.JPG&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Chocolate Red Bean Bao&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;While brown sugar boba is starting to gain traction in the states, the black sugar boba is not quite on the same level of popularity just yet. I personally don't love the licorice taste of the black sugar, but I for sure see the appeal of this drink. Just as brown sugar, or really any sugar, can be caramelized, black sugar can be as well, and that’s what you see above. The “Fiftea” bubble tea photo next to it was unfortunately more disappointing -- Antonia knew it was a well-known chain, so she suggested we try it. The bubbles were fine, but we didn't love the tea flavor as much. My dad said his milk tea tasted good, so maybe it’s just the fruit teas we had.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;We also went to a 7-Eleven in Taiwan, and much to my pleasant surprise, they had 7-11 Bubble Tea! It was actually quite good, but I do suggest supporting the local milk tea shops. Next to that, there’s the final dessert I share, which is the chocolate red bean bao. If you live in a U.S. state with a Din Tai Fung, you certainly don’t need to go to Taiwan for these, BUT...wow, I love red bean desserts, and this one repurposed those paper-thin dumpling skins I love to hold in some chocolate-y red bean goodness.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;h5 id=&quot;hong-kong&quot;&gt;Hong Kong&lt;/h5&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/hongkong/hkwaffle.jpg&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;That famous &lt;em&gt;gai dan jai&lt;/em&gt; from &lt;strong&gt;Lee Keung Kee North Point Egg Waffles&lt;/strong&gt;. My maternal extended family resides in Hong Kong, so they were excited for me to have my first Hong Kong egg waffle IN Hong Kong! I'm a huuuuuge egg waffle fan, and when I talk to my grandma about how much I love these waffles, we just laugh about the name every time. The name literally means little chicken egg, and we just think the name is so fitting for this dessert. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;button id=&quot;showfoods&quot; class=&quot;showmorephotosbutton&quot; onclick=&quot;toggleContent('foods', 'showfoods', '( - ) maybe later...', '( + ) show me the food!')&quot;&gt;( + ) show me the food!&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Activities&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&quot;places&quot;&gt;
  &lt;h5 id=&quot;guangzhou&quot;&gt;Guangzhou&lt;/h5&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/china/wallofshells.JPG&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Lingnan Impression Park&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/china/lilythepom.jpg&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Lily the Pomeranian&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lingnan Impression Park&lt;/strong&gt;: Stalls of street art and food, along with stunning attractions, like this Wall of Oyster Shells.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Lily is my Guangzhou family's dog. How do you not fall in love with those eyes?!&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Not quite an activity, but I wanted to share her beauty.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
  &lt;h5 id=&quot;taipei&quot;&gt;Taipei&lt;/h5&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/taiwan/chiang-kai-shek.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Chiang Kai-shek Memorial&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/taiwan/taiwanlandscape.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Yangmingshan National Park&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/taiwan/jadebokchoy.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Jade Bok Choy&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/taiwan/meatstone.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Dongpo Pork Stone&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;We didn't have a ton of stops on our trip, but that just meant we got to spend some more time at each! First is the &lt;strong&gt;Chiang Kai Shek Memorial&lt;/strong&gt;, as Chiang Kai-shek, the former leader of the Chinese Nationalist Party, died in Taipei. The memorial had multiple exhibits, so be sure to check those out when you're there.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Next, we checked out &lt;strong&gt;Yangmingshan National Park&lt;/strong&gt;, where there was a volcano, along with a ton of grass-lined valleys and COWS! Definitely smelled like cow dung, but an enjoyable experience nonetheless.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Now...onto the &lt;strong&gt;National Palace Museum&lt;/strong&gt;, home to the Jade Bok Choy and Dongpo Pork Stone! You can see how intricate the details are - they perfectly walk the fine line between ultra-elegant and realistic. &lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h5 id=&quot;hong-kong&quot;&gt;Hong Kong&lt;/h5&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/hongkong/bigbuddha.JPG&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Tian Tan Buddha&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/hongkong/hkclocktower.jpg&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;HK Railway Clock Tower&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tian Tan Buddha&lt;/strong&gt;, or as it's informally known, the Big Buddha! Wow, it was a &lt;em&gt;journey&lt;/em&gt; to get here. You first hop on a gondola, the ride of which took about 30-45 minutes one way, and then, take a decent walk to the steps of the Buddha. The Buddha sits above a hilltop, and the steps are no joke. However, I was truly in awe of this bronze masterpiece, beyond its sheer magnitude. I am nonreligious (I don't even know what I really identify as), but according to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.plm.org.hk/eng/buddha.php&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;Po Lin Monastery&lt;/a&gt;, the statue, which &quot;symbolizes the stability of Hong Kong, prosperity of China and peace on earth&quot;, took 12 years to plan and build. It wasn't ridiculously loud at the top, and I appreciated the peacefulness of the attraction. The Buddha would be very close to the top of my list for places I would like to return to. &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Former &lt;strong&gt;Kowloon-Canton Railway Clock Tower&lt;/strong&gt; is a symbol of &quot;moving on&quot; for the Chinese immigrants who passed through this terminus of Kowloon–Canton Railway to start new lives in Hong Kong. My dad told us we had to visit this clock tower, since my mom and him used to stop by.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;

  &lt;h5 id=&quot;singapore&quot;&gt;Singapore&lt;/h5&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/singapore/gardensbythebay.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Gardens by the Bay&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/singapore/faberpeakbells.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Faber Peak Bells&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/singapore/marinabaysands.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Marina Bay Sands&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/singapore/minimerlion.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Mini Merlion...&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gardens by the Bay&lt;/strong&gt;: One of the most famous Singaporean attractions, you can find beautiful flora and incredible architecture in any of the sub-exhibitions. I visited the Cloud Forest (where this photo was taken) and the Flower Dome. They also have a musical light show at night to check out - it's &lt;em&gt;free&lt;/em&gt;, and you just lie down on a  blanket and look up!&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mount Faber Peak&lt;/strong&gt;: take the Singapore Cable Car up to Faber Peak. There's a giant Bell of Happiness, but also a fence to tie your personalized mini bell.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Antonia in front of the &lt;strong&gt;Marina Bay Sands&lt;/strong&gt;, arguably one of the most famous hotels in the world. &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;This &lt;strong&gt;Merlion&lt;/strong&gt; is the national symbol of Singapore, but also a bit of an inside joke in my family. When my dad decided put Singapore as one of our destinations, he also was adamant about us seeing the giant Merlion. But this one...is ~only~ 8.6 meters tall. Not that it's not huge, but my dad kept saying that the Merlion he visited thirty years ago was far, far taller AND that the giant one was the original Merlion. So we kept looking up &quot;giant Merlion&quot; on Google, but we couldn't find it! Eventually, we discovered it was on Sentosa Island, which is certainly still in Singapore, just not as centrally located. Luckily, Singapore is quite small, so we made the trip to see the lovely Sentosa Merlion, which BTW, is a replica. This one is THIRTY SEVEN meters tall! You can ride an elevator up this giant replica, but we decided it wasn't worth the price. As I was writing this, I unfortunately found out it was permanently closed and demolished just over a year ago 😞 But I'm fortunate to have seen it before Singapore had to say goodbye.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
  
  &lt;p&gt;Without further ado, this is the giant Merlion...&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/singapore/sentosamerlion.jpg&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;Sentosa Merlion&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;button id=&quot;showplaces&quot; class=&quot;showmorephotosbutton&quot; onclick=&quot;toggleContent('places', 'showplaces', '( - ) maybe later...', '( + ) show me where to go!')&quot;&gt;( + ) show me where to go!&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope this guide helped you live vicariously through my 2018 self. I thought a lot about how disconnected I felt with my Chinese heritage, but I’ve been on a journey to understand my roots ever since then. Thank you China, Singapore, Taiwan, Hong Kong, and Macau for an amazing, introspective summer. I am so grateful for food on the table and each of these experiences❤️&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/hongkong/hkviews.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;HK Harbor&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="beyond" /><summary type="html">Fruity Cheese Tea Trio Oyster Omelette + Noodle Soup The reason I look back on Asia especially fondly is because the foods I’ve grown up eating and learned to love here in the states truly felt at home in Asia – which seems obvious, but only becomes more apparent when you finally go. Yes, the Asian food in America is undisputedly excellent, but the Asian food IN Asia is on another level. The meals can be so simple and “bare bones”, but are elevated when compared to how they taste in America. Chefs in the states who immigrated from Asia often need to adjust their flavorings to pander to a wide variety of taste buds, whereas chefs in China are catering to mostly Chinese consumers, allowing them to stick to their more traditional methods. These photos are from my summer in Asia in 2018, where I was introduced to so many new dishes and elevations of ones I already knew. My dad grew up in China, so he knows his way around and has some fun tidbits to add about some of the foods we tried, which only added to this incredible experience of staying in China. I will also preface this post by saying that a lot of the foods I’m sharing below are non-traditional, but I ate plenty of traditionally Cantonese dishes during my time - I was just enjoying the moment and couldn’t snap a photo! This post will include mostly photos, but I’ll write about any foods that may need more of a description, connections to other cultures, or have a story I want to share. While I don’t have the exact restaurant names, keep these dishes on your list for the future! Dishes Guangzhou Some people say Cantonese food is the most boring of the Eight Chinese Cuisines, as it doesn’t pack the kick of Sichuan or Hunan cuisine, but the simplicity of the dishes is the most impressive part. You might be used to seeing Cantonese cuisine through dim sum (to touch the heart) or yum cha (to drink tea), which is typically drinking tea with smaller plates. Some popular dishes you might know of are rice rolls drowning in sweet soy sauce (a personal favorite of mine) and char siu (叉烧) bao (baked or steamed roast pork buns). ~Fancy~ Char Siu Char Siu + Beef Chow Fun Crispy Garlic Ribs HK-style Cheung Fun Above are just a small sampling of Cantonese dishes I got a photo of: char siu, gon chow ngau huo (beef chow fun), crispy garlic pork ribs, and HK-style cheung fun. Note the distinction between the cheung fun pictured above, and the Cantonese one; HK-style ones are literally tiny rolls, and Cantonese ones are unrolled (but still “rolls), longer, and thinner. It’s pretty much just the shape, but both are shockingly addictive. Enjoy HK-style cheung fun doused in hoisin + peanut sauces (as seen above), and Cantonese ones doused in sweet soy sauce. This is important. This is NOT the soy sauce you eat with sushi, but a perfect umami and sweet combination that pares very well with the plainness of cheung fun. Siu Yuk Roast Pork Assorted Roast Platter Fried Dumplings See below! Just a miscellaneous collection of food pictured above. Siu yuk, or roast pork, is CRISPY, and there’s no deep frying involved. This roast pork is stuffed with a variety of seasonings and hoisin sauce, which you’ll get a taste of once the pork is cut up. The picture next to the roast pork is a platter of the most popular Cantonese meats, which are char siu, siu yuk, roast duck (different from Peking duck!), as well as the not originally Cantonese drunken chicken. You also see the jellyfish salad, which doesn’t taste like seafood whatsoever. Now, we all know what dumplings are, but what’s pictured on the right is still an enigma to me two years later. It’s this gorgeous fluffy pudding, soufflé/sponge cake thing covered in sliced nuts. I have virtually no idea what it’s actually intended to be, but it’s definitely something to try out if you ever come across it! Taipei Beef Noodle Soup Scallion Pancake Special Corn Dogs Xiao Long Bao The best food in Asia really comes from the no-frills restaurants and the famous Taiwanese night markets. We went to Raohe and Shi Lin Night Markets, IIRC, but there are plenty of lesser known ones that likely serve as equally good products. Those hand-pulled noodles and freshly-wrapped boiled dumplings were from this tiny, open-air shop a few blocks from the hotel we stayed at. And my GOSH, don't even get me started on those scallion pancakes. The scallion pancakes in America don't do these justice! You can get ham, cheese, egg, and a sweet-spicy sauce/glaze as toppings or just get it plain. Fantastic either way. Those corn dogs are just like Korean corn dogs, which are dipped in rice batter, as opposed to traditional cornmeal batter, coated in panko, and stuffed with mozzarella cheese and/or a hot dog. They’re also dusted with granulated sugar and topped with ketchup, honey mustard, and/or or Japanese mayo. The last photo is xiao long bao, which I don’t believe are originally Taiwanese, but you may recognize them from the Din Tai Fung empire that is 100% from Taiwan. Singapore Chashu (top) and Steak (Bottom) Rice Bowls Fry Basket Mixed Satay Suan Ni Bai Rou The top two photos are from PasarBella at Suntec City, an NYC-inspired food hall. I know some people are shaking their heads in disappointment for not eating traditionally Singaporean food, but I remember eating here more out of convenience than anything. Nonetheless, the food was delicious, and there's not really much else to say. This satay is from Newton Food Centre -- fun fact, it's where Crazy Rich Asians filmed that intro scene of Nick, Rachel, Colin, and Araminta eat at a hawker centre! We also ate chili crab (one of the national Singaporean dishes), accompanied by mantou (steamed or fried buns - no stuffing), as well as roti prata and quite a few more dishes from various stalls. Next to it is the Sichuan Suan Ni Bai Rou pork belly. I know this isn't quite Singaporean, but we did eat it in Singapore, so that's why it's under the Singapore &quot;category&quot;. It's a very famous Sichuan dish, and it consists of ultra-thin pork belly doused in chili-garlic sauce. This is one of Antonia's favorite dishes, but be warned - describing the sauce as just garlic is being modest. This dish is g a r l i c k y. Boba + Sweets Guangzhou Cheese Mango Black Sugar Boba Macanese Egg Tarts Fried Milk IT’S DESSERT TIMEEEE! I don’t have a preference for sweet or savory, but my sweet tooth was satisfied in Asia! The boba tea, the cheese tea, the tarts, EVERY dessert is incredible there. Above, you see some mango cheese tea, which is mango blended with ice topped with a lightly salted cheese foam, which I drank nearly every day on my journey. At the very top, you also see a strawberry cheese and grape cheese, which are solid competitors for best drink at HeyCha. You also see a black sugar boba, which is similar to brown sugar boba, a thicker and stickier drink topping, but with a more licorice-like taste. I prefer brown sugar, but black sugar boba tastes great, too. Below those drinks are Macanese egg tarts, which are inspired by Portuguese tarts, which are one of my favorite warm desserts. The Macanese egg tart shells are flakier and much more layered, compared to their Hong Kong-style counterparts with a crumblier, but still puff pastry-esque crust. Next, I’m ecstatic to present the incredible FRIED MILK!!! Don’t expect a drink to flow out once you bite in, but it’s a milk custard rolled in a thin wrapper (or sometimes a batter). It has only a subtle sweetness, which is ideal for me. I’ve never had the Spanish leche frita, but if it’s anything like this Cantonese variation, I am in. Taipei Black Sugar Boba Fiftea Original Boba Chocolate Red Bean Bao While brown sugar boba is starting to gain traction in the states, the black sugar boba is not quite on the same level of popularity just yet. I personally don't love the licorice taste of the black sugar, but I for sure see the appeal of this drink. Just as brown sugar, or really any sugar, can be caramelized, black sugar can be as well, and that’s what you see above. The “Fiftea” bubble tea photo next to it was unfortunately more disappointing -- Antonia knew it was a well-known chain, so she suggested we try it. The bubbles were fine, but we didn't love the tea flavor as much. My dad said his milk tea tasted good, so maybe it’s just the fruit teas we had. We also went to a 7-Eleven in Taiwan, and much to my pleasant surprise, they had 7-11 Bubble Tea! It was actually quite good, but I do suggest supporting the local milk tea shops. Next to that, there’s the final dessert I share, which is the chocolate red bean bao. If you live in a U.S. state with a Din Tai Fung, you certainly don’t need to go to Taiwan for these, BUT...wow, I love red bean desserts, and this one repurposed those paper-thin dumpling skins I love to hold in some chocolate-y red bean goodness. Hong Kong That famous gai dan jai from Lee Keung Kee North Point Egg Waffles. My maternal extended family resides in Hong Kong, so they were excited for me to have my first Hong Kong egg waffle IN Hong Kong! I'm a huuuuuge egg waffle fan, and when I talk to my grandma about how much I love these waffles, we just laugh about the name every time. The name literally means little chicken egg, and we just think the name is so fitting for this dessert. ( + ) show me the food! Activities Guangzhou Lingnan Impression Park Lily the Pomeranian Lingnan Impression Park: Stalls of street art and food, along with stunning attractions, like this Wall of Oyster Shells. Lily is my Guangzhou family's dog. How do you not fall in love with those eyes?! Not quite an activity, but I wanted to share her beauty. Taipei Chiang Kai-shek Memorial Yangmingshan National Park Jade Bok Choy Dongpo Pork Stone We didn't have a ton of stops on our trip, but that just meant we got to spend some more time at each! First is the Chiang Kai Shek Memorial, as Chiang Kai-shek, the former leader of the Chinese Nationalist Party, died in Taipei. The memorial had multiple exhibits, so be sure to check those out when you're there. Next, we checked out Yangmingshan National Park, where there was a volcano, along with a ton of grass-lined valleys and COWS! Definitely smelled like cow dung, but an enjoyable experience nonetheless. Now...onto the National Palace Museum, home to the Jade Bok Choy and Dongpo Pork Stone! You can see how intricate the details are - they perfectly walk the fine line between ultra-elegant and realistic. Hong Kong Tian Tan Buddha HK Railway Clock Tower Tian Tan Buddha, or as it's informally known, the Big Buddha! Wow, it was a journey to get here. You first hop on a gondola, the ride of which took about 30-45 minutes one way, and then, take a decent walk to the steps of the Buddha. The Buddha sits above a hilltop, and the steps are no joke. However, I was truly in awe of this bronze masterpiece, beyond its sheer magnitude. I am nonreligious (I don't even know what I really identify as), but according to the Po Lin Monastery, the statue, which &quot;symbolizes the stability of Hong Kong, prosperity of China and peace on earth&quot;, took 12 years to plan and build. It wasn't ridiculously loud at the top, and I appreciated the peacefulness of the attraction. The Buddha would be very close to the top of my list for places I would like to return to. The Former Kowloon-Canton Railway Clock Tower is a symbol of &quot;moving on&quot; for the Chinese immigrants who passed through this terminus of Kowloon–Canton Railway to start new lives in Hong Kong. My dad told us we had to visit this clock tower, since my mom and him used to stop by. Singapore Gardens by the Bay Faber Peak Bells Marina Bay Sands Mini Merlion... Gardens by the Bay: One of the most famous Singaporean attractions, you can find beautiful flora and incredible architecture in any of the sub-exhibitions. I visited the Cloud Forest (where this photo was taken) and the Flower Dome. They also have a musical light show at night to check out - it's free, and you just lie down on a blanket and look up! Mount Faber Peak: take the Singapore Cable Car up to Faber Peak. There's a giant Bell of Happiness, but also a fence to tie your personalized mini bell. Antonia in front of the Marina Bay Sands, arguably one of the most famous hotels in the world. This Merlion is the national symbol of Singapore, but also a bit of an inside joke in my family. When my dad decided put Singapore as one of our destinations, he also was adamant about us seeing the giant Merlion. But this one...is ~only~ 8.6 meters tall. Not that it's not huge, but my dad kept saying that the Merlion he visited thirty years ago was far, far taller AND that the giant one was the original Merlion. So we kept looking up &quot;giant Merlion&quot; on Google, but we couldn't find it! Eventually, we discovered it was on Sentosa Island, which is certainly still in Singapore, just not as centrally located. Luckily, Singapore is quite small, so we made the trip to see the lovely Sentosa Merlion, which BTW, is a replica. This one is THIRTY SEVEN meters tall! You can ride an elevator up this giant replica, but we decided it wasn't worth the price. As I was writing this, I unfortunately found out it was permanently closed and demolished just over a year ago 😞 But I'm fortunate to have seen it before Singapore had to say goodbye. Without further ado, this is the giant Merlion... Sentosa Merlion ( + ) show me where to go! I hope this guide helped you live vicariously through my 2018 self. I thought a lot about how disconnected I felt with my Chinese heritage, but I’ve been on a journey to understand my roots ever since then. Thank you China, Singapore, Taiwan, Hong Kong, and Macau for an amazing, introspective summer. I am so grateful for food on the table and each of these experiences❤️ HK Harbor</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/beyond/china/heycha1.JPG" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/beyond/china/heycha1.JPG" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Grandma’s Baozi</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/recipes/grandmabao" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Grandma’s Baozi" /><published>2021-01-06T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2021-01-06T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/recipes/grandmabao</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/recipes/grandmabao">&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/recipes/bao/grandmabao.png&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5GajgDBZeoQ&amp;amp;t=3s&amp;amp;ab_channel=bub&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Watch Antonia’s ~cinematography~ of our grandma making baozi&lt;/a&gt;! Please like, comment, and subscribe to the &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCqH5MDmErneKqkCnYxBGnEA&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;bub YouTube channel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, where she posts vlogs from her apartment provided by her internship, and I even make a cameo once in a while for our “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLXr-C5XyXq8c2sFUzGIP5w5HxpAtvWgYF&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;bake w/ bubs&lt;/a&gt;” series! The recipe is transcribed by Antonia, as my grandma speaks in Cantonese throughout.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I promised Antonia I would promo her videos, because she really works beyond hard on each and every one of them! Between the cover art and animations she creates, she really deserves all the love.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="recipes" /><summary type="html">Watch Antonia’s ~cinematography~ of our grandma making baozi! Please like, comment, and subscribe to the bub YouTube channel, where she posts vlogs from her apartment provided by her internship, and I even make a cameo once in a while for our “bake w/ bubs” series! The recipe is transcribed by Antonia, as my grandma speaks in Cantonese throughout. I promised Antonia I would promo her videos, because she really works beyond hard on each and every one of them! Between the cover art and animations she creates, she really deserves all the love.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/recipes/bao/grandmabao.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/recipes/bao/grandmabao.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">The Croissant Chronicles</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/recipes/croissantchronicles" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Croissant Chronicles" /><published>2020-12-23T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2020-12-23T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/recipes/croissantchronicles</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/recipes/croissantchronicles">&lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/recipes/croissant/croissantportrait1.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/recipes/croissant/croissantportrait3.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I made croissants from scratch for the first time! Ever since my sister, Antonia, a croissant connoisseur (just kidding, she’s only made croissants twice before), told me she made croissants from scratch, I’ve been itching to try making them too. It’s month eight of being totally at home, so we finally decided to tackle this challenge! Many hours later, they were far from perfect, but still the perfect homemade baked good to keep us company. This collaboration is with my big sister, Antonia, an aspiring vlogger.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;watch-our-bake-with-bubs-video-here--like-comment-and-subscribe&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2d7ew5ALNX0&amp;amp;ab_channel=bub&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;WATCH OUR BAKE WITH BUBS VIDEO HERE ~ Like, Comment, AND Subscribe!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/recipes/croissant/croissantfood/croissantsolo1.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/recipes/croissant/croissantfood/blueberrycroissant.JPEG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Recipe adapted from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jocooks.com/recipes/homemade-croissants/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Jo Cooks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; - great recipe!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;croissants-from-scratch&quot;&gt;Croissants From Scratch&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&quot;yields-8-medium-croissants-but-you-can-make-16-smaller-ones-instead&quot;&gt;Yields 8 medium croissants, but you can make ~16 smaller ones instead&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ingredients&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;¾ cup lukewarm milk&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;⅛ cup packed brown sugar&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1½ tsp active dry yeast&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;3½ cups all-purpose flour &lt;em&gt;(may need as little as 3¼ or as much as 4 cups)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;¾ cup salted butter, &lt;em&gt;if using unsalted butter, add ½ tbsp salt&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;½ egg for egg wash&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Lightly stir lukewarm milk, brown sugar, and yeast with a fork in your mixing bowl. Let sit for 5 minutes, until foamy.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Add flour (and salt, &lt;strong&gt;if using unsalted butter&lt;/strong&gt;) to the bowl 1 cup at a time, and mix until soft, elastic, but still a little bit sticky.
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Start off with a sturdy spatula, then move on to kneading with your hands.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Loosely wrap the dough in plastic wrap and place the dough in a bowl. Refrigerate for one hour.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Make. The. Butter. Layer.&lt;/strong&gt; Y’all, this is the moment I was looking forward to the most, because of how fun recipe videos made it look. &lt;em&gt;It was fun.&lt;/em&gt; Cut the butter into evenly sized (especially the &lt;strong&gt;thickness&lt;/strong&gt;; the other dimensions are less important). Arrange the layers into a rectangular formation onto a sheet of plastic wrap (what we did) or parchment paper (what we would recommend). Place another equally-sized sheet on top of the butter rectangle.
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Parchment paper is a lot less clingy than plastic wrap, which is why we recommend it.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;The sheet of plastic/parchment should be considerably larger than the rectangle of butter. I recommend skipping to &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/2d7ew5ALNX0?t=102&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;1:42&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; to see how large our rectangle of wrap was.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Use a rolling pin to roll out on all sides of the butter rectangle. Be very careful when rolling this butter rectangle out. The rectangle shouldn’t be over rolled on any one side, as this would distort the rectangular formation. I recommend alternating the orientation of the rolling pin from vertical to horizontal several times through this process. See &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/2d7ew5ALNX0?t=102&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;2:04&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; to get an idea of what we did for ours.
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;We had a pretty imperfect rectangle, so I wouldn’t be discouraged if yours comes out a bit wonky looking. However, don’t veer too far off the intended rectangle, and definitely try your best to attain that shape!&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Refrigerate the dough&lt;/strong&gt; until use. This is important. You do not want this butter to be melty in the slightest, as the kitchen itself already has heat. This heat will soften your butter with time, but this butter sheet needs to be very firm!&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Flour your work surface, whether that be directly on your countertop or on a large tray (like ours), and roll out the dough into a rectangle that’s about 5 millimeters thick. The other dimensions are a little bit more up to you, because a bunch of different recipes give different sizes. Just make sure that the height of the dough rectangle is about equal to the width of the butter sheet.
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;To clarify, the width is the longest side (in reference to either the individual butter or dough sheet). The height is the shorter dimension.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Place your butter sheet in the center of the dough rectangle. This butter sheet should be ⅓ of the dough - you can think of the dough not &lt;em&gt;currently&lt;/em&gt; in contact with the butter as flaps! These flaps should be just slightly larger than the butter sheet rectangle.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fold these two flaps over the butter sheet one after another, similar to how a letter is folded. Now, move your rolling pin vertically (the “height” or shorter side of the dough should be closest to you) to form another rectangle that is similar sized to the dimensions of the original dough rectangle.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fold the dough rectangle like a letter again (thirds!) Place it on a tray, and wrap the tray in plastic wrap. Refrigerate for one hour.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This step needs to be repeated 3 times, meaning four times in addition to the previous step&lt;/strong&gt;! Move your rolling pin vertically (the “height” or shorter side of the dough should be closest to you) to form another rectangle that is similar sized to the dimensions of the original dough rectangle. Fold the dough rectangle like a letter (in thirds). Place it on a tray, and wrap the tray in plastic wrap. Refrigerate for one hour, &lt;strong&gt;with the exception of the fourth time&lt;/strong&gt;. &lt;em&gt;Refrigerate (at least) overnight only for the fourth (final) time&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Split the dough in half - freeze one half if you plan on using it another time. Roll the dough halves into long, ¼ inch thick rectangles. Cut each rectangle into triangles (more like an isosceles). They really can be any length you want, but you can probably cut 4-12 from each half.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Use a rolling pin to “flatten” each triangle from the wide side up. Stretch out the skinny side and begin rolling your triangle as tightly as possible!&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Place each triangle 1 to 2 inches apart on a baking sheet lined with parchment paper.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Let the croissants rise a bit for one more hour - you’re almost there! Brush them with egg wash.
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;You can also roll them ahead of time, then refrigerate for up to 18 hours prior to baking. Wrap the baking with plastic wrap, not tightly or loosely, but just tight enough so as little moisture as possible escapes.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Preheat the oven to 400°F. Get those croissants in the oven and bake for 8 to 12 minutes at 400°F, then turn down the heat to 375°F and bake them for another 8 to 12 minutes. They should be golden brown!&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Enjoy with whatever spreads, jams, sauces, and anything you like! We tried them with several fruit jams (blueberry, fig, strawberry, and more).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/recipes/croissant/croissantfood/buttersheet.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/recipes/croissant/croissantfood/readytobakecroissant.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes, this is a loooonnnnngggggg process, but I can confidently say the end result is worth it. My sister made them without me one additional time after the filming of this video, and I enjoyed them so much. They are FAR from perfect, but are still an unbelievably good treat. &lt;em&gt;Warning&lt;/em&gt;: they ARE buttery, but equally flaky. Now, start the recipe and devour these little pockets of goodness!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;final-results&quot;&gt;FINAL RESULTS!🤩&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/recipes/croissant/croissantfood/croissant2.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;they-look-like-they-have-such-a-solid-bottom-because-we-over-egg-washed---no-worries-if-this-happens-to-you-as-theyre-still-awesome&quot;&gt;They look like they have such a solid bottom, because we over egg-washed - no worries if this happens to you, as they’re still awesome.&lt;/h6&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="recipes" /><summary type="html">I made croissants from scratch for the first time! Ever since my sister, Antonia, a croissant connoisseur (just kidding, she’s only made croissants twice before), told me she made croissants from scratch, I’ve been itching to try making them too. It’s month eight of being totally at home, so we finally decided to tackle this challenge! Many hours later, they were far from perfect, but still the perfect homemade baked good to keep us company. This collaboration is with my big sister, Antonia, an aspiring vlogger. WATCH OUR BAKE WITH BUBS VIDEO HERE ~ Like, Comment, AND Subscribe! Recipe adapted from Jo Cooks - great recipe! Croissants From Scratch Yields 8 medium croissants, but you can make ~16 smaller ones instead Ingredients ¾ cup lukewarm milk ⅛ cup packed brown sugar 1½ tsp active dry yeast 3½ cups all-purpose flour (may need as little as 3¼ or as much as 4 cups) ¾ cup salted butter, if using unsalted butter, add ½ tbsp salt ½ egg for egg wash Directions Lightly stir lukewarm milk, brown sugar, and yeast with a fork in your mixing bowl. Let sit for 5 minutes, until foamy. Add flour (and salt, if using unsalted butter) to the bowl 1 cup at a time, and mix until soft, elastic, but still a little bit sticky. Start off with a sturdy spatula, then move on to kneading with your hands. Loosely wrap the dough in plastic wrap and place the dough in a bowl. Refrigerate for one hour. Make. The. Butter. Layer. Y’all, this is the moment I was looking forward to the most, because of how fun recipe videos made it look. It was fun. Cut the butter into evenly sized (especially the thickness; the other dimensions are less important). Arrange the layers into a rectangular formation onto a sheet of plastic wrap (what we did) or parchment paper (what we would recommend). Place another equally-sized sheet on top of the butter rectangle. Parchment paper is a lot less clingy than plastic wrap, which is why we recommend it. The sheet of plastic/parchment should be considerably larger than the rectangle of butter. I recommend skipping to 1:42 to see how large our rectangle of wrap was. Use a rolling pin to roll out on all sides of the butter rectangle. Be very careful when rolling this butter rectangle out. The rectangle shouldn’t be over rolled on any one side, as this would distort the rectangular formation. I recommend alternating the orientation of the rolling pin from vertical to horizontal several times through this process. See 2:04 to get an idea of what we did for ours. We had a pretty imperfect rectangle, so I wouldn’t be discouraged if yours comes out a bit wonky looking. However, don’t veer too far off the intended rectangle, and definitely try your best to attain that shape! Refrigerate the dough until use. This is important. You do not want this butter to be melty in the slightest, as the kitchen itself already has heat. This heat will soften your butter with time, but this butter sheet needs to be very firm! Flour your work surface, whether that be directly on your countertop or on a large tray (like ours), and roll out the dough into a rectangle that’s about 5 millimeters thick. The other dimensions are a little bit more up to you, because a bunch of different recipes give different sizes. Just make sure that the height of the dough rectangle is about equal to the width of the butter sheet. To clarify, the width is the longest side (in reference to either the individual butter or dough sheet). The height is the shorter dimension. Place your butter sheet in the center of the dough rectangle. This butter sheet should be ⅓ of the dough - you can think of the dough not currently in contact with the butter as flaps! These flaps should be just slightly larger than the butter sheet rectangle. Fold these two flaps over the butter sheet one after another, similar to how a letter is folded. Now, move your rolling pin vertically (the “height” or shorter side of the dough should be closest to you) to form another rectangle that is similar sized to the dimensions of the original dough rectangle. Fold the dough rectangle like a letter again (thirds!) Place it on a tray, and wrap the tray in plastic wrap. Refrigerate for one hour. This step needs to be repeated 3 times, meaning four times in addition to the previous step! Move your rolling pin vertically (the “height” or shorter side of the dough should be closest to you) to form another rectangle that is similar sized to the dimensions of the original dough rectangle. Fold the dough rectangle like a letter (in thirds). Place it on a tray, and wrap the tray in plastic wrap. Refrigerate for one hour, with the exception of the fourth time. Refrigerate (at least) overnight only for the fourth (final) time. Split the dough in half - freeze one half if you plan on using it another time. Roll the dough halves into long, ¼ inch thick rectangles. Cut each rectangle into triangles (more like an isosceles). They really can be any length you want, but you can probably cut 4-12 from each half. Use a rolling pin to “flatten” each triangle from the wide side up. Stretch out the skinny side and begin rolling your triangle as tightly as possible! Place each triangle 1 to 2 inches apart on a baking sheet lined with parchment paper. Let the croissants rise a bit for one more hour - you’re almost there! Brush them with egg wash. You can also roll them ahead of time, then refrigerate for up to 18 hours prior to baking. Wrap the baking with plastic wrap, not tightly or loosely, but just tight enough so as little moisture as possible escapes. Preheat the oven to 400°F. Get those croissants in the oven and bake for 8 to 12 minutes at 400°F, then turn down the heat to 375°F and bake them for another 8 to 12 minutes. They should be golden brown! Enjoy with whatever spreads, jams, sauces, and anything you like! We tried them with several fruit jams (blueberry, fig, strawberry, and more). Yes, this is a loooonnnnngggggg process, but I can confidently say the end result is worth it. My sister made them without me one additional time after the filming of this video, and I enjoyed them so much. They are FAR from perfect, but are still an unbelievably good treat. Warning: they ARE buttery, but equally flaky. Now, start the recipe and devour these little pockets of goodness! FINAL RESULTS!🤩 They look like they have such a solid bottom, because we over egg-washed - no worries if this happens to you, as they’re still awesome.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/recipes/croissant/croissantportrait1.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/recipes/croissant/croissantportrait1.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">IRVINS x BOPOMOFO</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/stories/irvins-bopomofo" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="IRVINS x BOPOMOFO" /><published>2020-12-09T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2020-12-09T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/stories/irvins-bopomofo</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/stories/irvins-bopomofo">&lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/stories/irvins/irvins5.JPEG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/stories/irvins/irvins2.JPEG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m honored and ecstatic to finally announce that I’m a partner for the exclusive launch of IRVINS Salted Egg Salmon Fish Skin chips in North America!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://eatirvins.com/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;IRVINS Salted Egg&lt;/a&gt; chips turned a signature &lt;em&gt;Salted Egg Crab&lt;/em&gt; dish, which became a local River Valley phenomenon, into some #DangerouslyAddictive snacks. As they say on their website,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;tldr-started-from-a-restaurant-now-theyre-here&quot;&gt;TLDR: Started from a restaurant. Now [&lt;em&gt;they’re&lt;/em&gt;] here.&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had the privilege of travelling to Singapore for a few days in 2018, as its proximity to Guangzhou (where my dad grew up) made it an ideal getaway during my summer in China. Singapore was certainly on my bucket list, primarily for the hawker stands. But WOW, I was completely blown away by the country (island city-state?) - I would take the opportunity to live there in a heartbeat. Okay, probably with further research, too, but you get the point - Singapore felt like home! The humidity would likely be the greatest turn off for most, but I’m pretty indifferent to it. It didn’t feel humid when I was there, so I may just not have that weather association to Singapore, though.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;quick-singapore-facts-singapore-is-majority-ethnic-chinese-with-malay-and-indian-populations-making-up-the-subsequent-major-demographics-singapore-is-also-known-for-being-religiously-diverse&quot;&gt;Quick Singapore Facts: Singapore is majority ethnic Chinese, with Malay and Indian populations making up the subsequent major demographics. Singapore is also known for being religiously diverse.&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being Chinese-American, I feel seen in Singapore, and since I speak English, it’s pretty easy to get around. I hope I can return one day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, back to the stuff about deez chips! You know the basic origin story of IRVINS, and the company now has brick and mortar stores in Southeast Asia. IRVINS is finally ~making their way to the US~, and small businesses, like &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bopomofocafe.com/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;BOPOMOFO Café&lt;/a&gt; are partnering with the company to distribute their wonderful products!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;BOPOMOFO&lt;/em&gt; represents the “Chinese ABCs”. The café seeks to unite and uplift the Asian-American community through food, drink, design, and hospitality - not too far from what I hope food can do for the people I’m with!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/stories/irvins/antoniaphil.JPG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Antonia and Phil @ BPMF&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/stories/irvins/antoniaphildan.JPG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Antonia, Dan, and Phil&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Their food and drink celebrate the identity many Asian-Americans struggle with their whole lives: being too Asian to do or be x, y, or z, but not Asian enough to feel fully accepted by family members “in the motherland”. Dishes, like mapo tofu tater tots, combine the foods you ate at home with the ones from your school cafeteria. Homemade lunches were “too exotic” or “smelly”, yet you craved those flavors when you no longer brought them to school in fear of being made fun of. You start to get used to the chicken fingers and fries at school, and heck, you even start to like them. And that’s okay! BOPOMOFO embraces that and lets you know you’re not alone when you’re in their company. I’ve never eaten there, but Antonia goes to college very close by, and she got the opportunity to meet Phil, BOPOMOFO’s co-owner that you may recognize from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/user/WongFuProductions&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Wong Fu Productions&lt;/a&gt;, a true pioneer in Asian-American media. Antonia raves about their food, and I trust her taste. BOPOMOFO has become integral to the San Gabriel Valley (the 626 and beyond) community, and they’re aware of the platform they have and are using it for good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, they’ve partnered with IRVINS as one of the limited distributors of the Salted Egg Salmon Fish Skins! The fish skins are extremely popular in Southeast Asia, but the salmon fish skin was created specifically for American and Canadian taste buds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They are, indeed, #DANGEROUSLYADDICTIVE. I am not a huge fish skin person, but these chips could change that for me. The buzz word, &lt;em&gt;umami&lt;/em&gt;, is the best way to describe these.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/stories/irvins/irvins1.JPEG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/stories/irvins/irvins4.JPEG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They’re made with the following ultra-fresh ingredients, straight from their website:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Salted duck egg yolk, a familiar ingredient commonly used in Asian dishes.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Curry leaves, bringing out the fragrance in our snacks.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Red chili pepper, giving our snacks a slight kick while enhancing the salted egg taste.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some might be frightened by the idea of a fried fish skin, but PLEASE don’t knock it until you try it. I know some of my followers may be vegetarian or vegan, so I understand that this product may not fit all dietary restrictions. But if you don’t have any, give them a shot - they’re a true delicacy worth every bite. Enter my giveaway or &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bopomofocafe.com/market&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;order them from BOPOMOFO&lt;/a&gt; today. My giveaway closes December 16th at 5:00PM EST, and you can enter as many times as you’d like by tagging a different friend in separate comments. Sharing my giveaway post on your story will also grant an extra entry! Full details &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/carissaeats/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;on the post&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/stories/irvins/enjoyirvins.JPEG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/stories/irvins/irvins3.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;📣GO SUPPORT IRVINS AND BOPOMOFO📣&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/stories/irvins/btsirvins.JPEG&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;BTS of Photoshoot (ft. Cheese Puff Tiger)&lt;/div&gt;    
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="stories" /><summary type="html">I’m honored and ecstatic to finally announce that I’m a partner for the exclusive launch of IRVINS Salted Egg Salmon Fish Skin chips in North America! IRVINS Salted Egg chips turned a signature Salted Egg Crab dish, which became a local River Valley phenomenon, into some #DangerouslyAddictive snacks. As they say on their website, TLDR: Started from a restaurant. Now [they’re] here. I had the privilege of travelling to Singapore for a few days in 2018, as its proximity to Guangzhou (where my dad grew up) made it an ideal getaway during my summer in China. Singapore was certainly on my bucket list, primarily for the hawker stands. But WOW, I was completely blown away by the country (island city-state?) - I would take the opportunity to live there in a heartbeat. Okay, probably with further research, too, but you get the point - Singapore felt like home! The humidity would likely be the greatest turn off for most, but I’m pretty indifferent to it. It didn’t feel humid when I was there, so I may just not have that weather association to Singapore, though. Quick Singapore Facts: Singapore is majority ethnic Chinese, with Malay and Indian populations making up the subsequent major demographics. Singapore is also known for being religiously diverse. Being Chinese-American, I feel seen in Singapore, and since I speak English, it’s pretty easy to get around. I hope I can return one day. Now, back to the stuff about deez chips! You know the basic origin story of IRVINS, and the company now has brick and mortar stores in Southeast Asia. IRVINS is finally ~making their way to the US~, and small businesses, like BOPOMOFO Café are partnering with the company to distribute their wonderful products! BOPOMOFO represents the “Chinese ABCs”. The café seeks to unite and uplift the Asian-American community through food, drink, design, and hospitality - not too far from what I hope food can do for the people I’m with! Antonia and Phil @ BPMF Antonia, Dan, and Phil Their food and drink celebrate the identity many Asian-Americans struggle with their whole lives: being too Asian to do or be x, y, or z, but not Asian enough to feel fully accepted by family members “in the motherland”. Dishes, like mapo tofu tater tots, combine the foods you ate at home with the ones from your school cafeteria. Homemade lunches were “too exotic” or “smelly”, yet you craved those flavors when you no longer brought them to school in fear of being made fun of. You start to get used to the chicken fingers and fries at school, and heck, you even start to like them. And that’s okay! BOPOMOFO embraces that and lets you know you’re not alone when you’re in their company. I’ve never eaten there, but Antonia goes to college very close by, and she got the opportunity to meet Phil, BOPOMOFO’s co-owner that you may recognize from Wong Fu Productions, a true pioneer in Asian-American media. Antonia raves about their food, and I trust her taste. BOPOMOFO has become integral to the San Gabriel Valley (the 626 and beyond) community, and they’re aware of the platform they have and are using it for good. So, they’ve partnered with IRVINS as one of the limited distributors of the Salted Egg Salmon Fish Skins! The fish skins are extremely popular in Southeast Asia, but the salmon fish skin was created specifically for American and Canadian taste buds. They are, indeed, #DANGEROUSLYADDICTIVE. I am not a huge fish skin person, but these chips could change that for me. The buzz word, umami, is the best way to describe these. They’re made with the following ultra-fresh ingredients, straight from their website: Salted duck egg yolk, a familiar ingredient commonly used in Asian dishes. Curry leaves, bringing out the fragrance in our snacks. Red chili pepper, giving our snacks a slight kick while enhancing the salted egg taste. Some might be frightened by the idea of a fried fish skin, but PLEASE don’t knock it until you try it. I know some of my followers may be vegetarian or vegan, so I understand that this product may not fit all dietary restrictions. But if you don’t have any, give them a shot - they’re a true delicacy worth every bite. Enter my giveaway or order them from BOPOMOFO today. My giveaway closes December 16th at 5:00PM EST, and you can enter as many times as you’d like by tagging a different friend in separate comments. Sharing my giveaway post on your story will also grant an extra entry! Full details on the post. 📣GO SUPPORT IRVINS AND BOPOMOFO📣 BTS of Photoshoot (ft. Cheese Puff Tiger)</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/stories/irvins/irvins2.JPEG" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/stories/irvins/irvins2.JPEG" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Turkey Day 🥧</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/stories/thanksgiving" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Turkey Day 🥧" /><published>2020-11-26T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2020-11-26T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/stories/thanksgiving</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/stories/thanksgiving">&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/stories/thanksgiving/pumpkinpie.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Happy Turkey Day y’all! I wanted to say what I’m thankful for, recap how I celebrated for the past few years (and what I’m doing today), and share some Thanksgiving recipes from my favorite food bloggers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So what does Thanksgiving mean to me?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;i-want-to-preface-this-by-saying-this-post-is-about-what-im-grateful-for-and-what-ive-done-on-thanksgiving-day-for-the-past-few-years-you-can-practice-gratitude-while-still-acknowledging-thanksgivings-problematic-history--in-what-the-day-represents-to-indigenous-people--and-there-are-so-many-resources-out-there-to-educate-yourself-and-stop-perpetuating-the-myths-we-grew-up-learning&quot;&gt;I want to preface this by saying this post is about what I’m grateful for, and what I’ve done on Thanksgiving Day for the past few years. You can practice gratitude, while still acknowledging Thanksgiving’s problematic history – in what the day represents to Indigenous people – and there are so many resources out there to educate yourself and stop perpetuating the myths we grew up learning.&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In elementary and part of middle school, the Chinese community in my town would frequently have get-togethers (we used to hang out a lot!), and I would always look forward to the main event of the year: Thanksgiving dinner. Most, if not all of us (my town’s Chinese community), don’t have any extended family in the states, so our communal heritage brought us even closer as friends. As the years passed, though, we’ve lowered it on our priorities list. Quarantine makes me feel even more nostalgic about those times, but I remain hopeful about seeing them in the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But anyway…in the past few years, I’ve felt the magic of this four-day weekend fizzle out, but I still feel an immense appreciation for this quick getaway from the hecticness of school. I also spend this time to share my gratitude for people who’ve made a remarkable impact in my life in the past 11 months.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For 2020, I have a lot to be grateful for. Yes, it’s been a rough year; I’ve had to be on lockdown completely for the past eight months and be &lt;em&gt;almost excessively&lt;/em&gt; cautious, because I live with my grandma. It has definitely taken a toll on me, but I’ve had time to reflect on myself about many aspects of my life. This isn’t my journal, so I don’t want to delve in too deep, but I still want to share a a short list of the many things I’ve been especially thankful for this year…here it is:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I’ve gotten to cultivate a relationship with my dad that wouldn’t have had the time to be nurtured in other circumstances (and that is &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; to take away from how this pandemic has impacted millions; COVID-19 to have never happened would be ideal). Have we had our &lt;em&gt;very fair&lt;/em&gt; share of quarrels and times we’ve needed to spend apart? Absolutely. But I learned to empathize with him like I had never before, and that’s just one thing to be thankful for.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Simply having the privilege to stay at home. My dad’s been working from home for at least 15 years now, so our family situation was minimally affected. Please wear a mask &lt;em&gt;if&lt;/em&gt; you choose to see anyone outside the people you live with – do it for the people who do not have the privilege to stay at home (essential and frontline workers).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;This. blog. I have no idea what 2020 would be without this. Even if no one is reading this, I am incredibly lucky to use this platform as a way to share my stories behind food and the businesses I want to share. I’m not too caught up with the size of my audience, because I do this for myself and my passion for culinary adventures. Building this blog from scratch is my ultimate passion project: there’s always something to be done, whether it’s the inner framework, the CSS design, the stories. And I cherish every moment with it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/stories/thanksgiving/shackfuyupork.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;
        Iberico Pork Pluma
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 2016, my dad, Antonia, and I took our first trip in quite some time after we had a big event in our life happen earlier in the year. On Thanksgiving Day 2016, we headed to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bonedaddies.com/restaurant/shackfuyu/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Shack-Fuyu: The Japanese Restaurant by Bone Daddies&lt;/a&gt;. I kid you not, returning to this place is on my bucket list. Shack-Fuyu is the type of sit-down restaurant I’m most into - a spin on East Asian food with signature dishes and desserts. This spin doesn’t need to be a “modern” take, but needs to have a connection to the chef, in whichever way that may be. This dish is the Iberico Pork Pluma with Spring Onion and Black Pepper Miso. Get the Kinako French Toast with Matcha Soft Serve too. &lt;em&gt;Absolute chef’s kiss&lt;/em&gt;…okay, back to the Thanksgiving stuff. I went off on a tangent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/stories/thanksgiving/chickiesandpetes.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Crab Fries from Chickie’s &amp;amp; Pete’s, Philly Airport (2018)&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/stories/thanksgiving/becbagel2.JPG&quot; height=&quot;150px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Bacon, Egg, Cheese Bagel from Celebrity Bagels (2019)&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 2017, I remember it being a Chinese get together. It’s only a vague memory, but my dad made a point about this gathering being one of my sister’s last before heading off to college. In 2018, my dad and I were on a flight to visit Antonia! We flew from the Philly airport (far cheaper than from JFK), so that day was just getting to the airport, waiting (we ate crab fries 😋), flying, and eating at pretty much the only restaurant still open on Thanksgiving day (a Hong Kong café, IIRC). That weekend remains one of the favorite times in my life thus far. I was “homesick” for my sister, and it couldn’t have been a better getaway. Last year, I spent it by eating a BEC from Celebrity Bagels and just watching Netflix. This year will probably be similar: I’ll be eating some good food, taking a break, and hanging with Antonia. And I cannot wait.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To finish off, I want to share some Thanksgiving recipes from my favorite food bloggers. Some are more traditional, but some may be unexpected combinations or fusion flavors. Enjoy (even if it may be too late to try these out for this year)!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://seonkyounglongest.com/fried-rice-stuffing/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Fried Rice Stuffing&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;I’ve been a &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://seonkyounglongest.com/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Seonkyoung Longest&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; fan since the beginning! Her backstory is not without its challenges, but is inspiring when you see where she is today. She creates Korean, Chinese, and Japanese favorites, but also makes more experimental recipes like this one. She has a &lt;a href=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Korean-glazed&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://seonkyounglongest.com/how-to-cook-lemongrass-turkey/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;lemongrass&lt;/a&gt; turkey and &lt;a href=&quot;https://seonkyounglongest.com/cranberry-sauce/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;~spicy~ cranberry sauce&lt;/a&gt; recipe to check out as well. Fried rice stuffing blends two of my identities together (I am Chinese-American after all!), so I’m definitely optimistic about the results!&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://iamafoodblog.com/green-bean-casserole/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Green Bean Casserole&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;The classic green bean casserole! I loveeeee the French-fried onions on the top of these. &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://iamafoodblog.com/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;i am a food blog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; makes a ton of Asian/Asian-inspired recipes, along with a variety of other cuisines. This husband-wife duo has a stunning blog that I’ve followed for years, and you’ll be endlessly scrolling through their recipe index (not complaining though). They also have a &lt;a href=&quot;https://iamafoodblog.com/thanksgiving/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;guide to downsize your Thanksgiving&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.halfbakedharvest.com/maple-pecan-sticky-buns/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Extra Sticky Maple Pecan Sticky Buns&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Like cinnamon rolls, but without the cream cheese frosting. It’s perfect for those with a lot of baking ingredients (flour, eggs, yeast, sugar, cinnamon, etc.), but don’t have cream cheese. I am those.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.halfbakedharvest.com/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Half Baked Harvest&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;feels&lt;/em&gt; exactly the way it should sound. It’s warm, comforting, and feels like home.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.halfbakedharvest.com/sweet-potato-pie-dutch-baby/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Sweet Potato Pie Dutch Baby&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Another &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.halfbakedharvest.com/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Half Baked Harvest&lt;/a&gt; one. A homey pie favorite turned into a pancake - can’t get better than that.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://mynameisyeh.com/mynameisyeh/2018/8/overnight-cinnamon-rolls-with-tahini-cream-frosting&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Cinnamon Rolls with Tahini Cream Frosting and Pistachio Rose Dukkah&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;These rolls &lt;em&gt;do&lt;/em&gt; have cream cheese frosting, but heck, this was too cool of a recipe not to share! &lt;a href=&quot;https://mynameisyeh.com&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Molly Yeh&lt;/a&gt; is a Jewish-Chinese musician turned cookbook author and farm girl. I’m sure she’s still a musician at her core, but I admire her most as an awesome food blogger with tons of narratives to share! She certainly draws inspiration from her experiences in all different walks of life, whether it be the city AND farm girl in her or her multiracial background.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/stories/thanksgiving/bmbcheesecake3.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250px&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m also enjoying this Cranberry and Goat Cheese Cheesecake from &lt;a href=&quot;https://mynameisyeh.com/mynameisyeh/2018/8/overnight-cinnamon-rolls-with-tahini-cream-frosting&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Black Magic Bakehouse&lt;/a&gt;. I may do a future post for it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ENJOY YOUR TURKEY DAY Y’ALL! 🦃 (turkey isn’t on everyone’s table, but the point isn’t any different 🥔) Stay safe, and I’m sending all my positivity your way!!!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="stories" /><summary type="html">Happy Turkey Day y’all! I wanted to say what I’m thankful for, recap how I celebrated for the past few years (and what I’m doing today), and share some Thanksgiving recipes from my favorite food bloggers. So what does Thanksgiving mean to me? I want to preface this by saying this post is about what I’m grateful for, and what I’ve done on Thanksgiving Day for the past few years. You can practice gratitude, while still acknowledging Thanksgiving’s problematic history – in what the day represents to Indigenous people – and there are so many resources out there to educate yourself and stop perpetuating the myths we grew up learning. In elementary and part of middle school, the Chinese community in my town would frequently have get-togethers (we used to hang out a lot!), and I would always look forward to the main event of the year: Thanksgiving dinner. Most, if not all of us (my town’s Chinese community), don’t have any extended family in the states, so our communal heritage brought us even closer as friends. As the years passed, though, we’ve lowered it on our priorities list. Quarantine makes me feel even more nostalgic about those times, but I remain hopeful about seeing them in the future. But anyway…in the past few years, I’ve felt the magic of this four-day weekend fizzle out, but I still feel an immense appreciation for this quick getaway from the hecticness of school. I also spend this time to share my gratitude for people who’ve made a remarkable impact in my life in the past 11 months. For 2020, I have a lot to be grateful for. Yes, it’s been a rough year; I’ve had to be on lockdown completely for the past eight months and be almost excessively cautious, because I live with my grandma. It has definitely taken a toll on me, but I’ve had time to reflect on myself about many aspects of my life. This isn’t my journal, so I don’t want to delve in too deep, but I still want to share a a short list of the many things I’ve been especially thankful for this year…here it is: I’ve gotten to cultivate a relationship with my dad that wouldn’t have had the time to be nurtured in other circumstances (and that is not to take away from how this pandemic has impacted millions; COVID-19 to have never happened would be ideal). Have we had our very fair share of quarrels and times we’ve needed to spend apart? Absolutely. But I learned to empathize with him like I had never before, and that’s just one thing to be thankful for. Simply having the privilege to stay at home. My dad’s been working from home for at least 15 years now, so our family situation was minimally affected. Please wear a mask if you choose to see anyone outside the people you live with – do it for the people who do not have the privilege to stay at home (essential and frontline workers). This. blog. I have no idea what 2020 would be without this. Even if no one is reading this, I am incredibly lucky to use this platform as a way to share my stories behind food and the businesses I want to share. I’m not too caught up with the size of my audience, because I do this for myself and my passion for culinary adventures. Building this blog from scratch is my ultimate passion project: there’s always something to be done, whether it’s the inner framework, the CSS design, the stories. And I cherish every moment with it. Iberico Pork Pluma In 2016, my dad, Antonia, and I took our first trip in quite some time after we had a big event in our life happen earlier in the year. On Thanksgiving Day 2016, we headed to Shack-Fuyu: The Japanese Restaurant by Bone Daddies. I kid you not, returning to this place is on my bucket list. Shack-Fuyu is the type of sit-down restaurant I’m most into - a spin on East Asian food with signature dishes and desserts. This spin doesn’t need to be a “modern” take, but needs to have a connection to the chef, in whichever way that may be. This dish is the Iberico Pork Pluma with Spring Onion and Black Pepper Miso. Get the Kinako French Toast with Matcha Soft Serve too. Absolute chef’s kiss…okay, back to the Thanksgiving stuff. I went off on a tangent. Crab Fries from Chickie’s &amp;amp; Pete’s, Philly Airport (2018) Bacon, Egg, Cheese Bagel from Celebrity Bagels (2019) In 2017, I remember it being a Chinese get together. It’s only a vague memory, but my dad made a point about this gathering being one of my sister’s last before heading off to college. In 2018, my dad and I were on a flight to visit Antonia! We flew from the Philly airport (far cheaper than from JFK), so that day was just getting to the airport, waiting (we ate crab fries 😋), flying, and eating at pretty much the only restaurant still open on Thanksgiving day (a Hong Kong café, IIRC). That weekend remains one of the favorite times in my life thus far. I was “homesick” for my sister, and it couldn’t have been a better getaway. Last year, I spent it by eating a BEC from Celebrity Bagels and just watching Netflix. This year will probably be similar: I’ll be eating some good food, taking a break, and hanging with Antonia. And I cannot wait. To finish off, I want to share some Thanksgiving recipes from my favorite food bloggers. Some are more traditional, but some may be unexpected combinations or fusion flavors. Enjoy (even if it may be too late to try these out for this year)! Fried Rice Stuffing I’ve been a Seonkyoung Longest fan since the beginning! Her backstory is not without its challenges, but is inspiring when you see where she is today. She creates Korean, Chinese, and Japanese favorites, but also makes more experimental recipes like this one. She has a Korean-glazed and lemongrass turkey and ~spicy~ cranberry sauce recipe to check out as well. Fried rice stuffing blends two of my identities together (I am Chinese-American after all!), so I’m definitely optimistic about the results! Green Bean Casserole The classic green bean casserole! I loveeeee the French-fried onions on the top of these. i am a food blog makes a ton of Asian/Asian-inspired recipes, along with a variety of other cuisines. This husband-wife duo has a stunning blog that I’ve followed for years, and you’ll be endlessly scrolling through their recipe index (not complaining though). They also have a guide to downsize your Thanksgiving! Extra Sticky Maple Pecan Sticky Buns Like cinnamon rolls, but without the cream cheese frosting. It’s perfect for those with a lot of baking ingredients (flour, eggs, yeast, sugar, cinnamon, etc.), but don’t have cream cheese. I am those. Half Baked Harvest feels exactly the way it should sound. It’s warm, comforting, and feels like home. Sweet Potato Pie Dutch Baby Another Half Baked Harvest one. A homey pie favorite turned into a pancake - can’t get better than that. Cinnamon Rolls with Tahini Cream Frosting and Pistachio Rose Dukkah These rolls do have cream cheese frosting, but heck, this was too cool of a recipe not to share! Molly Yeh is a Jewish-Chinese musician turned cookbook author and farm girl. I’m sure she’s still a musician at her core, but I admire her most as an awesome food blogger with tons of narratives to share! She certainly draws inspiration from her experiences in all different walks of life, whether it be the city AND farm girl in her or her multiracial background. I’m also enjoying this Cranberry and Goat Cheese Cheesecake from Black Magic Bakehouse. I may do a future post for it! ENJOY YOUR TURKEY DAY Y’ALL! 🦃 (turkey isn’t on everyone’s table, but the point isn’t any different 🥔) Stay safe, and I’m sending all my positivity your way!!!</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/stories/thanksgiving/pumpkinpie.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/stories/thanksgiving/pumpkinpie.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry></feed>