<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2024-10-11T22:17:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">CarissaEats</title><subtitle>A food and travel blog by @CarissaEats, where I share my favorite small businesses, easy recipes, and travel adventures.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Bridgetown Roti</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/losangeleseats/bridgetown-roti" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Bridgetown Roti" /><published>2024-10-11T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2024-10-11T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/losangeleseats/bridgetown-roti</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/losangeleseats/bridgetown-roti">&lt;p&gt;This love letter was light on letters, heavy on love (and flavor).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img class=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/laeats/bridgetownroti/bridgetown-roti-spread-2.jpeg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From Los Angeles to the Caribbean, chef Rashida Holmes pays homage to her Afro-Caribbean roots with this Bajan and Trinidadian family-run spot. I was immediately greeted with a mural of exactly who they are and what they stand for: joy, flavor, love, heritage, innovation, and community. No restaurant &lt;em&gt;has&lt;/em&gt; to share their values, but Bridgetown Roti’s effort to share theirs set me up with the comforting energy I needed for the feast I was about to enjoy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I first stumbled upon Bridgetown Roti back in September 2022, when the concept was just a pop-up achieving their dreams and accomplishing even more. Appearing as a local celebrity chef at the USC Annenberg 50th Anniversary evening celebration, Rashida served up small plates of green curry head-on shrimp &amp;amp; cucumber chutney roti chips, curried yam and mango mini patties, and pineapple upside-down cake.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img class=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/laeats/bridgetownroti/annenberg-50-bridgetown-dish.jpeg&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;
    (Left) Patty, (Right) Roti Chip, (Back) Pineapple Cake
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Perhaps I ate this plate a little too long ago to have a solid review of it, but I will say this much – after eating Rashida’s food that day, I have been a loyal fan, previously mapping out a multiple bus route to their former residence in the shared space, Crafted Kitchen, and staying posted for updates on the brick-and-mortar Rashida dreamed of opening.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img class=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/laeats/bridgetownroti/bridgetown-roti-front.JPG&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img class=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/laeats/bridgetownroti/bridgetown-roti-patty-display.jpeg&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And this dream took &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/p/C9d4WskvECr/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;official flight on July 20th, 2024&lt;/a&gt;! Big day for Bridgetown Roti fans. So on my first brick-and-mortar visit just a week ago, I felt honored to be the first customer of the day! Truthfully, I do love me some takeout, but I figured it was worthwhile to stay in the environment I had waited so long to enjoy her food in. Lined with vibrant decorative Bahama shutters and a massive patty warmer, Bridgetown Roti convinces you to stay without even asking. After all, the establishment is set up as a counter-serve, so its purpose is more of a good time rather than a long time. But once the beautifully arranged tray of food arrived, I sat peacefully in my decision to stay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img class=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/laeats/bridgetownroti/bridgetown-roti-menu.JPG&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was devastated to find out that their doubles, which are staples of Trinidadian cuisine, were only served on Sundays and Mondays, but like any place I dearly love – one item missed just means one more reason to return. At a place with enough options to make my indecision sound off, no doubles, no problem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;red-pepper-goat-roti-w-peanut-sauce&quot;&gt;Red Pepper Goat Roti w/ Peanut Sauce&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img class=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/laeats/bridgetownroti/bridgetown-roti-goat-roti-1.JPG&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;
      Smoked Goat Shoulder, Peanut Sauce, Crispy Weiser Potatoes, Turmeric Spiced Slaw, Cilantro, and Scallions ($18)
    &lt;/div&gt;    
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The handmade roti is flaky, with an unmistakable fat-laden composition to it. I was trying to figure out if it was vegetable shortening, oil, ghee, or butter, but this &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GqbSUuYDjuU&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Eater video&lt;/a&gt; with Rashida cooking up this exact dish shows her use of butter. Scraping softened butter with her fingers and rubbing it across the top of the roti, Rashida demonstrates food is a labor of love. While other parts of the roti-making process require scales to produce exact measurements – like when Rashida measures out exactly 120 grams of dough – the amount of butter to add is something she just feels out with her own ten fingers. A thin wrap would not be able to withstand the saucy goat, cooked two ways, but a thick wrap would dominate the dish in which multiple elements should share the spotlight. Rashida, the master of roti, finds the perfect balance. And after hours of sitting in my fridge, the leftover half of this wrap was still perfectly intact – minimal roti was soaked in the juices, and it did not disintegrate like other wraps that fail the test of time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The tender red pepper goat, seasoned with Rashida’s curry blend that she purposefully proportioned, was accented by the aforementioned peanut sauce. My immediate reaction was a desire for a stronger peanut taste (I love peanuts), but I remembered there were more guests at this party to make room for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img class=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/laeats/bridgetownroti/bridgetown-roti-goat-roti-2.jpeg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rashida also explains in the video that the fried potato is an ode to the potatoes in traditional curries. I loved this twist (and crisp), but found myself wishing that this curry-inspired potato remembered its roots a bit more. In potato curries, the potatoes are like sponges, soaking in every dimension of the broth and infused with spice in most bites. I would want this potato to be smothered with one more gesture of love. But if my only critique of this wrap was a slightly under seasoned potato, then we might as well be splitting hairs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This roti was decadent, but the ample portion of slaw stuffed inside this juicy wrap was like the sun peeking out of an already delicious rainbow; the roti is a beautiful sight (and eat) itself, but with a necessary brightness we all cherish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;oxtail-and-peppers-patty&quot;&gt;Oxtail and Peppers Patty&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img class=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/laeats/bridgetownroti/bridgetown-roti-oxtail-patty-1.jpeg&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;
    Curry Braised Oxtail, Green Pepper Sofrito ($8)
  &lt;/div&gt;    
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since I was already committed to a roti with pulled meat, I was initially leaning towards the green curry shrimp patty in hopes of diversifying my protein for this meal. As much as I wish I could say all my choices were original opinions, I fell victim to the crowd’s opinions – the ones found on no other than TikTok – and the people said I could &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; miss the oxtail patty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img class=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/laeats/bridgetownroti/bridgetown-roti-oxtail-patty-2.jpeg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And the people were very correct. The oxtail patty was delightful, and out of all the dishes, the Indian impact in Caribbean cuisine was highlighted most in this one. It was reminiscent of the mutton curries I had previously eaten at Indian restaurants, but enveloped in a turmeric-tinted crumbly pastry. When the British moved enslaved Africans over to America following the abolishment of slavery in Caribbean British colonies, the British exploited and brought hundreds of thousands of Indians to nations, like Barbados and Trinidad, in the 1800s to be indentured laborers. In the words of Rashida, “They brought their breads, they brought their curries, they brought everything there, and kind of created this new cuisine with the local tropical fruit and everything that was already there.” Oxtail is a staple ingredient in Caribbean cuisine, and this patty is an emblem of this culture blend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;curried-yam-and-mango-with-coconut-patty&quot;&gt;Curried Yam and Mango with Coconut Patty&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img class=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/laeats/bridgetownroti/bridgetown-roti-mango-sweet-potato-patty.jpeg&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;
    Red Pepper Sofrito and Young Coconut Chutney ($8)
  &lt;/div&gt;    
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some might be craving a spicy dish – I like heat, but I can only tolerate it in small amounts. But you can certainly find it in their optional sauces, or &lt;em&gt;maybe&lt;/em&gt; as a surprise in some dishes. Where else is the heat, you might ask? Well, that would be the dark horse. Pair my favorite fruit with my favorite vegetable, and there you have it: the curried yam and mango with coconut patty. The mango plays second fiddle to the yam, but the sweetness it adds is the kind you can only get from a mango at its prime. The heat level of this patty will not send you into a frenzy, but it may give you a kick if you don’t expect it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;sweet-and-spicy-plantains&quot;&gt;Sweet and Spicy Plantains&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img class=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/laeats/bridgetownroti/bridgetown-roti-plantains.jpeg&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;
    Tamarind, Turmeric Curry Powder ($7)
  &lt;/div&gt;  
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another unexpected revelation from this meal? How unique a dish of fried plantains could taste. I am a simple girl – I see plantains on the menu, I order the plantains. Yet these plantains are bursting with flavors throughout. While plantains have a natural sweetness to them, the addition of tamarind penetrates with both a sticky sweetness and sharp acidity that keeps this dish firmly on the savory side. Paired with curry powder…give this dish Plantains of the Year, stat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;pigeon-peas-and-rice&quot;&gt;Pigeon Peas and Rice&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img class=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/laeats/bridgetownroti/bridgetown-roti-pigeon-peas-1.JPG&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;
    Pigeon Peas, Rice, Grated Tomato, and Fried Okra ($7)
  &lt;/div&gt;  
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I ordered the pigeon peas, because of their popularity in Caribbean cuisine, but the biggest surprise of this dish was how it flipped okra on its head for me. Okra is one of the more divisive vegetables out there – people say you either love it or hate it – yet I have always been the in-between. I have been impartial to either side, but never paid much attention to it. But here, I adored the addition of fried, thin slices of okra, because the method of preparation reduced the sliminess that makes people hate it. It was as good as a tasty fried potato – the kind that only requires a perfect pinch of salt to make it shine. My only note would be to add more grated tomato – this dish needed that natural brightness, and because of the acidity present in tomatoes, grating it let that acid come through quite nicely.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img class=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/laeats/bridgetownroti/bridgetown-roti-spread-1.JPG&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Somehow I felt so invested in this restaurant’s success, even though I knew it would likely be just fine. Rashida is a highly acclaimed chef, recognized by the James Beard Foundation and widely respected by publications – both food-specific and general ones – across the nation. But Bridgetown Roti stands out, because it is not every day I see a Caribbean restaurant and chef get their flowers in an industry that tends to prioritize fine dining curated by chefs who master French techniques. Many Americans take advantage of the Caribbean’s proximity for their yearly holiday, yet less remember Caribbean nations are home to rich, storied histories beyond their pristine beaches. Folks go to these beautiful oases and enjoy hospitality as a getaway from the hardships of their lives, but the same folks must remember there are real humans behind each of their vacation experiences – communities who carry legacies of happiness, community, and resilience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So what can we do to support and appreciate the greater Caribbean diaspora? We can start by learning the history of the West Indies / Caribbean – its history as nations colonized by the British is directly linked with America’s past. We can amplify Caribbean-owned businesses, like Bridgetown Roti, particularly in spaces where their accomplishments are not usually celebrated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you remember back to Bridgetown Roti’s values, joy stood at number one. Joy is an act of resilience, and the one value that ignites the other five listed. At Bridgetown Roti, joy is an ingredient you can experience with all five senses: the sound of laughter amongst the tight-knit crew, the smell of curried aromas, the taste of spiced goat stewed for hours on end, the feel of a hand-buttered roti, and the sight of diners who traveled from all over to enjoy a bite of Rashida’s recipes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img class=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/laeats/bridgetownroti/bridgetown-roti-wallpaper.jpeg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was the loveliest letter to enjoy, Rashida. Thank you, and I hope my letter &lt;em&gt;to you&lt;/em&gt; shows how special you are to this one college student. From Carissa to Bridgetown Roti, much love!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="losangeleseats" /><summary type="html">This love letter was light on letters, heavy on love (and flavor). From Los Angeles to the Caribbean, chef Rashida Holmes pays homage to her Afro-Caribbean roots with this Bajan and Trinidadian family-run spot. I was immediately greeted with a mural of exactly who they are and what they stand for: joy, flavor, love, heritage, innovation, and community. No restaurant has to share their values, but Bridgetown Roti’s effort to share theirs set me up with the comforting energy I needed for the feast I was about to enjoy. I first stumbled upon Bridgetown Roti back in September 2022, when the concept was just a pop-up achieving their dreams and accomplishing even more. Appearing as a local celebrity chef at the USC Annenberg 50th Anniversary evening celebration, Rashida served up small plates of green curry head-on shrimp &amp;amp; cucumber chutney roti chips, curried yam and mango mini patties, and pineapple upside-down cake. (Left) Patty, (Right) Roti Chip, (Back) Pineapple Cake Perhaps I ate this plate a little too long ago to have a solid review of it, but I will say this much – after eating Rashida’s food that day, I have been a loyal fan, previously mapping out a multiple bus route to their former residence in the shared space, Crafted Kitchen, and staying posted for updates on the brick-and-mortar Rashida dreamed of opening. And this dream took official flight on July 20th, 2024! Big day for Bridgetown Roti fans. So on my first brick-and-mortar visit just a week ago, I felt honored to be the first customer of the day! Truthfully, I do love me some takeout, but I figured it was worthwhile to stay in the environment I had waited so long to enjoy her food in. Lined with vibrant decorative Bahama shutters and a massive patty warmer, Bridgetown Roti convinces you to stay without even asking. After all, the establishment is set up as a counter-serve, so its purpose is more of a good time rather than a long time. But once the beautifully arranged tray of food arrived, I sat peacefully in my decision to stay. I was devastated to find out that their doubles, which are staples of Trinidadian cuisine, were only served on Sundays and Mondays, but like any place I dearly love – one item missed just means one more reason to return. At a place with enough options to make my indecision sound off, no doubles, no problem. Red Pepper Goat Roti w/ Peanut Sauce Smoked Goat Shoulder, Peanut Sauce, Crispy Weiser Potatoes, Turmeric Spiced Slaw, Cilantro, and Scallions ($18) The handmade roti is flaky, with an unmistakable fat-laden composition to it. I was trying to figure out if it was vegetable shortening, oil, ghee, or butter, but this Eater video with Rashida cooking up this exact dish shows her use of butter. Scraping softened butter with her fingers and rubbing it across the top of the roti, Rashida demonstrates food is a labor of love. While other parts of the roti-making process require scales to produce exact measurements – like when Rashida measures out exactly 120 grams of dough – the amount of butter to add is something she just feels out with her own ten fingers. A thin wrap would not be able to withstand the saucy goat, cooked two ways, but a thick wrap would dominate the dish in which multiple elements should share the spotlight. Rashida, the master of roti, finds the perfect balance. And after hours of sitting in my fridge, the leftover half of this wrap was still perfectly intact – minimal roti was soaked in the juices, and it did not disintegrate like other wraps that fail the test of time. The tender red pepper goat, seasoned with Rashida’s curry blend that she purposefully proportioned, was accented by the aforementioned peanut sauce. My immediate reaction was a desire for a stronger peanut taste (I love peanuts), but I remembered there were more guests at this party to make room for. Rashida also explains in the video that the fried potato is an ode to the potatoes in traditional curries. I loved this twist (and crisp), but found myself wishing that this curry-inspired potato remembered its roots a bit more. In potato curries, the potatoes are like sponges, soaking in every dimension of the broth and infused with spice in most bites. I would want this potato to be smothered with one more gesture of love. But if my only critique of this wrap was a slightly under seasoned potato, then we might as well be splitting hairs. This roti was decadent, but the ample portion of slaw stuffed inside this juicy wrap was like the sun peeking out of an already delicious rainbow; the roti is a beautiful sight (and eat) itself, but with a necessary brightness we all cherish. Oxtail and Peppers Patty Curry Braised Oxtail, Green Pepper Sofrito ($8) Since I was already committed to a roti with pulled meat, I was initially leaning towards the green curry shrimp patty in hopes of diversifying my protein for this meal. As much as I wish I could say all my choices were original opinions, I fell victim to the crowd’s opinions – the ones found on no other than TikTok – and the people said I could not miss the oxtail patty. And the people were very correct. The oxtail patty was delightful, and out of all the dishes, the Indian impact in Caribbean cuisine was highlighted most in this one. It was reminiscent of the mutton curries I had previously eaten at Indian restaurants, but enveloped in a turmeric-tinted crumbly pastry. When the British moved enslaved Africans over to America following the abolishment of slavery in Caribbean British colonies, the British exploited and brought hundreds of thousands of Indians to nations, like Barbados and Trinidad, in the 1800s to be indentured laborers. In the words of Rashida, “They brought their breads, they brought their curries, they brought everything there, and kind of created this new cuisine with the local tropical fruit and everything that was already there.” Oxtail is a staple ingredient in Caribbean cuisine, and this patty is an emblem of this culture blend. Curried Yam and Mango with Coconut Patty Red Pepper Sofrito and Young Coconut Chutney ($8) Some might be craving a spicy dish – I like heat, but I can only tolerate it in small amounts. But you can certainly find it in their optional sauces, or maybe as a surprise in some dishes. Where else is the heat, you might ask? Well, that would be the dark horse. Pair my favorite fruit with my favorite vegetable, and there you have it: the curried yam and mango with coconut patty. The mango plays second fiddle to the yam, but the sweetness it adds is the kind you can only get from a mango at its prime. The heat level of this patty will not send you into a frenzy, but it may give you a kick if you don’t expect it. Sweet and Spicy Plantains Tamarind, Turmeric Curry Powder ($7) Another unexpected revelation from this meal? How unique a dish of fried plantains could taste. I am a simple girl – I see plantains on the menu, I order the plantains. Yet these plantains are bursting with flavors throughout. While plantains have a natural sweetness to them, the addition of tamarind penetrates with both a sticky sweetness and sharp acidity that keeps this dish firmly on the savory side. Paired with curry powder…give this dish Plantains of the Year, stat. Pigeon Peas and Rice Pigeon Peas, Rice, Grated Tomato, and Fried Okra ($7) I ordered the pigeon peas, because of their popularity in Caribbean cuisine, but the biggest surprise of this dish was how it flipped okra on its head for me. Okra is one of the more divisive vegetables out there – people say you either love it or hate it – yet I have always been the in-between. I have been impartial to either side, but never paid much attention to it. But here, I adored the addition of fried, thin slices of okra, because the method of preparation reduced the sliminess that makes people hate it. It was as good as a tasty fried potato – the kind that only requires a perfect pinch of salt to make it shine. My only note would be to add more grated tomato – this dish needed that natural brightness, and because of the acidity present in tomatoes, grating it let that acid come through quite nicely. Somehow I felt so invested in this restaurant’s success, even though I knew it would likely be just fine. Rashida is a highly acclaimed chef, recognized by the James Beard Foundation and widely respected by publications – both food-specific and general ones – across the nation. But Bridgetown Roti stands out, because it is not every day I see a Caribbean restaurant and chef get their flowers in an industry that tends to prioritize fine dining curated by chefs who master French techniques. Many Americans take advantage of the Caribbean’s proximity for their yearly holiday, yet less remember Caribbean nations are home to rich, storied histories beyond their pristine beaches. Folks go to these beautiful oases and enjoy hospitality as a getaway from the hardships of their lives, but the same folks must remember there are real humans behind each of their vacation experiences – communities who carry legacies of happiness, community, and resilience. So what can we do to support and appreciate the greater Caribbean diaspora? We can start by learning the history of the West Indies / Caribbean – its history as nations colonized by the British is directly linked with America’s past. We can amplify Caribbean-owned businesses, like Bridgetown Roti, particularly in spaces where their accomplishments are not usually celebrated. If you remember back to Bridgetown Roti’s values, joy stood at number one. Joy is an act of resilience, and the one value that ignites the other five listed. At Bridgetown Roti, joy is an ingredient you can experience with all five senses: the sound of laughter amongst the tight-knit crew, the smell of curried aromas, the taste of spiced goat stewed for hours on end, the feel of a hand-buttered roti, and the sight of diners who traveled from all over to enjoy a bite of Rashida’s recipes. This was the loveliest letter to enjoy, Rashida. Thank you, and I hope my letter to you shows how special you are to this one college student. From Carissa to Bridgetown Roti, much love!</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/laeats/bridgetownroti/bridgetown-roti-spread-2.jpeg" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/laeats/bridgetownroti/bridgetown-roti-spread-2.jpeg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Trojan Farmers Market</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/losangeleseats/usc-farmers-market" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trojan Farmers Market" /><published>2022-11-24T00:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2022-11-24T00:00:00-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/losangeleseats/usc-farmers-market</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/losangeleseats/usc-farmers-market">&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img class=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/laeats/trojan-farmers-market/scallop-dynamite-1.jpg&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;
        Scallop Dynamite
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every Wednesday, USC invites vendors who sell anything from jewelry, fresh-baked goods, locally-grown produce, sauces, dips, and prepared foods.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;jacks-thai-bbq&quot;&gt;Jack’s Thai BBQ&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img class=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/laeats/trojan-farmers-market/pad-thai-1.jpeg&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img class=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/laeats/trojan-farmers-market/thai-tea.jpeg&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you know me, you know I am a Trojan Farmers Market &lt;strong&gt;pad Thai&lt;/strong&gt; fan first, human second!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can order it with or without the chicken pictured, and it’s absolutely delicious either way. A full plate of pad Thai is $8, while a pad Thai + chicken runs at $13. The first time I had it, I could tell it had been sitting out for a while…yet it still tasted fantastic. The next few times, it came out looking as smooth and soft as it looks pictured here. If you like peanuts, I highly suggest eating the chicken with the peanut sauce they provide. The chicken is already so flavorful, but the peanut sauce balances it out by adding a dimension of sweetness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Their &lt;strong&gt;Thai tea&lt;/strong&gt; is also great! At $5, it is a bit on the pricier side, but on a 100° Wednesday, I never regret getting it if I can!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;pupusas-delmy&quot;&gt;Pupusas Delmy&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img class=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/laeats/trojan-farmers-market/pupusa-1.jpeg&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img class=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/laeats/trojan-farmers-market/pupusa-2.jpg&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These pupusas run at $4 apiece, regardless of the filling inside. I’ve tried the &lt;strong&gt;pupusas con pollo, vegetales, y queso&lt;/strong&gt; (chicken, vegetables, &amp;amp; cheese), as well as the &lt;strong&gt;pupusas con carne asada y queso&lt;/strong&gt; (steak &amp;amp; cheese). They are served with a side of curtido, a Salvadoran fermented cabbage, carrot, onion, and hot pepper slaw, as well as crema Salvadoreña if you’d like. Crispy, savory, and cheesy, pupusas make me feel so happy. I mean, just look at that crispy cheese skirt!! They’re a great grab-and-go meal on busy Wednesdays, making it convenient, filling, and satisfying.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;teppangeles&quot;&gt;Teppangeles&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img class=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/laeats/trojan-farmers-market/scallop-dynamite-2.jpeg&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img class=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/laeats/trojan-farmers-market/gyoza.jpg&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Life is (scallop) *dynamite*.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the most unique dish I’ve found at the farmers market. Get ready for an absolute flavor explosion, just like the name implies. The &lt;strong&gt;scallop dynamite&lt;/strong&gt; consists of teppanyaki-grilled mini scallops in garlic butter, along with mushrooms, onions, and broccoli. The scallops are all over a bed of rice, which ends up being as good as everyone’s favorite teppanyaki fried rice, because it soaks up all the caramelized bits and garlic butter from the scallops. It’s all topped off with roe too!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pictured on the right is the &lt;strong&gt;gyoza entree&lt;/strong&gt;, which is pretty straightforward, but very well-executed. I’m a big proponent of caramelization on my gyoza, and Teppangeles delivers. So good!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;gourmet-empanadas&quot;&gt;Gourmet Empanadas&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img class=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/laeats/trojan-farmers-market/empanadas.jpeg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;vanias-gogo-sauce&quot;&gt;Vania’s Gogo Sauce&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img class=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/laeats/trojan-farmers-market/vanias-onigiri-1.jpeg&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img class=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/laeats/trojan-farmers-market/vanias-onigiri-2.jpeg&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;aloha-hawaii-style-bbq&quot;&gt;Aloha Hawai’i Style BBQ&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img class=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/laeats/trojan-farmers-market/hawaiian-bbq-chicken-plate.jpeg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="losangeleseats" /><summary type="html">Scallop Dynamite Every Wednesday, USC invites vendors who sell anything from jewelry, fresh-baked goods, locally-grown produce, sauces, dips, and prepared foods. Jack’s Thai BBQ If you know me, you know I am a Trojan Farmers Market pad Thai fan first, human second! You can order it with or without the chicken pictured, and it’s absolutely delicious either way. A full plate of pad Thai is $8, while a pad Thai + chicken runs at $13. The first time I had it, I could tell it had been sitting out for a while…yet it still tasted fantastic. The next few times, it came out looking as smooth and soft as it looks pictured here. If you like peanuts, I highly suggest eating the chicken with the peanut sauce they provide. The chicken is already so flavorful, but the peanut sauce balances it out by adding a dimension of sweetness. Their Thai tea is also great! At $5, it is a bit on the pricier side, but on a 100° Wednesday, I never regret getting it if I can! Pupusas Delmy These pupusas run at $4 apiece, regardless of the filling inside. I’ve tried the pupusas con pollo, vegetales, y queso (chicken, vegetables, &amp;amp; cheese), as well as the pupusas con carne asada y queso (steak &amp;amp; cheese). They are served with a side of curtido, a Salvadoran fermented cabbage, carrot, onion, and hot pepper slaw, as well as crema Salvadoreña if you’d like. Crispy, savory, and cheesy, pupusas make me feel so happy. I mean, just look at that crispy cheese skirt!! They’re a great grab-and-go meal on busy Wednesdays, making it convenient, filling, and satisfying. Teppangeles Life is (scallop) *dynamite*. This is the most unique dish I’ve found at the farmers market. Get ready for an absolute flavor explosion, just like the name implies. The scallop dynamite consists of teppanyaki-grilled mini scallops in garlic butter, along with mushrooms, onions, and broccoli. The scallops are all over a bed of rice, which ends up being as good as everyone’s favorite teppanyaki fried rice, because it soaks up all the caramelized bits and garlic butter from the scallops. It’s all topped off with roe too! Pictured on the right is the gyoza entree, which is pretty straightforward, but very well-executed. I’m a big proponent of caramelization on my gyoza, and Teppangeles delivers. So good! Gourmet Empanadas Vania’s Gogo Sauce Aloha Hawai’i Style BBQ</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/laeats/trojan-farmers-market/scallop-dynamite-1.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/laeats/trojan-farmers-market/scallop-dynamite-1.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Ten Ten (Out of Ten)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/orlandoeats/ten-ten-seafood" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ten Ten (Out of Ten)" /><published>2022-11-24T00:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2022-11-24T00:00:00-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/orlandoeats/ten-ten-seafood</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/orlandoeats/ten-ten-seafood">&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img class=&quot;image&quot; id=&quot;bft-seafood&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/orlandoeats/ten-ten/bei-fung-tong-seafood.jpg&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;
        Bei Fung Tong Seafood
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meet the restaurant that made me realize how delicious the Cantonese food could be in Orlando.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And since my first time eating here, I’ve been nothing short of impressed by the Cantonese restaurants in this city.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you walk into a Chinese restaurant and “seafood” is part of its name, you can expect it to serve Cantonese cuisine specifically. This is likely because Guangzhou (also known as Canton) is located along the South China Sea, along with other cities in the Guangdong Province and Hong Kong. This prime location by the sea means the seafood in this region is always excellent, fresh, and pretty plentiful. Cantonese food is one of the most well-known Chinese cuisines in America — &lt;em&gt;dim sum&lt;/em&gt; is most frequently associated with Cantonese cuisine. Many of these seafood restaurants do dim sum services, whether it’s by ordering from a menu or waving down the people who push the iconic dim sum carts. &lt;strong&gt;Ten Ten Seafood and Grill&lt;/strong&gt; offers the beloved push cart service, so you’re never at a shortage of quick decisions needing to be made when you’re here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;ten-ten-or-tiāntiān-天天-means-every-day&quot;&gt;Ten Ten, or tiāntiān 天天, means every day.&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During fall of 2021, my family came here once or twice a week. It’s not uncommon for Cantonese people to go to dim sum daily. People go with two or three friends, and they split a pot of &lt;em&gt;cha&lt;/em&gt; and two or three dim sum dishes. Dim sum is designed to be shared — a steamer of &lt;em&gt;siu mai&lt;/em&gt; may come with three pieces, for example. People may go to dim sum as a morning or afternoon snack, making dim sum an easy, delicious excuse to catch up with friends. Whenever we went to Ten Ten, we saw many of the same people with the same trusty two or three steamers of dim sum.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ten Ten offers the beloved push cart service, so you’re never at a shortage of quick decisions needing to be made while you’re here. They not only offer basically every dim sum dish you’d want, but they also do it excellently. Might I make a case for the best egg tarts in Orlando, potentially in all of America? Continue scrolling to see what’s up 👀 However, like all dim sum restaurants, you can participate in picking dishes from the carts and/or order something to be prepared &lt;em&gt;a la carte&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s get to it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;har-cheung-fun-虾肠粉&quot;&gt;Har Cheung Fun 虾肠粉&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img class=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/orlandoeats/ten-ten/cheung-fun.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s so simple, but it will always be a favorite. This har cheung fun, or shrimp rice noodle roll, is one of the most popular dim sum dishes, and for a good reason. Rice noodle rolls can be filled with anything, whether it’s beef, char siu, or &lt;em&gt;youtiao&lt;/em&gt; (Chinese donut). Plus, once they’re topped with the sweet soy sauce, it’s hard to beat the simple, yet perfect match of rice rolls and sweet soy sauce. Regular soy sauce won’t do, yet to this day, I still don’t know exactly what kind of soy sauce dim sum restaurants use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ten Ten’s rice noodle rolls are well-executed, as the batter is always well-mixed, meaning the rolls are not too thick or too thin and are never doughy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;bean-curd-rolls-腐皮卷&quot;&gt;Bean Curd Rolls 腐皮卷&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img class=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/orlandoeats/ten-ten/bean-curd-rolls.jpeg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tofu skin rolls have mixed reviews in the Liu family. Personally, these weren’t always my favorite, but my sister loves them. However, I now also really like this dish now. The tofu skin rolls are deep-fried, which puffs up/activates some layers and gives it the flavor of fried food. However, they are then steamed, which makes these rolls soft and slightly chewy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;cantonese-style-seafood&quot;&gt;Cantonese-style Seafood&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img class=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/orlandoeats/ten-ten/ten-ten-seafood-plates.jpeg&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;
      Front: Bei Fung Tong Seafood; Back: Ginger Scallion Lobster
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I say there’s no other preparations of seafood I love more than these two, I mean it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The front dish, which is also &lt;a href=&quot;#bft-seafood&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;pictured at the top&lt;/a&gt;, is &lt;em&gt;bei fung tong&lt;/em&gt; 避风塘 style seafood. &lt;em&gt;Bei fung tong&lt;/em&gt; translates into “typhoon shelter,” because of how it originated in Hong Kong’s typhoon shelters. This preparation can be ordered with any choice of seafood, but we always get it with three kinds — scallops, shrimp, and squid. While every restaurant does this dish differently, Ten Ten’s is deep-fried and battered seafood that is then tossed with fried garlic, onions, scallions, and chilies. The result is an unbelievably aromatic, deep-fried pile of crispiness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The back dish is the classic Cantonese-style ginger scallion lobster, a common course in Cantonese banquet weddings. This deep-fried lobster is stir-fried in a ginger scallion-infused oil and is lightly seasoned with shaoxing wine and soy sauce. Ten Ten sometimes offers deals where they do these lobsters for around $25, although it is variable due to the ever-fluctuating market price of seafood. When these sales are offered, they’re a great opportunity to try out this incredible preparation of lobster.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;gon-chow-ngau-huo-乾炒牛河&quot;&gt;Gon Chow Ngau Huo 乾炒牛河&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img class=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/orlandoeats/ten-ten/beef-chow-fun-1.JPEG&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img class=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/orlandoeats/ten-ten/beef-chow-fun-2.JPEG&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also known as beef chow fun, this dish is a popular Cantonese dish that consists of wok-tossed rice noodles, soy sauce, thin steak, mung bean sprouts, onions, and scallions. The ingredients are so simple, but requires years of perfecting a technique, according to my dad. This is because chefs need to develop the &lt;em&gt;wok hei&lt;/em&gt;, or the “wok’s breath/air.” This &lt;a href=&quot;https://guide.michelin.com/en/article/dining-out/what-is-wok-hei&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;article on the Michelin Guide&lt;/a&gt; explains it quite well. To achieve &lt;em&gt;wok hei&lt;/em&gt;, chefs must use intense heat and have lots of stamina, because the food needs to be constantly tossed. While many professional chefs have little to no arm and hair, my dad always says Cantonese chefs are especially prone to this, because they constantly have their wrists/hands near the flames. Anyway, I digress. The &lt;em&gt;wok hei&lt;/em&gt; produces a unique smoky, often caramelized, savory taste — it’s something that needs to be experienced to understand. I’m hungry just thinking about all the dishes made with &lt;em&gt;wok hei&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ten Ten makes a great chow fun, and I can’t wait to go back home and eat it. Over these past few years, it’s landed at the top of my favorite food rankings. This is my dad’s favorite dish, and eating it with him has made me a superfan. For fellow cooked onion/scallion lovers, you will be satisfied!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;the-gon-chow-means-dry-stir-fried-which-means-the-thin-sauce-is-tossed-and-stir-fried-in-the-wok-wet-style-or-sup-chow-means-the-noodles-and-vegetables-are-all-wok-tossed-without-sauce-but-are-topped-with-a-soupier-thicker-sauce-upon-serving&quot;&gt;The &lt;em&gt;gon chow&lt;/em&gt; means dry stir-fried, which means the thin sauce is tossed and stir-fried in the wok. Wet-style, or &lt;em&gt;sup chow&lt;/em&gt;, means the noodles and vegetables are all wok-tossed without sauce, but are topped with a soupier, thicker sauce upon serving.&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;dan-tat-蛋挞&quot;&gt;Dan Tat 蛋挞&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img class=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/orlandoeats/ten-ten/egg-tart-1.jpeg&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img class=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/orlandoeats/ten-ten/egg-tart-2.jpeg&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes…the best egg tarts I’ve &lt;em&gt;ever&lt;/em&gt; had. Yes, they’re in Orlando, Florida. Please hold the chuckles, but I’m being honest when I say some of the best food I’ve had in my life has been in Orlando. Perhaps it’s recency bias or even the fact that I’m older and know my taste buds better now, but nonetheless, I absolutely adore the Orlando food scene.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These egg tarts deserve a four photo spotlight. I also included four, because it demonstrates their different look each time I go. You can tell these are made in-house because of that! Despite the different looks, they never fail to deliver on the flakiest crust and perfect custard. Absolutely exquisite. 🤌&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;just-look-how-puffy-they-are&quot;&gt;Just look how puffy they are!&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img class=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/orlandoeats/ten-ten/egg-tart-3.jpeg&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img class=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/orlandoeats/ten-ten/egg-tart-4.jpeg&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ten Ten remains at the top of my favorite restaurants in Orlando, because they always deliver on my Cantonese favorites at the highest quality. Coming from a Cantonese family, I’ve enjoyed my fair share of great Canto food. However, Ten Ten is special to me, because it solidified to me that I could find a home here in Orlando. I’ve since discovered several other fantastic dim sum places, but I feel like I learned so much about Cantonese food just from coming here. Fall of 2021 was the freest I had ever been, and I got to &lt;em&gt;yum cha&lt;/em&gt; with my grandma and dad more times than I had my whole life before that. During these meals, my dad and grandma introduced me to dim sum traditions and dishes beyond my childhood favorites of cheung fun and sesame balls. I’ve felt so much more connected to Cantonese culture since we’ve discovered this restaurant — so Ten Ten will always represent the start of my journey in absolutely loving my Cantonese heritage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ten Ten Seafood and Grill at 5600 W Colonial Dr, Orlando, FL 32808&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="orlandoeats" /><summary type="html">Bei Fung Tong Seafood Meet the restaurant that made me realize how delicious the Cantonese food could be in Orlando. And since my first time eating here, I’ve been nothing short of impressed by the Cantonese restaurants in this city. If you walk into a Chinese restaurant and “seafood” is part of its name, you can expect it to serve Cantonese cuisine specifically. This is likely because Guangzhou (also known as Canton) is located along the South China Sea, along with other cities in the Guangdong Province and Hong Kong. This prime location by the sea means the seafood in this region is always excellent, fresh, and pretty plentiful. Cantonese food is one of the most well-known Chinese cuisines in America — dim sum is most frequently associated with Cantonese cuisine. Many of these seafood restaurants do dim sum services, whether it’s by ordering from a menu or waving down the people who push the iconic dim sum carts. Ten Ten Seafood and Grill offers the beloved push cart service, so you’re never at a shortage of quick decisions needing to be made when you’re here. Ten Ten, or tiāntiān 天天, means every day. During fall of 2021, my family came here once or twice a week. It’s not uncommon for Cantonese people to go to dim sum daily. People go with two or three friends, and they split a pot of cha and two or three dim sum dishes. Dim sum is designed to be shared — a steamer of siu mai may come with three pieces, for example. People may go to dim sum as a morning or afternoon snack, making dim sum an easy, delicious excuse to catch up with friends. Whenever we went to Ten Ten, we saw many of the same people with the same trusty two or three steamers of dim sum. Ten Ten offers the beloved push cart service, so you’re never at a shortage of quick decisions needing to be made while you’re here. They not only offer basically every dim sum dish you’d want, but they also do it excellently. Might I make a case for the best egg tarts in Orlando, potentially in all of America? Continue scrolling to see what’s up 👀 However, like all dim sum restaurants, you can participate in picking dishes from the carts and/or order something to be prepared a la carte. Let’s get to it! Har Cheung Fun 虾肠粉 It’s so simple, but it will always be a favorite. This har cheung fun, or shrimp rice noodle roll, is one of the most popular dim sum dishes, and for a good reason. Rice noodle rolls can be filled with anything, whether it’s beef, char siu, or youtiao (Chinese donut). Plus, once they’re topped with the sweet soy sauce, it’s hard to beat the simple, yet perfect match of rice rolls and sweet soy sauce. Regular soy sauce won’t do, yet to this day, I still don’t know exactly what kind of soy sauce dim sum restaurants use. Ten Ten’s rice noodle rolls are well-executed, as the batter is always well-mixed, meaning the rolls are not too thick or too thin and are never doughy. Bean Curd Rolls 腐皮卷 Tofu skin rolls have mixed reviews in the Liu family. Personally, these weren’t always my favorite, but my sister loves them. However, I now also really like this dish now. The tofu skin rolls are deep-fried, which puffs up/activates some layers and gives it the flavor of fried food. However, they are then steamed, which makes these rolls soft and slightly chewy. Cantonese-style Seafood Front: Bei Fung Tong Seafood; Back: Ginger Scallion Lobster When I say there’s no other preparations of seafood I love more than these two, I mean it! The front dish, which is also pictured at the top, is bei fung tong 避风塘 style seafood. Bei fung tong translates into “typhoon shelter,” because of how it originated in Hong Kong’s typhoon shelters. This preparation can be ordered with any choice of seafood, but we always get it with three kinds — scallops, shrimp, and squid. While every restaurant does this dish differently, Ten Ten’s is deep-fried and battered seafood that is then tossed with fried garlic, onions, scallions, and chilies. The result is an unbelievably aromatic, deep-fried pile of crispiness. The back dish is the classic Cantonese-style ginger scallion lobster, a common course in Cantonese banquet weddings. This deep-fried lobster is stir-fried in a ginger scallion-infused oil and is lightly seasoned with shaoxing wine and soy sauce. Ten Ten sometimes offers deals where they do these lobsters for around $25, although it is variable due to the ever-fluctuating market price of seafood. When these sales are offered, they’re a great opportunity to try out this incredible preparation of lobster. Gon Chow Ngau Huo 乾炒牛河 Also known as beef chow fun, this dish is a popular Cantonese dish that consists of wok-tossed rice noodles, soy sauce, thin steak, mung bean sprouts, onions, and scallions. The ingredients are so simple, but requires years of perfecting a technique, according to my dad. This is because chefs need to develop the wok hei, or the “wok’s breath/air.” This article on the Michelin Guide explains it quite well. To achieve wok hei, chefs must use intense heat and have lots of stamina, because the food needs to be constantly tossed. While many professional chefs have little to no arm and hair, my dad always says Cantonese chefs are especially prone to this, because they constantly have their wrists/hands near the flames. Anyway, I digress. The wok hei produces a unique smoky, often caramelized, savory taste — it’s something that needs to be experienced to understand. I’m hungry just thinking about all the dishes made with wok hei. Ten Ten makes a great chow fun, and I can’t wait to go back home and eat it. Over these past few years, it’s landed at the top of my favorite food rankings. This is my dad’s favorite dish, and eating it with him has made me a superfan. For fellow cooked onion/scallion lovers, you will be satisfied! The gon chow means dry stir-fried, which means the thin sauce is tossed and stir-fried in the wok. Wet-style, or sup chow, means the noodles and vegetables are all wok-tossed without sauce, but are topped with a soupier, thicker sauce upon serving. Dan Tat 蛋挞 Yes…the best egg tarts I’ve ever had. Yes, they’re in Orlando, Florida. Please hold the chuckles, but I’m being honest when I say some of the best food I’ve had in my life has been in Orlando. Perhaps it’s recency bias or even the fact that I’m older and know my taste buds better now, but nonetheless, I absolutely adore the Orlando food scene. These egg tarts deserve a four photo spotlight. I also included four, because it demonstrates their different look each time I go. You can tell these are made in-house because of that! Despite the different looks, they never fail to deliver on the flakiest crust and perfect custard. Absolutely exquisite. 🤌 Just look how puffy they are! Ten Ten remains at the top of my favorite restaurants in Orlando, because they always deliver on my Cantonese favorites at the highest quality. Coming from a Cantonese family, I’ve enjoyed my fair share of great Canto food. However, Ten Ten is special to me, because it solidified to me that I could find a home here in Orlando. I’ve since discovered several other fantastic dim sum places, but I feel like I learned so much about Cantonese food just from coming here. Fall of 2021 was the freest I had ever been, and I got to yum cha with my grandma and dad more times than I had my whole life before that. During these meals, my dad and grandma introduced me to dim sum traditions and dishes beyond my childhood favorites of cheung fun and sesame balls. I’ve felt so much more connected to Cantonese culture since we’ve discovered this restaurant — so Ten Ten will always represent the start of my journey in absolutely loving my Cantonese heritage. Ten Ten Seafood and Grill at 5600 W Colonial Dr, Orlando, FL 32808</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/orlandoeats/ten-ten/bei-fung-tong-seafood.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/orlandoeats/ten-ten/bei-fung-tong-seafood.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Noodles.</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/stories/noodles" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Noodles." /><published>2021-08-02T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2021-08-02T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/stories/noodles</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/stories/noodles">&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/stories/noodle/mitsuwa.jpg&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;Santouka Ramen&lt;/div&gt;    
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yup, you read that right. Noodles. In virtually every culture, an iconic noodle dish exists – Italian &lt;em&gt;pasta&lt;/em&gt;, Japanese &lt;em&gt;udon&lt;/em&gt;, Korean &lt;em&gt;japchae&lt;/em&gt;, Jewish &lt;em&gt;kugel&lt;/em&gt;, Singaporean &lt;em&gt;laksa&lt;/em&gt;, Filipino &lt;em&gt;pancit&lt;/em&gt;, Dominican &lt;em&gt;espaguetis&lt;/em&gt; – you get the point. So where did this versatile ingredient / base originate? What was the catalyst for its widespread popularity? How are noodles the foundation to many fusion cuisines? How can plant-based eaters enjoy this dish that’s typically accompanied by meat? And then I’m excited to share my dream noodle list.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you don’t know I love noodles, &lt;em&gt;udon know me&lt;/em&gt;. Be prepared for all the noodle puns I could think of (and find online).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The comprehensive noodle research guide will launch soon!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="stories" /><summary type="html">Santouka Ramen Yup, you read that right. Noodles. In virtually every culture, an iconic noodle dish exists – Italian pasta, Japanese udon, Korean japchae, Jewish kugel, Singaporean laksa, Filipino pancit, Dominican espaguetis – you get the point. So where did this versatile ingredient / base originate? What was the catalyst for its widespread popularity? How are noodles the foundation to many fusion cuisines? How can plant-based eaters enjoy this dish that’s typically accompanied by meat? And then I’m excited to share my dream noodle list. If you don’t know I love noodles, udon know me. Be prepared for all the noodle puns I could think of (and find online). The comprehensive noodle research guide will launch soon!</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/stories/noodle/mitsuwa.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/stories/noodle/mitsuwa.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Life Update</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/stories/life-update-1" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Life Update" /><published>2021-04-21T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2021-04-21T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/stories/life-update-1</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/stories/life-update-1">&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/vectorart/tofupuddingvectorart.svg&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;  
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hey everyone! So I’ve been pretty MIA on here and on Instagram, so I just wanted to keep you all updated on where I’ve been.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I do have a lot on my mind, regarding where I’m at and what I want to do, so bear with me while I explain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;First thing&lt;/strong&gt;: I’m moving. I’ll be going to college next year, but my dad is also moving! I’ve lived in [redacted town, out of an abundance of caution] my entire life, and it’s rather bittersweet to move. On one hand, I’ve always felt safe living in my house, which has been a huge privilege to have. This town is the only place I’ve ever known as “home”, which is a true luxury that many people yearn for. While my sister and I took our daily walk the other day, I began reminiscing on all of the staples in my town: the multitude of pizza shops, the (now-closed) cookware store, the diner, among many others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And then, there’s the “sweet” part of moving: I would love a fresh start. My family was actually supposed to move three years ago, but those plans fell through. My family went through a big loss nearly five years ago, and the house sometimes feels like a never-ending reminder of that loss and all events leading up to it. Plus, the opportunity to have a fresh start feels more appealing than ever, since the last year has felt very stagnant due to the pandemic – which is absolutely not a terrible thing – but to have the ability to move by choice is exciting. We’ll be heading to &lt;strong&gt;Orlando&lt;/strong&gt;, which I can only imagine will be a bit of a culture shock. Although I don’t live in the most diverse place, I’m still surrounded by a lot of people who look like me. We’ll be living in a suburb in the Orlando metro area, so it’ll just be a peaceful summer at a new home. So &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.publix.com/shop-online/in-store-pickup&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Publix&lt;/a&gt;, here I come!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We could be moving in just a couple weeks, so packing time has commenced! Packing the home you’ve lived in for 17 years is bound to have 17 years worth of stuff (x4 for everyone who lives here), and we are &lt;em&gt;that&lt;/em&gt; hoarding family. I would love to spend my free time working on this blog, but until we get up out of this house, most of my time will go to packing. On top of school, I’ve been a little more stressed than usual, but we just have to keep going. July and August will be months of weekly blogging at the minimum, though, I promise!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Next thing&lt;/strong&gt;: I have a lot of content in mind – three articles unlike anything I’ve ever posted! Restaurant recommendations and a few stories make up most of my content here, but I’m ecstatic to write the following pieces, some of which delve into identity and culture. Here’s a little tease for each one:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Noodles&lt;/strong&gt;: Noodles are popular in a multitude of cultures. Where did this versatile ingredient / base originate? What was the catalyst for its widespread popularity? How are noodles the foundation to many fusion (intercultural) cuisines? How can plant-based eaters enjoy this dish that’s typically accompanied by meat? And then I’m excited to share my dream noodle list.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More Than Sesame Chicken&lt;/strong&gt;: BIPOC are often flattened to their ethnic identity in the food industry (and beyond), whereas their white peers are allowed to venture into any cuisine they want. “More Than Sesame Chicken” discusses my Chinese-American experience and how that impacts my love for food in America. I’ll also dispel the melting pot myth and talk a bit about what it means to be Asian in America.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bro-Ritos Taco Kit&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.broritosfoodtruck.com/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bro-Ritos Food Truck&lt;/a&gt; (flagship in Hackensack) launched a taco kit in early February 2021. The taco kit consists of their signature “Red Salt”, 12 tortillas, and their taco hot (or mild) sauce. Y’all, that Red Salt is really just out of this world. I still have a little left, but only because we want to savor it forever. This taco kit gives you all the directions to making a taco with different proteins – I’ll show how I made them with shrimp in this post. I would 10000000% recommend anyone who &lt;em&gt;can&lt;/em&gt; buy this kit to &lt;a href=&quot;https://broritosfoodtruck.square.site/product/tacokit/46?cs=true&amp;amp;cst=custom&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;buy it&lt;/a&gt;. The “Red Salt” veers on the sweet side, which I prefer anyway, but my taste buds were dancing after trying this salt.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Those are just some of the things I wanted to share with y’all today, since I haven’t been posting much lately. I have exciting projects to come, so I appreciate your patience 😊&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="stories" /><summary type="html">Hey everyone! So I’ve been pretty MIA on here and on Instagram, so I just wanted to keep you all updated on where I’ve been. I do have a lot on my mind, regarding where I’m at and what I want to do, so bear with me while I explain. First thing: I’m moving. I’ll be going to college next year, but my dad is also moving! I’ve lived in [redacted town, out of an abundance of caution] my entire life, and it’s rather bittersweet to move. On one hand, I’ve always felt safe living in my house, which has been a huge privilege to have. This town is the only place I’ve ever known as “home”, which is a true luxury that many people yearn for. While my sister and I took our daily walk the other day, I began reminiscing on all of the staples in my town: the multitude of pizza shops, the (now-closed) cookware store, the diner, among many others. And then, there’s the “sweet” part of moving: I would love a fresh start. My family was actually supposed to move three years ago, but those plans fell through. My family went through a big loss nearly five years ago, and the house sometimes feels like a never-ending reminder of that loss and all events leading up to it. Plus, the opportunity to have a fresh start feels more appealing than ever, since the last year has felt very stagnant due to the pandemic – which is absolutely not a terrible thing – but to have the ability to move by choice is exciting. We’ll be heading to Orlando, which I can only imagine will be a bit of a culture shock. Although I don’t live in the most diverse place, I’m still surrounded by a lot of people who look like me. We’ll be living in a suburb in the Orlando metro area, so it’ll just be a peaceful summer at a new home. So Publix, here I come! We could be moving in just a couple weeks, so packing time has commenced! Packing the home you’ve lived in for 17 years is bound to have 17 years worth of stuff (x4 for everyone who lives here), and we are that hoarding family. I would love to spend my free time working on this blog, but until we get up out of this house, most of my time will go to packing. On top of school, I’ve been a little more stressed than usual, but we just have to keep going. July and August will be months of weekly blogging at the minimum, though, I promise! Next thing: I have a lot of content in mind – three articles unlike anything I’ve ever posted! Restaurant recommendations and a few stories make up most of my content here, but I’m ecstatic to write the following pieces, some of which delve into identity and culture. Here’s a little tease for each one: Noodles: Noodles are popular in a multitude of cultures. Where did this versatile ingredient / base originate? What was the catalyst for its widespread popularity? How are noodles the foundation to many fusion (intercultural) cuisines? How can plant-based eaters enjoy this dish that’s typically accompanied by meat? And then I’m excited to share my dream noodle list. More Than Sesame Chicken: BIPOC are often flattened to their ethnic identity in the food industry (and beyond), whereas their white peers are allowed to venture into any cuisine they want. “More Than Sesame Chicken” discusses my Chinese-American experience and how that impacts my love for food in America. I’ll also dispel the melting pot myth and talk a bit about what it means to be Asian in America. Bro-Ritos Taco Kit: Bro-Ritos Food Truck (flagship in Hackensack) launched a taco kit in early February 2021. The taco kit consists of their signature “Red Salt”, 12 tortillas, and their taco hot (or mild) sauce. Y’all, that Red Salt is really just out of this world. I still have a little left, but only because we want to savor it forever. This taco kit gives you all the directions to making a taco with different proteins – I’ll show how I made them with shrimp in this post. I would 10000000% recommend anyone who can buy this kit to buy it. The “Red Salt” veers on the sweet side, which I prefer anyway, but my taste buds were dancing after trying this salt. Those are just some of the things I wanted to share with y’all today, since I haven’t been posting much lately. I have exciting projects to come, so I appreciate your patience 😊</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/vectorart/tofupuddingvectorart.svg" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/vectorart/tofupuddingvectorart.svg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Recipe Spotlights #1</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/recipes/recipe-spotlights-1" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Recipe Spotlights #1" /><published>2021-02-24T00:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2021-02-24T00:00:00-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/recipes/recipe-spotlights-1</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/recipes/recipe-spotlights-1">&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/recipes/spotlights/recipespotlights.jpg&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome to my new recipe series, where I’m highlighting BIPOC creatives in the food industry!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This first release of the BIPOC Recipe Series spotlights Black recipe creators. I chose mostly independent creatives, because independent creatives have complete control over their narratives, meaning they are Black stories told by Black people. So without further ado, here are five Black recipe creators and food storytelling communities comprised of Black voices!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://jikoni.co/recipes/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Jikoni&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: Jikoni means kitchen in Swahili. According to their website, Jikoni focuses on African culture and people, as African cuisine and stories are underrepresented in the culinary world. By looking through the lens of cuisine, people can learn about culture. “All roads to lead to Africa” for Jikoni.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc8n9VxRO2ei45mXzZAJluA/videos&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Lady of Q&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: Sylvie Curry of &lt;em&gt;The American Barbecue Showdown&lt;/em&gt; often used Asian-inspired flavors in their barbecue, but their range of cuisines spans all around the world. Sylvie may be a barbecue pitmaster, but that doesn’t stop them from crafting mouth-watering, non-BBQ recipes like the &lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/4FHmPPgP6MA&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Alaskan Seafood Feasts&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/DRN3Iyw9O1o&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Korean Crispy Corn Dogs&lt;/a&gt;. Their YouTube channel has content discussing their time and how they got on the show, but also recipes from well before their TV show stint. Sylvie deserves all the subscribers and fans, so be sure to hit the subscribe button!&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://meikoandthedish.com/tag/recipe/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Meiko and The Dish&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: Meiko Temple spent time in a Corporate America career of marketing and design, but ultimately, they found their passion in food. And what better way to combine design and culinary skills (along with a love for food!) than this beautiful blog! Meiko’s personal favorites are listed on the &lt;a href=&quot;https://meikoandthedish.com/about-meiko/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;About&lt;/a&gt; page, and the recipes are colorful, creative, and culinary delights (re: &lt;a href=&quot;https://meikoandthedish.com/pink-spaghetti-beet-pesto/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Pink Spaghetti&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;https://meikoandthedish.com/elote-corn-chowder/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Elote Corn Chowder&lt;/a&gt;)!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;-vegan-or-plant-forward&quot;&gt;🌱 Vegan (or Plant-Forward)&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.baumassfoods.com/category/recipes/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;baumassfoods&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: Hilaire Baumgartner follows a mostly vegan diet (“zero meat (even fish), very limited dairy, and very little egg”, according to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.baumassfoods.com/about/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;About&lt;/a&gt; page). Hilaire is making “bomb-ass, plant-forward food” and is showing the world that a plant-based lifestyle, if accessible, is as enjoyable as (if not better and more sustainable than) one with meat. I mean, are you &lt;em&gt;kidding&lt;/em&gt; me with these &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.baumassfoods.com/triple-chocolate-pistachio-cookies/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;triple chocolate pistachio cookies&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.baumassfoods.com/bbq-jackfruit-bean-bowls-with-cornbread-croutons-and-coleslaw/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;bbq jackfruit bean bowls with cornbread croutons and coleslaw&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.baumassfoods.com/20-minute-creamy-skillet-lasagna/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;skillet lasagna&lt;/a&gt;?! Warning: You may want to eat your screen after scrolling through their recipe feed. After all, Hilaire &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; a commercial food photographer in addition to running this blog, so the stunning visuals should come as no surprise.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cocoverdevegan.com/food-blog&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;coco verde vegan&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: The Rodriguez Flores family is cooking up various plant-based foods and Latinx vegan dishes. They are Afro-Dominican and are passionate about food, welfare and social justice. Their Instagram captions are in both English and Spanish. Their Instagram feed pops of color, but also consists of heart-warming family photos.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;ways-to-support-bipoc-bloggers&quot;&gt;Ways to Support BIPOC Bloggers:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Many sites are supported by ads. If you use an ad blocker, please turn it off or remove it. If you see any ads that appeal to you (and look safe), click on them, as this may help the creatives get that revenue.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Just show them some ❤️. Hit that follow button if you feel like you identify with their mission. Drive their Instagram engagement up by &lt;strong&gt;saving&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;sharing&lt;/strong&gt;, or any other interactions. Followers aren’t always the goal, but enthusiastic and dedicated members of their Instagram communities are. Subscribe, like, and comment on YouTube channels, if they have them!&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sign up for their Recipe Newsletters (typically a lightbox that appears on the screen or on the bottom).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;If their website has them, leave a review &lt;em&gt;if&lt;/em&gt; you try their recipes &lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt; love them.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;supporting-blogs-doesnt-seem-like-it-means-much-but-black-indigenous-and-people-of-color-are-underrepresented-in-creative-spaces-uplifting-the-bipoc-voices-that-do-exist-also-creates-more-space-for-future-creatives-to-leave-their-mark-bipoc-stories-are-beautiful-diverse-and-meaningful--remember-that-the-bipoc-community-isnt-a-monolith-and-sub-communities-face-different-experiences&quot;&gt;Supporting blogs doesn’t seem like it means much, but Black, Indigenous, and People of Color are underrepresented in creative spaces. Uplifting the BIPOC voices that do exist also creates more space for future creatives to leave their mark. BIPOC stories are beautiful, diverse, and meaningful – remember that the BIPOC community isn’t a monolith and sub-communities face different experiences.&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;-to-be-copyright-conscious-i-didnt-include-any-photos-from-their-blogs&quot;&gt;* To be copyright conscious, I didn’t include any photos from their blogs.&lt;/h6&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="recipes" /><summary type="html">Welcome to my new recipe series, where I’m highlighting BIPOC creatives in the food industry! This first release of the BIPOC Recipe Series spotlights Black recipe creators. I chose mostly independent creatives, because independent creatives have complete control over their narratives, meaning they are Black stories told by Black people. So without further ado, here are five Black recipe creators and food storytelling communities comprised of Black voices! Jikoni: Jikoni means kitchen in Swahili. According to their website, Jikoni focuses on African culture and people, as African cuisine and stories are underrepresented in the culinary world. By looking through the lens of cuisine, people can learn about culture. “All roads to lead to Africa” for Jikoni. Lady of Q: Sylvie Curry of The American Barbecue Showdown often used Asian-inspired flavors in their barbecue, but their range of cuisines spans all around the world. Sylvie may be a barbecue pitmaster, but that doesn’t stop them from crafting mouth-watering, non-BBQ recipes like the Alaskan Seafood Feasts and Korean Crispy Corn Dogs. Their YouTube channel has content discussing their time and how they got on the show, but also recipes from well before their TV show stint. Sylvie deserves all the subscribers and fans, so be sure to hit the subscribe button! Meiko and The Dish: Meiko Temple spent time in a Corporate America career of marketing and design, but ultimately, they found their passion in food. And what better way to combine design and culinary skills (along with a love for food!) than this beautiful blog! Meiko’s personal favorites are listed on the About page, and the recipes are colorful, creative, and culinary delights (re: Pink Spaghetti or Elote Corn Chowder)! 🌱 Vegan (or Plant-Forward) baumassfoods: Hilaire Baumgartner follows a mostly vegan diet (“zero meat (even fish), very limited dairy, and very little egg”, according to the About page). Hilaire is making “bomb-ass, plant-forward food” and is showing the world that a plant-based lifestyle, if accessible, is as enjoyable as (if not better and more sustainable than) one with meat. I mean, are you kidding me with these triple chocolate pistachio cookies, bbq jackfruit bean bowls with cornbread croutons and coleslaw, and skillet lasagna?! Warning: You may want to eat your screen after scrolling through their recipe feed. After all, Hilaire is a commercial food photographer in addition to running this blog, so the stunning visuals should come as no surprise. coco verde vegan: The Rodriguez Flores family is cooking up various plant-based foods and Latinx vegan dishes. They are Afro-Dominican and are passionate about food, welfare and social justice. Their Instagram captions are in both English and Spanish. Their Instagram feed pops of color, but also consists of heart-warming family photos. Ways to Support BIPOC Bloggers: Many sites are supported by ads. If you use an ad blocker, please turn it off or remove it. If you see any ads that appeal to you (and look safe), click on them, as this may help the creatives get that revenue. Just show them some ❤️. Hit that follow button if you feel like you identify with their mission. Drive their Instagram engagement up by saving, sharing, or any other interactions. Followers aren’t always the goal, but enthusiastic and dedicated members of their Instagram communities are. Subscribe, like, and comment on YouTube channels, if they have them! Sign up for their Recipe Newsletters (typically a lightbox that appears on the screen or on the bottom). If their website has them, leave a review if you try their recipes and love them. Supporting blogs doesn’t seem like it means much, but Black, Indigenous, and People of Color are underrepresented in creative spaces. Uplifting the BIPOC voices that do exist also creates more space for future creatives to leave their mark. BIPOC stories are beautiful, diverse, and meaningful – remember that the BIPOC community isn’t a monolith and sub-communities face different experiences. * To be copyright conscious, I didn’t include any photos from their blogs.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/recipes/spotlights/recipespotlights.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/recipes/spotlights/recipespotlights.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Summer in Asia</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/beyond/asia" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Summer in Asia" /><published>2021-01-20T00:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2021-01-20T00:00:00-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/beyond/asia</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/beyond/asia">&lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/taiwan/taipeifood.jpg&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;
          Oyster Omelette + Noodle Soup
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/china/heycha1.JPG&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;
          Fruity Cheese Tea Trio
        &lt;/div&gt;        
    &lt;/div&gt;    
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reason I look back on Asia especially fondly is because the foods I’ve grown up eating and learned to love here in the states truly felt at home in Asia – which seems obvious, but only becomes more apparent when you finally go. Yes, the Asian food in America is undisputedly excellent, but the Asian food &lt;em&gt;in&lt;/em&gt; Asia is on another level. The meals can be so simple and “bare bones”, but are elevated when compared to how they taste in America. Chefs in the states who immigrated from Asia often need to adjust their flavorings to pander to a wide variety of taste buds, whereas chefs in China are catering to mostly Chinese consumers, allowing them to stick to their more traditional methods. These photos are from my summer in Asia in 2018, where I was introduced to so many new dishes and elevations of ones I already knew. My dad grew up in China, so he knows his way around and has some fun tidbits to add about some of the foods we tried, which only added to this incredible experience of staying in China. I will also preface this post by saying that a lot of the foods I’m sharing below are non-traditional, but I ate plenty of traditionally Cantonese dishes during my time - I was just enjoying the moment and couldn’t snap a photo!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This post will include mostly photos, but I’ll write about any foods that may need more of a description, connections to other cultures, or have a story I want to share. While I don’t have the exact restaurant names, keep these dishes on your list for the future!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Dishes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&quot;foods&quot;&gt;
  &lt;h5 id=&quot;guangzhou&quot;&gt;Guangzhou&lt;/h5&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Some people say Cantonese food is the most boring of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://hakkasan.com/stories/eight-culinary-traditions-china/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;Eight Chinese Cuisines&lt;/a&gt;, as it doesn’t pack the kick of Sichuan or Hunan cuisine, but the simplicity of the dishes is the most impressive part. You might be used to seeing Cantonese cuisine through &lt;em&gt;dim sum&lt;/em&gt; (to touch the heart) or &lt;em&gt;yum cha&lt;/em&gt; (to drink tea), which is typically drinking tea with smaller plates. Some popular dishes you might know of are rice rolls drowning in sweet soy sauce (a personal favorite of mine) and char siu (叉烧) bao (baked or steamed roast pork buns). &lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/china/gzchashu.jpg&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;~Fancy~ Char Siu&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/china/gzcafe.JPG&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Char Siu + Beef Chow Fun&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/china/garlicribs.jpg&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Crispy Garlic Ribs&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/china/riceroll.jpg&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;HK-style Cheung Fun&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Above are just a small sampling of Cantonese dishes I got a photo of: char siu, &lt;em&gt;gon chow ngau huo&lt;/em&gt; (beef chow fun), crispy garlic pork ribs, and HK-style cheung fun. Note the distinction between the cheung fun pictured above, and the Cantonese one; HK-style ones are literally tiny rolls, and Cantonese ones are unrolled (but still “rolls), longer, and thinner. It’s pretty much just the shape, but both are shockingly addictive. Enjoy HK-style cheung fun doused in hoisin + peanut sauces (as seen above), and Cantonese ones doused in sweet soy sauce. This is &lt;em&gt;important&lt;/em&gt;. This is NOT the soy sauce you eat with sushi, but a perfect umami and sweet combination that pares very well with the plainness of cheung fun. &lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/china/gzroastpork.jpg&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Siu Yuk Roast Pork&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;  
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/china/roastplatter2.jpg&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Assorted Roast Platter&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/china/gzdumplings.JPG&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Fried Dumplings&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/china/gzpuff.jpg&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;See below!&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Just a miscellaneous collection of food pictured above. Siu yuk, or roast pork, is CRISPY, and there’s no deep frying involved. This roast pork is stuffed with a variety of seasonings and hoisin sauce, which you’ll get a taste of once the pork is cut up. The picture next to the roast pork is a platter of the most popular Cantonese meats, which are char siu, siu yuk, roast duck (different from Peking duck!), as well as the not originally Cantonese drunken chicken. You also see the jellyfish salad, which doesn’t taste like seafood whatsoever.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Now, we all know what dumplings are, but what’s pictured on the right is still an enigma to me two years later. It’s this gorgeous fluffy pudding, soufflé/sponge cake thing covered in sliced nuts. I have virtually no idea what it’s actually intended to be, but it’s definitely something to try out if you ever come across it! &lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h5 id=&quot;taipei&quot;&gt;Taipei&lt;/h5&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/taiwan/beefnoodle1.JPG&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Beef Noodle Soup&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/taiwan/scallionpancake.jpg&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Scallion Pancake&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/taiwan/taipeicorndog.jpg&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Special Corn Dogs&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/taiwan/taiwanxlb.JPG&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Xiao Long Bao&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;The best food in Asia really comes from the no-frills restaurants and the famous Taiwanese night markets. We went to &lt;strong&gt;Raohe&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Shi Lin Night Markets&lt;/strong&gt;, IIRC, but there are plenty of lesser known ones that likely serve as equally good products. &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Those hand-pulled noodles and freshly-wrapped boiled dumplings were from this tiny, open-air shop a few blocks from the hotel we stayed at. And my GOSH, don't even get me started on those scallion pancakes. The scallion pancakes in America don't do these justice! You can get ham, cheese, egg, and a sweet-spicy sauce/glaze as toppings or just get it plain. Fantastic either way.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Those corn dogs are just like Korean corn dogs, which are dipped in rice batter, as opposed to traditional cornmeal batter, coated in panko, and stuffed with mozzarella cheese and/or a hot dog. They’re also dusted with granulated sugar and topped with ketchup, honey mustard, and/or or Japanese mayo. The last photo is &lt;em&gt;xiao long bao&lt;/em&gt;, which I don’t believe are originally Taiwanese, but you may recognize them from the &lt;a href=&quot;https://dintaifungusa.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;Din Tai Fung&lt;/a&gt; empire that is 100% from Taiwan.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h5 id=&quot;singapore&quot;&gt;Singapore&lt;/h5&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/singapore/chashu.jpg&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Chashu (top) and Steak (Bottom) Rice Bowls&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/singapore/frybasket.JPG&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Fry Basket&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/singapore/satay.JPG&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Mixed Satay&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/singapore/spicypork.jpg&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Suan Ni Bai Rou&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;The top two photos are from &lt;a href=&quot;https://pasarbella.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;PasarBella at Suntec City&lt;/a&gt;, an NYC-inspired food hall. I know some people are shaking their heads in disappointment for not eating traditionally Singaporean food, but I remember eating here more out of convenience than anything. Nonetheless, the food was delicious, and there's not really much else to say.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;This satay is from &lt;strong&gt;Newton Food Centre&lt;/strong&gt; -- fun fact, it's where Crazy Rich Asians filmed that intro scene of Nick, Rachel, Colin, and Araminta eat at a hawker centre! We also ate chili crab (one of the national Singaporean dishes), accompanied by mantou (steamed or fried buns - no stuffing), as well as roti prata and quite a few more dishes from various stalls. Next to it is the Sichuan &lt;em&gt;Suan Ni Bai Rou&lt;/em&gt; pork belly. I know this isn't quite Singaporean, but we did eat it in Singapore, so that's why it's under the Singapore &quot;category&quot;. It's a very famous Sichuan dish, and it consists of &lt;em&gt;ultra-thin&lt;/em&gt; pork belly doused in chili-garlic sauce. This is one of Antonia's favorite dishes, but be warned - describing the sauce as &lt;em&gt;just&lt;/em&gt; garlic is being modest. This dish is g a r l i c k y.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;h4 id=&quot;boba-sweets&quot;&gt;&lt;u&gt;Boba + Sweets&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
  &lt;h5 id=&quot;guangzhou&quot;&gt;Guangzhou&lt;/h5&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/china/heycha2.JPG&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Cheese Mango&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/china/heycha3.jpg&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Black Sugar Boba&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/china/gztart1.jpg&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Macanese Egg Tarts&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/china/milkfry.jpg&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Fried Milk&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;IT’S DESSERT TIMEEEE! I don’t have a preference for sweet or savory, but my sweet tooth was satisfied in Asia! The boba tea, the cheese tea, the tarts, EVERY dessert is incredible there. Above, you see some mango cheese tea, which is mango blended with ice topped with a lightly salted cheese foam, which I drank nearly every day on my journey. At the very top, you also see a strawberry cheese and grape cheese, which are solid competitors for best drink at HeyCha. You also see a black sugar boba, which is similar to brown sugar boba, a thicker and stickier drink topping, but with a more licorice-like taste. I prefer brown sugar, but black sugar boba tastes great, too. &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Below those drinks are Macanese egg tarts, which are inspired by Portuguese tarts, which are one of my favorite warm desserts. The Macanese egg tart shells are flakier and much more layered, compared to their Hong Kong-style counterparts with a crumblier, but still puff pastry-esque crust. Next, I’m ecstatic to present the incredible FRIED MILK!!! Don’t expect a drink to flow out once you bite in, but it’s a milk custard rolled in a thin wrapper (or sometimes a batter). It has only a subtle sweetness, which is ideal for me. I’ve never had the Spanish leche frita, but if it’s anything like this Cantonese variation, I am &lt;em&gt;in&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;h5 id=&quot;taipei&quot;&gt;Taipei&lt;/h5&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/taiwan/brownsugarbub.jpg&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Black Sugar Boba&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/taiwan/bubbletea.JPG&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Fiftea&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/taiwan/7_11_bub.jpg&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Original Boba&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/taiwan/chocolatebao.JPG&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Chocolate Red Bean Bao&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;While brown sugar boba is starting to gain traction in the states, the black sugar boba is not quite on the same level of popularity just yet. I personally don't love the licorice taste of the black sugar, but I for sure see the appeal of this drink. Just as brown sugar, or really any sugar, can be caramelized, black sugar can be as well, and that’s what you see above. The “Fiftea” bubble tea photo next to it was unfortunately more disappointing -- Antonia knew it was a well-known chain, so she suggested we try it. The bubbles were fine, but we didn't love the tea flavor as much. My dad said his milk tea tasted good, so maybe it’s just the fruit teas we had.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;We also went to a 7-Eleven in Taiwan, and much to my pleasant surprise, they had 7-11 Bubble Tea! It was actually quite good, but I do suggest supporting the local milk tea shops. Next to that, there’s the final dessert I share, which is the chocolate red bean bao. If you live in a U.S. state with a Din Tai Fung, you certainly don’t need to go to Taiwan for these, BUT...wow, I love red bean desserts, and this one repurposed those paper-thin dumpling skins I love to hold in some chocolate-y red bean goodness.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;h5 id=&quot;hong-kong&quot;&gt;Hong Kong&lt;/h5&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/hongkong/hkwaffle.jpg&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;That famous &lt;em&gt;gai dan jai&lt;/em&gt; from &lt;strong&gt;Lee Keung Kee North Point Egg Waffles&lt;/strong&gt;. My maternal extended family resides in Hong Kong, so they were excited for me to have my first Hong Kong egg waffle IN Hong Kong! I'm a huuuuuge egg waffle fan, and when I talk to my grandma about how much I love these waffles, we just laugh about the name every time. The name literally means little chicken egg, and we just think the name is so fitting for this dessert. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;button id=&quot;showfoods&quot; class=&quot;showmorephotosbutton&quot; onclick=&quot;toggleContent('foods', 'showfoods', '( - ) maybe later...', '( + ) show me the food!')&quot;&gt;( + ) show me the food!&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Activities&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&quot;places&quot;&gt;
  &lt;h5 id=&quot;guangzhou&quot;&gt;Guangzhou&lt;/h5&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/china/wallofshells.JPG&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Lingnan Impression Park&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/china/lilythepom.jpg&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Lily the Pomeranian&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lingnan Impression Park&lt;/strong&gt;: Stalls of street art and food, along with stunning attractions, like this Wall of Oyster Shells.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Lily is my Guangzhou family's dog. How do you not fall in love with those eyes?!&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Not quite an activity, but I wanted to share her beauty.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
  &lt;h5 id=&quot;taipei&quot;&gt;Taipei&lt;/h5&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/taiwan/chiang-kai-shek.jpg&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Chiang Kai-shek Memorial&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/taiwan/taiwanlandscape.jpg&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Yangmingshan National Park&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/taiwan/jadebokchoy.jpg&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Jade Bok Choy&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/taiwan/meatstone.jpg&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Dongpo Pork Stone&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;We didn't have a ton of stops on our trip, but that just meant we got to spend some more time at each! First is the &lt;strong&gt;Chiang Kai Shek Memorial&lt;/strong&gt;, as Chiang Kai-shek, the former leader of the Chinese Nationalist Party, died in Taipei. The memorial had multiple exhibits, so be sure to check those out when you're there.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Next, we checked out &lt;strong&gt;Yangmingshan National Park&lt;/strong&gt;, where there was a volcano, along with a ton of grass-lined valleys and COWS! Definitely smelled like cow dung, but an enjoyable experience nonetheless.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Now...onto the &lt;strong&gt;National Palace Museum&lt;/strong&gt;, home to the Jade Bok Choy and Dongpo Pork Stone! You can see how intricate the details are - they perfectly walk the fine line between ultra-elegant and realistic. &lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h5 id=&quot;hong-kong&quot;&gt;Hong Kong&lt;/h5&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/hongkong/bigbuddha.JPG&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Tian Tan Buddha&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/hongkong/hkclocktower.jpg&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;HK Railway Clock Tower&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tian Tan Buddha&lt;/strong&gt;, or as it's informally known, the Big Buddha! Wow, it was a &lt;em&gt;journey&lt;/em&gt; to get here. You first hop on a gondola, the ride of which took about 30-45 minutes one way, and then, take a decent walk to the steps of the Buddha. The Buddha sits above a hilltop, and the steps are no joke. However, I was truly in awe of this bronze masterpiece, beyond its sheer magnitude. I am nonreligious (I don't even know what I really identify as), but according to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.plm.org.hk/eng/buddha.php&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot;&gt;Po Lin Monastery&lt;/a&gt;, the statue, which &quot;symbolizes the stability of Hong Kong, prosperity of China and peace on earth&quot;, took 12 years to plan and build. It wasn't ridiculously loud at the top, and I appreciated the peacefulness of the attraction. The Buddha would be very close to the top of my list for places I would like to return to. &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Former &lt;strong&gt;Kowloon-Canton Railway Clock Tower&lt;/strong&gt; is a symbol of &quot;moving on&quot; for the Chinese immigrants who passed through this terminus of Kowloon–Canton Railway to start new lives in Hong Kong. My dad told us we had to visit this clock tower, since my mom and him used to stop by.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;

  &lt;h5 id=&quot;singapore&quot;&gt;Singapore&lt;/h5&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/singapore/gardensbythebay.jpg&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Gardens by the Bay&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/singapore/faberpeakbells.jpg&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Faber Peak Bells&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/singapore/marinabaysands.jpg&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Marina Bay Sands&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/singapore/minimerlion.jpg&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Mini Merlion...&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gardens by the Bay&lt;/strong&gt;: One of the most famous Singaporean attractions, you can find beautiful flora and incredible architecture in any of the sub-exhibitions. I visited the Cloud Forest (where this photo was taken) and the Flower Dome. They also have a musical light show at night to check out - it's &lt;em&gt;free&lt;/em&gt;, and you just lie down on a  blanket and look up!&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mount Faber Peak&lt;/strong&gt;: take the Singapore Cable Car up to Faber Peak. There's a giant Bell of Happiness, but also a fence to tie your personalized mini bell.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Antonia in front of the &lt;strong&gt;Marina Bay Sands&lt;/strong&gt;, arguably one of the most famous hotels in the world. &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;This &lt;strong&gt;Merlion&lt;/strong&gt; is the national symbol of Singapore, but also a bit of an inside joke in my family. When my dad decided put Singapore as one of our destinations, he also was adamant about us seeing the giant Merlion. But this one...is ~only~ 8.6 meters tall. Not that it's not huge, but my dad kept saying that the Merlion he visited thirty years ago was far, far taller AND that the giant one was the original Merlion. So we kept looking up &quot;giant Merlion&quot; on Google, but we couldn't find it! Eventually, we discovered it was on Sentosa Island, which is certainly still in Singapore, just not as centrally located. Luckily, Singapore is quite small, so we made the trip to see the lovely Sentosa Merlion, which BTW, is a replica. This one is THIRTY SEVEN meters tall! You can ride an elevator up this giant replica, but we decided it wasn't worth the price. As I was writing this, I unfortunately found out it was permanently closed and demolished just over a year ago 😞 But I'm fortunate to have seen it before Singapore had to say goodbye.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
  
  &lt;p&gt;Without further ado, this is the giant Merlion...&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/singapore/sentosamerlion.jpg&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;Sentosa Merlion&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;button id=&quot;showplaces&quot; class=&quot;showmorephotosbutton&quot; onclick=&quot;toggleContent('places', 'showplaces', '( - ) maybe later...', '( + ) show me where to go!')&quot;&gt;( + ) show me where to go!&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope this guide helped you live vicariously through my 2018 self. I thought a lot about how disconnected I felt with my Chinese heritage, but I’ve been on a journey to understand my roots ever since then. Thank you China, Singapore, Taiwan, Hong Kong, and Macau for an amazing, introspective summer. I am so grateful for food on the table and each of these experiences❤️&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/beyond/hongkong/hkviews.jpg&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;HK Harbor&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="beyond" /><summary type="html">Oyster Omelette + Noodle Soup Fruity Cheese Tea Trio The reason I look back on Asia especially fondly is because the foods I’ve grown up eating and learned to love here in the states truly felt at home in Asia – which seems obvious, but only becomes more apparent when you finally go. Yes, the Asian food in America is undisputedly excellent, but the Asian food in Asia is on another level. The meals can be so simple and “bare bones”, but are elevated when compared to how they taste in America. Chefs in the states who immigrated from Asia often need to adjust their flavorings to pander to a wide variety of taste buds, whereas chefs in China are catering to mostly Chinese consumers, allowing them to stick to their more traditional methods. These photos are from my summer in Asia in 2018, where I was introduced to so many new dishes and elevations of ones I already knew. My dad grew up in China, so he knows his way around and has some fun tidbits to add about some of the foods we tried, which only added to this incredible experience of staying in China. I will also preface this post by saying that a lot of the foods I’m sharing below are non-traditional, but I ate plenty of traditionally Cantonese dishes during my time - I was just enjoying the moment and couldn’t snap a photo! This post will include mostly photos, but I’ll write about any foods that may need more of a description, connections to other cultures, or have a story I want to share. While I don’t have the exact restaurant names, keep these dishes on your list for the future! Dishes Guangzhou Some people say Cantonese food is the most boring of the Eight Chinese Cuisines, as it doesn’t pack the kick of Sichuan or Hunan cuisine, but the simplicity of the dishes is the most impressive part. You might be used to seeing Cantonese cuisine through dim sum (to touch the heart) or yum cha (to drink tea), which is typically drinking tea with smaller plates. Some popular dishes you might know of are rice rolls drowning in sweet soy sauce (a personal favorite of mine) and char siu (叉烧) bao (baked or steamed roast pork buns). ~Fancy~ Char Siu Char Siu + Beef Chow Fun Crispy Garlic Ribs HK-style Cheung Fun Above are just a small sampling of Cantonese dishes I got a photo of: char siu, gon chow ngau huo (beef chow fun), crispy garlic pork ribs, and HK-style cheung fun. Note the distinction between the cheung fun pictured above, and the Cantonese one; HK-style ones are literally tiny rolls, and Cantonese ones are unrolled (but still “rolls), longer, and thinner. It’s pretty much just the shape, but both are shockingly addictive. Enjoy HK-style cheung fun doused in hoisin + peanut sauces (as seen above), and Cantonese ones doused in sweet soy sauce. This is important. This is NOT the soy sauce you eat with sushi, but a perfect umami and sweet combination that pares very well with the plainness of cheung fun. Siu Yuk Roast Pork Assorted Roast Platter Fried Dumplings See below! Just a miscellaneous collection of food pictured above. Siu yuk, or roast pork, is CRISPY, and there’s no deep frying involved. This roast pork is stuffed with a variety of seasonings and hoisin sauce, which you’ll get a taste of once the pork is cut up. The picture next to the roast pork is a platter of the most popular Cantonese meats, which are char siu, siu yuk, roast duck (different from Peking duck!), as well as the not originally Cantonese drunken chicken. You also see the jellyfish salad, which doesn’t taste like seafood whatsoever. Now, we all know what dumplings are, but what’s pictured on the right is still an enigma to me two years later. It’s this gorgeous fluffy pudding, soufflé/sponge cake thing covered in sliced nuts. I have virtually no idea what it’s actually intended to be, but it’s definitely something to try out if you ever come across it! Taipei Beef Noodle Soup Scallion Pancake Special Corn Dogs Xiao Long Bao The best food in Asia really comes from the no-frills restaurants and the famous Taiwanese night markets. We went to Raohe and Shi Lin Night Markets, IIRC, but there are plenty of lesser known ones that likely serve as equally good products. Those hand-pulled noodles and freshly-wrapped boiled dumplings were from this tiny, open-air shop a few blocks from the hotel we stayed at. And my GOSH, don't even get me started on those scallion pancakes. The scallion pancakes in America don't do these justice! You can get ham, cheese, egg, and a sweet-spicy sauce/glaze as toppings or just get it plain. Fantastic either way. Those corn dogs are just like Korean corn dogs, which are dipped in rice batter, as opposed to traditional cornmeal batter, coated in panko, and stuffed with mozzarella cheese and/or a hot dog. They’re also dusted with granulated sugar and topped with ketchup, honey mustard, and/or or Japanese mayo. The last photo is xiao long bao, which I don’t believe are originally Taiwanese, but you may recognize them from the Din Tai Fung empire that is 100% from Taiwan. Singapore Chashu (top) and Steak (Bottom) Rice Bowls Fry Basket Mixed Satay Suan Ni Bai Rou The top two photos are from PasarBella at Suntec City, an NYC-inspired food hall. I know some people are shaking their heads in disappointment for not eating traditionally Singaporean food, but I remember eating here more out of convenience than anything. Nonetheless, the food was delicious, and there's not really much else to say. This satay is from Newton Food Centre -- fun fact, it's where Crazy Rich Asians filmed that intro scene of Nick, Rachel, Colin, and Araminta eat at a hawker centre! We also ate chili crab (one of the national Singaporean dishes), accompanied by mantou (steamed or fried buns - no stuffing), as well as roti prata and quite a few more dishes from various stalls. Next to it is the Sichuan Suan Ni Bai Rou pork belly. I know this isn't quite Singaporean, but we did eat it in Singapore, so that's why it's under the Singapore &quot;category&quot;. It's a very famous Sichuan dish, and it consists of ultra-thin pork belly doused in chili-garlic sauce. This is one of Antonia's favorite dishes, but be warned - describing the sauce as just garlic is being modest. This dish is g a r l i c k y. Boba + Sweets Guangzhou Cheese Mango Black Sugar Boba Macanese Egg Tarts Fried Milk IT’S DESSERT TIMEEEE! I don’t have a preference for sweet or savory, but my sweet tooth was satisfied in Asia! The boba tea, the cheese tea, the tarts, EVERY dessert is incredible there. Above, you see some mango cheese tea, which is mango blended with ice topped with a lightly salted cheese foam, which I drank nearly every day on my journey. At the very top, you also see a strawberry cheese and grape cheese, which are solid competitors for best drink at HeyCha. You also see a black sugar boba, which is similar to brown sugar boba, a thicker and stickier drink topping, but with a more licorice-like taste. I prefer brown sugar, but black sugar boba tastes great, too. Below those drinks are Macanese egg tarts, which are inspired by Portuguese tarts, which are one of my favorite warm desserts. The Macanese egg tart shells are flakier and much more layered, compared to their Hong Kong-style counterparts with a crumblier, but still puff pastry-esque crust. Next, I’m ecstatic to present the incredible FRIED MILK!!! Don’t expect a drink to flow out once you bite in, but it’s a milk custard rolled in a thin wrapper (or sometimes a batter). It has only a subtle sweetness, which is ideal for me. I’ve never had the Spanish leche frita, but if it’s anything like this Cantonese variation, I am in. Taipei Black Sugar Boba Fiftea Original Boba Chocolate Red Bean Bao While brown sugar boba is starting to gain traction in the states, the black sugar boba is not quite on the same level of popularity just yet. I personally don't love the licorice taste of the black sugar, but I for sure see the appeal of this drink. Just as brown sugar, or really any sugar, can be caramelized, black sugar can be as well, and that’s what you see above. The “Fiftea” bubble tea photo next to it was unfortunately more disappointing -- Antonia knew it was a well-known chain, so she suggested we try it. The bubbles were fine, but we didn't love the tea flavor as much. My dad said his milk tea tasted good, so maybe it’s just the fruit teas we had. We also went to a 7-Eleven in Taiwan, and much to my pleasant surprise, they had 7-11 Bubble Tea! It was actually quite good, but I do suggest supporting the local milk tea shops. Next to that, there’s the final dessert I share, which is the chocolate red bean bao. If you live in a U.S. state with a Din Tai Fung, you certainly don’t need to go to Taiwan for these, BUT...wow, I love red bean desserts, and this one repurposed those paper-thin dumpling skins I love to hold in some chocolate-y red bean goodness. Hong Kong That famous gai dan jai from Lee Keung Kee North Point Egg Waffles. My maternal extended family resides in Hong Kong, so they were excited for me to have my first Hong Kong egg waffle IN Hong Kong! I'm a huuuuuge egg waffle fan, and when I talk to my grandma about how much I love these waffles, we just laugh about the name every time. The name literally means little chicken egg, and we just think the name is so fitting for this dessert. ( + ) show me the food! Activities Guangzhou Lingnan Impression Park Lily the Pomeranian Lingnan Impression Park: Stalls of street art and food, along with stunning attractions, like this Wall of Oyster Shells. Lily is my Guangzhou family's dog. How do you not fall in love with those eyes?! Not quite an activity, but I wanted to share her beauty. Taipei Chiang Kai-shek Memorial Yangmingshan National Park Jade Bok Choy Dongpo Pork Stone We didn't have a ton of stops on our trip, but that just meant we got to spend some more time at each! First is the Chiang Kai Shek Memorial, as Chiang Kai-shek, the former leader of the Chinese Nationalist Party, died in Taipei. The memorial had multiple exhibits, so be sure to check those out when you're there. Next, we checked out Yangmingshan National Park, where there was a volcano, along with a ton of grass-lined valleys and COWS! Definitely smelled like cow dung, but an enjoyable experience nonetheless. Now...onto the National Palace Museum, home to the Jade Bok Choy and Dongpo Pork Stone! You can see how intricate the details are - they perfectly walk the fine line between ultra-elegant and realistic. Hong Kong Tian Tan Buddha HK Railway Clock Tower Tian Tan Buddha, or as it's informally known, the Big Buddha! Wow, it was a journey to get here. You first hop on a gondola, the ride of which took about 30-45 minutes one way, and then, take a decent walk to the steps of the Buddha. The Buddha sits above a hilltop, and the steps are no joke. However, I was truly in awe of this bronze masterpiece, beyond its sheer magnitude. I am nonreligious (I don't even know what I really identify as), but according to the Po Lin Monastery, the statue, which &quot;symbolizes the stability of Hong Kong, prosperity of China and peace on earth&quot;, took 12 years to plan and build. It wasn't ridiculously loud at the top, and I appreciated the peacefulness of the attraction. The Buddha would be very close to the top of my list for places I would like to return to. The Former Kowloon-Canton Railway Clock Tower is a symbol of &quot;moving on&quot; for the Chinese immigrants who passed through this terminus of Kowloon–Canton Railway to start new lives in Hong Kong. My dad told us we had to visit this clock tower, since my mom and him used to stop by. Singapore Gardens by the Bay Faber Peak Bells Marina Bay Sands Mini Merlion... Gardens by the Bay: One of the most famous Singaporean attractions, you can find beautiful flora and incredible architecture in any of the sub-exhibitions. I visited the Cloud Forest (where this photo was taken) and the Flower Dome. They also have a musical light show at night to check out - it's free, and you just lie down on a blanket and look up! Mount Faber Peak: take the Singapore Cable Car up to Faber Peak. There's a giant Bell of Happiness, but also a fence to tie your personalized mini bell. Antonia in front of the Marina Bay Sands, arguably one of the most famous hotels in the world. This Merlion is the national symbol of Singapore, but also a bit of an inside joke in my family. When my dad decided put Singapore as one of our destinations, he also was adamant about us seeing the giant Merlion. But this one...is ~only~ 8.6 meters tall. Not that it's not huge, but my dad kept saying that the Merlion he visited thirty years ago was far, far taller AND that the giant one was the original Merlion. So we kept looking up &quot;giant Merlion&quot; on Google, but we couldn't find it! Eventually, we discovered it was on Sentosa Island, which is certainly still in Singapore, just not as centrally located. Luckily, Singapore is quite small, so we made the trip to see the lovely Sentosa Merlion, which BTW, is a replica. This one is THIRTY SEVEN meters tall! You can ride an elevator up this giant replica, but we decided it wasn't worth the price. As I was writing this, I unfortunately found out it was permanently closed and demolished just over a year ago 😞 But I'm fortunate to have seen it before Singapore had to say goodbye. Without further ado, this is the giant Merlion... Sentosa Merlion ( + ) show me where to go! I hope this guide helped you live vicariously through my 2018 self. I thought a lot about how disconnected I felt with my Chinese heritage, but I’ve been on a journey to understand my roots ever since then. Thank you China, Singapore, Taiwan, Hong Kong, and Macau for an amazing, introspective summer. I am so grateful for food on the table and each of these experiences❤️ HK Harbor</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/beyond/taiwan/taipeifood.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/beyond/taiwan/taipeifood.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Making Mi-so Happy!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jerseyeats/misoteriyaki" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Making Mi-so Happy!" /><published>2021-01-20T00:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2021-01-20T00:00:00-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jerseyeats/misoteriyaki</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jerseyeats/misoteriyaki">&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/jerseyeats/miso/misoteriyaki1.jpg&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;Beef Teriyaki&lt;/div&gt;    
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Serving up everything from teri buns to Korean-style ramen to mixed tempura, &lt;a href=&quot;http://misoteriyaki.com/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Miso Teriyaki&lt;/a&gt; entered the Bergen County dining scene in March 2020. When I saw a teriyaki restaurant coming to Tenafly, it dawned on me that I haven’t had teriyaki in years. Apparently, it’s the unofficial signature dish of Seattle, which now makes me regret not eating it when I had the opportunity to go there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But alas, Miso arrived and according to their logo, they’re based in Seattle! I don’t know their full story, but I would love to interview them to get the full scoop on their roots and why they decided to bring their West Coast food over to &lt;em&gt;freezing Jersey&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Above, you can see their hand trimmed, char-broiled &lt;strong&gt;beef teriyaki&lt;/strong&gt;, which from some angles, kind of just looks like cooked beef. But wow, it packs a punch! If you love beef bulgogi, you may equally enjoy this. The classic “burnt” flavor is present, but not in an overwhelming way that turns you off – if you’ve ever had East Asian barbecue, you know the sensation! You can tell the marinade is deeply embedded throughout the beef and isn’t just added in the last few minutes of cooking. What an incredible dish!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I believe all the teriyaki dishes come with a small container of their teriyaki sauce, but I personally prefer the meat or “substance” (tofu, shrimp, salmon, etc.) of the dish by itself. Save that little sauce vessel for those huge portions of rice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/jerseyeats/miso/yakisoba.jpg&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;singleimageoverlay&quot;&gt;Chicken Yakisoba&lt;/div&gt;    
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay, vegetable galore in this noodle dish. The amount of veggies in their &lt;strong&gt;chicken yakisoba&lt;/strong&gt; would be my only criticism, but not for a dislike of veggies!! I enjoy vegetables, but felt there was an imbalance of noodle to vegetable. I found this a bit odd, since restaurants typically try to overload with carbs rather than the more expensive vegetables. I enjoyed the chicken and the noodles, as I’m a huuuuuuge “thick egg-type” noodle fan, as opposed to thinner spaghetti-like types. Note that they cook their noodles a little under al-dente, so if you prefer less chewy noodles, just request them to be “fully cooked”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/jerseyeats/miso/chickenkatsu.jpg&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Chicken Katsu&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/jerseyeats/miso/ribteriyaki.jpg&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt; 
        &lt;div class=&quot;flexoverlay&quot;&gt;Rib Teriyaki&lt;/div&gt;  
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t know why, but &lt;strong&gt;chicken katsu&lt;/strong&gt; always hits the spot for me. It’s some part of a chicken covered in panko breadcrumbs, BUT OH MY I just love it. Miso serves a katsu sauce that’s not the traditional &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Bull-Dog-Vegetable-Fruit-Tonkatsu-Bottles/dp/B01N5DB4EW&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bull-Dog Tonkatsu Sauce&lt;/a&gt;. I wasn’t able to catch a photo of the sauce, but dare I say, it was better than the Bull-Dog? I may just be making that up – they could very well be the same. Anyway, Miso’s katsu was thinner than I liked, but that’s simply a preference. The katsu is a great pairing to an assortment of otherwise grilled meats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, to the right of the chicken katsu is the &lt;strong&gt;rib teriyaki&lt;/strong&gt;. It’s the winner of these four dishes for me! The ribs are laterally cut – the same way Korean galbi ribs* are. While I think the marinade is likely the same for both, I think the char has the ability to shine more on ribs. With thinner beef, too much char can overpower the taste of the meat itself, while these flanken (lateral) cut ribs need that mild burnt taste to draw out the flavor of the beef.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;fun-fact-if-youve-ever-heard-the-term-la-galbi-the-name-stems-from-either-1-the-korean-communitys-popularization-of-the-dish-in-los-angeles-or-2-the-lateral-cut-style-of-the-ribs&quot;&gt;*Fun fact: If you’ve ever heard the term LA Galbi, the name stems from either 1. the Korean community’s popularization of the dish in Los Angeles or 2. the lateral cut style of the ribs.&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Operating during the pandemic is already a huge challenge, but opening at the beginning of one adds its own obstacles to an already difficult time. I know Miso isn’t alone in this struggle, but if you have the means to support another business right now, keep Miso on your list! They deliver on their commitment to serve exceptional teriyaki, and I hope to try their fried rice and teri bun dishes soon as well.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="jerseyeats" /><summary type="html">Beef Teriyaki Serving up everything from teri buns to Korean-style ramen to mixed tempura, Miso Teriyaki entered the Bergen County dining scene in March 2020. When I saw a teriyaki restaurant coming to Tenafly, it dawned on me that I haven’t had teriyaki in years. Apparently, it’s the unofficial signature dish of Seattle, which now makes me regret not eating it when I had the opportunity to go there. But alas, Miso arrived and according to their logo, they’re based in Seattle! I don’t know their full story, but I would love to interview them to get the full scoop on their roots and why they decided to bring their West Coast food over to freezing Jersey. Above, you can see their hand trimmed, char-broiled beef teriyaki, which from some angles, kind of just looks like cooked beef. But wow, it packs a punch! If you love beef bulgogi, you may equally enjoy this. The classic “burnt” flavor is present, but not in an overwhelming way that turns you off – if you’ve ever had East Asian barbecue, you know the sensation! You can tell the marinade is deeply embedded throughout the beef and isn’t just added in the last few minutes of cooking. What an incredible dish! I believe all the teriyaki dishes come with a small container of their teriyaki sauce, but I personally prefer the meat or “substance” (tofu, shrimp, salmon, etc.) of the dish by itself. Save that little sauce vessel for those huge portions of rice. Chicken Yakisoba Okay, vegetable galore in this noodle dish. The amount of veggies in their chicken yakisoba would be my only criticism, but not for a dislike of veggies!! I enjoy vegetables, but felt there was an imbalance of noodle to vegetable. I found this a bit odd, since restaurants typically try to overload with carbs rather than the more expensive vegetables. I enjoyed the chicken and the noodles, as I’m a huuuuuuge “thick egg-type” noodle fan, as opposed to thinner spaghetti-like types. Note that they cook their noodles a little under al-dente, so if you prefer less chewy noodles, just request them to be “fully cooked”. Chicken Katsu Rib Teriyaki I don’t know why, but chicken katsu always hits the spot for me. It’s some part of a chicken covered in panko breadcrumbs, BUT OH MY I just love it. Miso serves a katsu sauce that’s not the traditional Bull-Dog Tonkatsu Sauce. I wasn’t able to catch a photo of the sauce, but dare I say, it was better than the Bull-Dog? I may just be making that up – they could very well be the same. Anyway, Miso’s katsu was thinner than I liked, but that’s simply a preference. The katsu is a great pairing to an assortment of otherwise grilled meats. Finally, to the right of the chicken katsu is the rib teriyaki. It’s the winner of these four dishes for me! The ribs are laterally cut – the same way Korean galbi ribs* are. While I think the marinade is likely the same for both, I think the char has the ability to shine more on ribs. With thinner beef, too much char can overpower the taste of the meat itself, while these flanken (lateral) cut ribs need that mild burnt taste to draw out the flavor of the beef. *Fun fact: If you’ve ever heard the term LA Galbi, the name stems from either 1. the Korean community’s popularization of the dish in Los Angeles or 2. the lateral cut style of the ribs. Operating during the pandemic is already a huge challenge, but opening at the beginning of one adds its own obstacles to an already difficult time. I know Miso isn’t alone in this struggle, but if you have the means to support another business right now, keep Miso on your list! They deliver on their commitment to serve exceptional teriyaki, and I hope to try their fried rice and teri bun dishes soon as well.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/jerseyeats/miso/misoteriyaki1.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/jerseyeats/miso/misoteriyaki1.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Grandma’s Baozi</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/recipes/grandmabao" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Grandma’s Baozi" /><published>2021-01-06T00:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2021-01-06T00:00:00-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/recipes/grandmabao</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/recipes/grandmabao">&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/recipes/bao/grandmabao.png&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5GajgDBZeoQ&amp;amp;t=3s&amp;amp;ab_channel=bub&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Watch Antonia’s ~cinematography~ of our grandma making baozi&lt;/a&gt;! Please like, comment, and subscribe to the &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCqH5MDmErneKqkCnYxBGnEA&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;bub YouTube channel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, where she posts vlogs from her apartment provided by her internship, and I even make a cameo once in a while for our “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLXr-C5XyXq8c2sFUzGIP5w5HxpAtvWgYF&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;bake w/ bubs&lt;/a&gt;” series! The recipe is transcribed by Antonia, as my grandma speaks in Cantonese throughout.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I promised Antonia I would promo her videos, because she really works beyond hard on each and every one of them! Between the cover art and animations she creates, she really deserves all the love.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="recipes" /><summary type="html">Watch Antonia’s ~cinematography~ of our grandma making baozi! Please like, comment, and subscribe to the bub YouTube channel, where she posts vlogs from her apartment provided by her internship, and I even make a cameo once in a while for our “bake w/ bubs” series! The recipe is transcribed by Antonia, as my grandma speaks in Cantonese throughout. I promised Antonia I would promo her videos, because she really works beyond hard on each and every one of them! Between the cover art and animations she creates, she really deserves all the love.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/recipes/bao/grandmabao.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/recipes/bao/grandmabao.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">The Croissant Chronicles</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/recipes/croissantchronicles" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Croissant Chronicles" /><published>2020-12-23T00:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2020-12-23T00:00:00-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/recipes/croissantchronicles</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/recipes/croissantchronicles">&lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/recipes/croissant/croissantportrait1.jpg&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/recipes/croissant/croissantportrait3.jpg&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I made croissants from scratch for the first time! Ever since my sister, Antonia, a croissant connoisseur (just kidding, she’s only made croissants twice before), told me she made croissants from scratch, I’ve been itching to try making them too. It’s month eight of being totally at home, so we finally decided to tackle this challenge! Many hours later, they were far from perfect, but still the perfect homemade baked good to keep us company. This collaboration is with my big sister, Antonia, an aspiring vlogger.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;watch-our-bake-with-bubs-video-here--like-comment-and-subscribe&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2d7ew5ALNX0&amp;amp;ab_channel=bub&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;WATCH OUR BAKE WITH BUBS VIDEO HERE ~ Like, Comment, AND Subscribe!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/recipes/croissant/croissantfood/croissantsolo1.jpg&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/recipes/croissant/croissantfood/blueberrycroissant.JPEG&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Recipe adapted from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jocooks.com/recipes/homemade-croissants/&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Jo Cooks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; - great recipe!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;croissants-from-scratch&quot;&gt;Croissants From Scratch&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&quot;yields-8-medium-croissants-but-you-can-make-16-smaller-ones-instead&quot;&gt;Yields 8 medium croissants, but you can make ~16 smaller ones instead&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ingredients&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;¾ cup lukewarm milk&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;⅛ cup packed brown sugar&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1½ tsp active dry yeast&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;3½ cups all-purpose flour &lt;em&gt;(may need as little as 3¼ or as much as 4 cups)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;¾ cup salted butter, &lt;em&gt;if using unsalted butter, add ½ tbsp salt&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;½ egg for egg wash&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Lightly stir lukewarm milk, brown sugar, and yeast with a fork in your mixing bowl. Let sit for 5 minutes, until foamy.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Add flour (and salt, &lt;strong&gt;if using unsalted butter&lt;/strong&gt;) to the bowl 1 cup at a time, and mix until soft, elastic, but still a little bit sticky.
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Start off with a sturdy spatula, then move on to kneading with your hands.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Loosely wrap the dough in plastic wrap and place the dough in a bowl. Refrigerate for one hour.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Make. The. Butter. Layer.&lt;/strong&gt; Y’all, this is the moment I was looking forward to the most, because of how fun recipe videos made it look. &lt;em&gt;It was fun.&lt;/em&gt; Cut the butter into evenly sized (especially the &lt;strong&gt;thickness&lt;/strong&gt;; the other dimensions are less important). Arrange the layers into a rectangular formation onto a sheet of plastic wrap (what we did) or parchment paper (what we would recommend). Place another equally-sized sheet on top of the butter rectangle.
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Parchment paper is a lot less clingy than plastic wrap, which is why we recommend it.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;The sheet of plastic/parchment should be considerably larger than the rectangle of butter. I recommend skipping to &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/2d7ew5ALNX0?t=102&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;1:42&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; to see how large our rectangle of wrap was.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Use a rolling pin to roll out on all sides of the butter rectangle. Be very careful when rolling this butter rectangle out. The rectangle shouldn’t be over rolled on any one side, as this would distort the rectangular formation. I recommend alternating the orientation of the rolling pin from vertical to horizontal several times through this process. See &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/2d7ew5ALNX0?t=102&quot; class=&quot;nounderline&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;2:04&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; to get an idea of what we did for ours.
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;We had a pretty imperfect rectangle, so I wouldn’t be discouraged if yours comes out a bit wonky looking. However, don’t veer too far off the intended rectangle, and definitely try your best to attain that shape!&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Refrigerate the dough&lt;/strong&gt; until use. This is important. You do not want this butter to be melty in the slightest, as the kitchen itself already has heat. This heat will soften your butter with time, but this butter sheet needs to be very firm!&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Flour your work surface, whether that be directly on your countertop or on a large tray (like ours), and roll out the dough into a rectangle that’s about 5 millimeters thick. The other dimensions are a little bit more up to you, because a bunch of different recipes give different sizes. Just make sure that the height of the dough rectangle is about equal to the width of the butter sheet.
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;To clarify, the width is the longest side (in reference to either the individual butter or dough sheet). The height is the shorter dimension.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Place your butter sheet in the center of the dough rectangle. This butter sheet should be ⅓ of the dough - you can think of the dough not &lt;em&gt;currently&lt;/em&gt; in contact with the butter as flaps! These flaps should be just slightly larger than the butter sheet rectangle.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fold these two flaps over the butter sheet one after another, similar to how a letter is folded. Now, move your rolling pin vertically (the “height” or shorter side of the dough should be closest to you) to form another rectangle that is similar sized to the dimensions of the original dough rectangle.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fold the dough rectangle like a letter again (thirds!) Place it on a tray, and wrap the tray in plastic wrap. Refrigerate for one hour.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This step needs to be repeated 3 times, meaning four times in addition to the previous step&lt;/strong&gt;! Move your rolling pin vertically (the “height” or shorter side of the dough should be closest to you) to form another rectangle that is similar sized to the dimensions of the original dough rectangle. Fold the dough rectangle like a letter (in thirds). Place it on a tray, and wrap the tray in plastic wrap. Refrigerate for one hour, &lt;strong&gt;with the exception of the fourth time&lt;/strong&gt;. &lt;em&gt;Refrigerate (at least) overnight only for the fourth (final) time&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Split the dough in half - freeze one half if you plan on using it another time. Roll the dough halves into long, ¼ inch thick rectangles. Cut each rectangle into triangles (more like an isosceles). They really can be any length you want, but you can probably cut 4-12 from each half.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Use a rolling pin to “flatten” each triangle from the wide side up. Stretch out the skinny side and begin rolling your triangle as tightly as possible!&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Place each triangle 1 to 2 inches apart on a baking sheet lined with parchment paper.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Let the croissants rise a bit for one more hour - you’re almost there! Brush them with egg wash.
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;You can also roll them ahead of time, then refrigerate for up to 18 hours prior to baking. Wrap the baking with plastic wrap, not tightly or loosely, but just tight enough so as little moisture as possible escapes.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Preheat the oven to 400°F. Get those croissants in the oven and bake for 8 to 12 minutes at 400°F, then turn down the heat to 375°F and bake them for another 8 to 12 minutes. They should be golden brown!&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Enjoy with whatever spreads, jams, sauces, and anything you like! We tried them with several fruit jams (blueberry, fig, strawberry, and more).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;flex-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/recipes/croissant/croissantfood/buttersheet.jpg&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex-item&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/recipes/croissant/croissantfood/readytobakecroissant.jpg&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes, this is a loooonnnnngggggg process, but I can confidently say the end result is worth it. My sister made them without me one additional time after the filming of this video, and I enjoyed them so much. They are FAR from perfect, but are still an unbelievably good treat. &lt;em&gt;Warning&lt;/em&gt;: they ARE buttery, but equally flaky. Now, start the recipe and devour these little pockets of goodness!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;final-results&quot;&gt;FINAL RESULTS!🤩&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;singleimagecontainer&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/recipes/croissant/croissantfood/croissant2.jpg&quot; class=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;they-look-like-they-have-such-a-solid-bottom-because-we-over-egg-washed---no-worries-if-this-happens-to-you-as-theyre-still-awesome&quot;&gt;They look like they have such a solid bottom, because we over egg-washed - no worries if this happens to you, as they’re still awesome.&lt;/h6&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="recipes" /><summary type="html">I made croissants from scratch for the first time! Ever since my sister, Antonia, a croissant connoisseur (just kidding, she’s only made croissants twice before), told me she made croissants from scratch, I’ve been itching to try making them too. It’s month eight of being totally at home, so we finally decided to tackle this challenge! Many hours later, they were far from perfect, but still the perfect homemade baked good to keep us company. This collaboration is with my big sister, Antonia, an aspiring vlogger. WATCH OUR BAKE WITH BUBS VIDEO HERE ~ Like, Comment, AND Subscribe! Recipe adapted from Jo Cooks - great recipe! Croissants From Scratch Yields 8 medium croissants, but you can make ~16 smaller ones instead Ingredients ¾ cup lukewarm milk ⅛ cup packed brown sugar 1½ tsp active dry yeast 3½ cups all-purpose flour (may need as little as 3¼ or as much as 4 cups) ¾ cup salted butter, if using unsalted butter, add ½ tbsp salt ½ egg for egg wash Directions Lightly stir lukewarm milk, brown sugar, and yeast with a fork in your mixing bowl. Let sit for 5 minutes, until foamy. Add flour (and salt, if using unsalted butter) to the bowl 1 cup at a time, and mix until soft, elastic, but still a little bit sticky. Start off with a sturdy spatula, then move on to kneading with your hands. Loosely wrap the dough in plastic wrap and place the dough in a bowl. Refrigerate for one hour. Make. The. Butter. Layer. Y’all, this is the moment I was looking forward to the most, because of how fun recipe videos made it look. It was fun. Cut the butter into evenly sized (especially the thickness; the other dimensions are less important). Arrange the layers into a rectangular formation onto a sheet of plastic wrap (what we did) or parchment paper (what we would recommend). Place another equally-sized sheet on top of the butter rectangle. Parchment paper is a lot less clingy than plastic wrap, which is why we recommend it. The sheet of plastic/parchment should be considerably larger than the rectangle of butter. I recommend skipping to 1:42 to see how large our rectangle of wrap was. Use a rolling pin to roll out on all sides of the butter rectangle. Be very careful when rolling this butter rectangle out. The rectangle shouldn’t be over rolled on any one side, as this would distort the rectangular formation. I recommend alternating the orientation of the rolling pin from vertical to horizontal several times through this process. See 2:04 to get an idea of what we did for ours. We had a pretty imperfect rectangle, so I wouldn’t be discouraged if yours comes out a bit wonky looking. However, don’t veer too far off the intended rectangle, and definitely try your best to attain that shape! Refrigerate the dough until use. This is important. You do not want this butter to be melty in the slightest, as the kitchen itself already has heat. This heat will soften your butter with time, but this butter sheet needs to be very firm! Flour your work surface, whether that be directly on your countertop or on a large tray (like ours), and roll out the dough into a rectangle that’s about 5 millimeters thick. The other dimensions are a little bit more up to you, because a bunch of different recipes give different sizes. Just make sure that the height of the dough rectangle is about equal to the width of the butter sheet. To clarify, the width is the longest side (in reference to either the individual butter or dough sheet). The height is the shorter dimension. Place your butter sheet in the center of the dough rectangle. This butter sheet should be ⅓ of the dough - you can think of the dough not currently in contact with the butter as flaps! These flaps should be just slightly larger than the butter sheet rectangle. Fold these two flaps over the butter sheet one after another, similar to how a letter is folded. Now, move your rolling pin vertically (the “height” or shorter side of the dough should be closest to you) to form another rectangle that is similar sized to the dimensions of the original dough rectangle. Fold the dough rectangle like a letter again (thirds!) Place it on a tray, and wrap the tray in plastic wrap. Refrigerate for one hour. This step needs to be repeated 3 times, meaning four times in addition to the previous step! Move your rolling pin vertically (the “height” or shorter side of the dough should be closest to you) to form another rectangle that is similar sized to the dimensions of the original dough rectangle. Fold the dough rectangle like a letter (in thirds). Place it on a tray, and wrap the tray in plastic wrap. Refrigerate for one hour, with the exception of the fourth time. Refrigerate (at least) overnight only for the fourth (final) time. Split the dough in half - freeze one half if you plan on using it another time. Roll the dough halves into long, ¼ inch thick rectangles. Cut each rectangle into triangles (more like an isosceles). They really can be any length you want, but you can probably cut 4-12 from each half. Use a rolling pin to “flatten” each triangle from the wide side up. Stretch out the skinny side and begin rolling your triangle as tightly as possible! Place each triangle 1 to 2 inches apart on a baking sheet lined with parchment paper. Let the croissants rise a bit for one more hour - you’re almost there! Brush them with egg wash. You can also roll them ahead of time, then refrigerate for up to 18 hours prior to baking. Wrap the baking with plastic wrap, not tightly or loosely, but just tight enough so as little moisture as possible escapes. Preheat the oven to 400°F. Get those croissants in the oven and bake for 8 to 12 minutes at 400°F, then turn down the heat to 375°F and bake them for another 8 to 12 minutes. They should be golden brown! Enjoy with whatever spreads, jams, sauces, and anything you like! We tried them with several fruit jams (blueberry, fig, strawberry, and more). Yes, this is a loooonnnnngggggg process, but I can confidently say the end result is worth it. My sister made them without me one additional time after the filming of this video, and I enjoyed them so much. They are FAR from perfect, but are still an unbelievably good treat. Warning: they ARE buttery, but equally flaky. Now, start the recipe and devour these little pockets of goodness! FINAL RESULTS!🤩 They look like they have such a solid bottom, because we over egg-washed - no worries if this happens to you, as they’re still awesome.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/recipes/croissant/croissantportrait1.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/recipes/croissant/croissantportrait1.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry></feed>